<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime</id><title>AI Daily Short Story</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.893638+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime" rel="self"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><logo>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/ai_generated_stories.png</logo><subtitle>A daily pod cast of an AI generated short story</subtitle><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-24-one-day,-a-rich-man-sat-in-his-big-chair.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-24 - One day, a rich man sat in his big chair</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.974827+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a rich man sat in his big chair. He ate a big waffle. It was very yummy. He wanted to share it with his friends. So, he called his friends and said, "Come to my house. I have a big waffle to share."His friends came to his house. They sat in chairs and ate the waffle together. They were very happy. But then, something unexpected happened. A little bird flew into the house. The bird landed on the big chair.The little bird looked at the waffle and said, "Can I have some waffle too?" The rich man and his friends were surprised. They did not know that birds could talk. But they shared their waffle with the little bird.The bird ate the waffle very fast. It was so full that the bird started to weep. The rich man and his friends felt sad for the bird. They wanted to make it feel better.In the end, the rich man and his friends gave the bird more waffle. The bird stopped weeping and became very happy. They all became good friends and ate waffles together every day.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/24/one-day,-a-rich-man-sat-in-his-big-chair.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/24/one-day,-a-rich-man-sat-in-his-big-chair.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-24-one-day,-a-rich-man-sat-in-his-big-chair.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-23-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-mom-and-her-daughter.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-23 - Once upon a time, there was a mom and her daughter</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.973989+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a mom and her daughter. They lived in a small house. The daughter loved to play with her toys and make a big mess. One day, the mom said, "Daughter, your room is very messy. Let's clean it up."While they were cleaning, the mom found a pretty toy that could glow. She showed it to her daughter and said, "Look, this toy can glow at night. It is so fun to play with when it is dark."That night, the daughter took the glowing toy to bed with her. The toy made her room glow with a soft light. She was so happy and said, "Thank you, mom, for showing me the glowing toy. I love it!"The mom smiled and said, "You're welcome, my little star. Now you know the importance of keeping your room clean." And from that day on, the daughter always made sure her room was clean and her toys were dry.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/23/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-mom-and-her-daughter.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/23/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-mom-and-her-daughter.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-23-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-mom-and-her-daughter.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-were-two-twins-named-tim-and-tom.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-22 - Once upon a time, there were two twins named Tim and Tom</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.973158+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there were two twins named Tim and Tom. They were always together and loved to play. One day, they went to the park to play on the slide. Tim went first and slid down the slide very fast. Tom wanted to try too, but he was scared.Tim said, "Don't be scared, Tom! It's fun!" But Tom was still scared. Tim then had an idea. He said, "Let's go down the slide one more time, but this time we'll go down together." So they did, and it was so much fun that Tom forgot to be scared.After they finished playing, they went home and their mom asked how their day was. Tom said, "It was fun! We went down the slide and it was very fast. But then we went down the slide and our mom said we were scared. That's crazy!" Their mom smiled and said, "I'm glad you had fun, but next time make sure you're not so scared." The twins nodded and promised to be more careful.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-were-two-twins-named-tim-and-tom.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-were-two-twins-named-tim-and-tom.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-were-two-twins-named-tim-and-tom.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-21 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.972402+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play outside with her friends. One day, they were playing with a ball when suddenly it rolled into a net. The net was big and strong, but it was also very good at catching things.Lily went to get the ball, and when she looked inside the net, she saw a surprise! There was a little bird inside, and it looked hurt. Lily knew she had to help the bird, so she carefully took it out of the net.She called her mommy to come and pick the bird up. They took it to the vet and made sure it was okay. Lily was very happy that she could help the bird, and she felt good inside because she did the right thing.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-20 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.971396+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She liked to play with her toys and run around outside. One day, her mommy asked her if she wanted to help make dinner. Lily didn't know what to do, so her mommy taught her how to chop vegetables with a big knife.Lily thought it was funny that the knife was so sharp and shiny. She liked helping her mommy cook dinner and they made yummy spaghetti together. After dinner, Lily went to bed and fell asleep right away because she was so tired from all the fun she had that day.The end.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-19 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.970485+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to pretend that she was a princess and would wear a big, sparkly crown on her head. One day, she decided to go on an adventure in the forest near her house.As she walked through the trees, she saw a group of animals having a race. One of the animals was a fast rabbit, and the others were slow and competitive. Lily wanted to join in on the fun, so she asked if she could race too.The rabbit said yes, and they started to run. Lily was not the fastest, but she pretended that she was the fastest runner in the forest. She ran as fast as she could and even though she did not win, she had a great time pretending to be a brave racer.When she got back home, she told her mom all about her adventure in the forest. Her mom was so proud of her for using her imagination and having fun. From that day on, Lily loved to pretend and use her imagination to go on exciting adventures.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-18-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-named-george.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-18 - Once upon a time there was a boy named George</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.969640+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time there was a boy named George. He was so excited for his first day of school and all the nice things he would get to do.When he arrived home, George was feeling a bit nervous. He didn't know anyone or anything to be petted or played with.His mum noticed and came over to him. She said, "Don't worry, George. I'm here to comfort you." She gave him a big hug and said that everything was going to be easy.George felt a bit better and smiled. He knew he wasn't alone and that his mum was always there to make him feel better. Together they went off to school the next day.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/18/once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-named-george.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/18/once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-named-george.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-18-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-named-george.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-17-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-outside.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-17 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily who loved to play outside</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.968771+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily who loved to play outside. One day, she saw a cute little puppy and she wanted to pet it. But when she got close, the puppy bit her finger! It hurt a lot and Lily started to cry.Her mom came running over and asked, "What happened, Lily?" Lily said, "The puppy bit me and it hurts." Her mom looked at her finger and saw that it was red and swollen. She said, "Let's go inside and clean it up."When they went inside, Lily's big brother came in and asked what happened. Lily was still crying and her brother said, "Don't worry, Lily. I'll go get the puppy's owner and he can help us." Lily's brother went outside and talked to his neighbor. He told them about the puppy and the owner. Soon, the owner came over and helped clean the puppy's paw. Lily felt better and thanked her brother for helping her.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/17/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-outside.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/17/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-outside.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-17-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-outside.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-16 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.968127+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim. Tim had a toy car with a high wheel. He loved to play with his car all day.One day, Tim saw a girl named Sue. Sue was sad because she had no toys to play with. Tim wanted to help Sue, so he said, "Sue, do you want to play with my car?" Sue smiled and said, "Yes, please!"Tim and Sue played with the car together. They had so much fun! But then, Tim's mom said, "Tim, you must pay for the ice cream we just bought." Tim gave Sue some money, and Sue gave Tim a big hug. They both enjoyed their ice cream and became best friends.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-15-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-15 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.967370+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to eat mint candies, especially the green ones. One day, she went to the store with her mom to buy some more. While they were there, they saw a man who was acting foolish. He was wearing a funny hat and dancing around.Lily's mom told her to stay away from the man and they continued to buy their mint candies. But Lily couldn't resist the snolalph and wanted to say hi to the man. She walked over to him and gave him a mint candy. The man smiled and thanked her.Lily was happy that she could make the man smile. She went home with her mom and shared her mint candies with her little brother. From that day on, Lily always remembered the man at the store who started acting foolish and made her smile.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/15/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/15/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-15-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-14-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-14 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.966623+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim. Tim liked to pack his toy truck with blocks. He wanted to build a very tall tower. Tim tried and tried, but it was not easy.One day, Tim found a magic toy car. The car had the power to make the tower easy to build. Tim asked the magic car to help him. The car said, "I will help you, but you must promise to share the blocks with me."Tim agreed, and they built the tower together. The magic car's power made the tower easy to build. Tim was so happy. The magic car kept its promise and shared the blocks with Tim. They played together and had lots of fun. And from that day on, Tim and the magic car were best friends.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/14/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/14/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-14-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-13-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-13 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.965777+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim. Tim loved to watch videos on his mom's phone. One day, while he was watching a video, his mom said, "Tim, please turn down the video. It is time for bed."But Tim did not want to stop watching the video. He refused to turn off the phone. "No, Mom. I want to watch more video," he said. His mom looked at him and knew that he did not want to go to bed.Tim's mom said, "Tim, it is not fair for you to watch too much video. You need to sleep and be a good boy." Tim thought about it and knew his mom was right. He turned off the phone and went to bed. From that day on, Tim made sure to turn off the screen and go to bed when it was time.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/13/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/13/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-13-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-13-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-truck.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-13 - Once upon a time, there was a big truck</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.964914+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a big truck. The truck was very heavy and it had to carry a lot of things. One day, the truck was driving down the road when it saw a big cliff. The truck was scared and didn't know what to do.But then, the truck remembered something its driver had told it before. "Relax, everything will be okay," the driver had said. So the truck took a deep breath and tried to relax. It closed its eyes and took a deep breath in and out.Suddenly, the truck felt better. It realized that even though it was heavy and scared, it could still be brave and strong. And with that swore to face any chase that came its way. So the truck drove onto the road and continued on its way, feeling proud and happy.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/13/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-truck.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/13/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-truck.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-13-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-truck.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-12-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lucy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-12 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lucy</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.964052+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lucy. She loved to design things. One day, she wanted to make a chair. Lucy was very excited.Lucy was very careful while making the chair. She put big wood and a soft cushion on top. When she was done, she wanted to show her mom and dad.But when Lucy tried to sit on the chair, something unexpected happened. The chair moved! It was not a chair, it was a big turtle! The turtle said, "Hello, Lucy!" Lucy was surprised but happy. She made a new friend and they played together.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/12/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lucy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/12/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lucy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-12-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lucy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-11-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-who-loved-to-play-with-his-toys.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-11 - Once upon a time, there was a boy who loved to play with his toys</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.963146+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a boy who loved to play with his toys. One day, he wanted to play with his favorite toy, but it was in the attic. He climbed up the ladder to get it, but he accidentally knocked over a box. The box shook and a scary monster came out!The boy was scared and ran away, but the monster chased him. The boy thought he was going to be caught, but then he saw a grumpy old man walking by. The man asked the boy what was wrong, and the boy told him about the monster. The old man laughed and said, "That's just the spirit of the toy! It's supposed to shake and move by itself."The boy didn't believe him at first, but then he turned around and saw that the monster was gone. He was so happy and thanked the old man. From that day on, the boy learned to be careful when playing with his toys in the attic, but he also learned that sometimes things that seem scary can turn out to be fun at the full price.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/11/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-who-loved-to-play-with-his-toys.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/11/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-who-loved-to-play-with-his-toys.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-11-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-who-loved-to-play-with-his-toys.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-10-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big,-red-couch.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-10 - Once upon a time, there was a big, red couch</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.962319+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a big, red couch. It was in a room where many kids liked to play. One day, a little boy named Tim and his friend, Sue, were playing near the couch. They were running around and laughing."Stop!" said Tim. "We need to be careful near the couch." Sue looked at Tim and said, "Okay, let's play on the floor." They played happily on the floor, but then they heard a strange noise.The noise came from the couch! They stopped and listened carefully. Tim and Sue were scared, but they wanted to know what was making the noise. They slowly walked closer to the couch and looked inside. To their surprise, they found a little, lost kitten! The kitten was scared too, but Tim and Sue were kind to it. They took the kitten out of the couch and played with it all day long. The kitten became their new friend, and they all lived happily ever after.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/10/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big,-red-couch.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/10/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big,-red-couch.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-10-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big,-red-couch.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-09-lily-and-tom-were-twins-who-liked-to-play-with-their-toys.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-09 - Lily and Tom were twins who liked to play with their toys</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.961468+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Lily and Tom were twins who liked to play with their toys. One day, they found a big box in the living room. It had a red ribbon on it and a note that said: "To Lily and Tom, from Grandma and Grandpa. Happy birthday!"Lily and Tom were very excited. They wanted to see what was inside the box. They tried to open it, but it was too hard. They pulled and pushed on the ribbon, but it did not move."Maybe we need to ask Mom for help," Lily said."Or maybe we need to pull harder," Tom said.They decided to do both. They helped each other to pull the ribbon harder. They pulled and pulled until the ribbon came off with a loud pop. The box opened and they saw a lot of shiny things inside.Lily and Tom gasped. They saw many necklaces, bracelets, rings, and earrings. They were all different colors and shapes. Lily saw a clear necklace that sparkled like stars. She wanted to try it on."Wow, look at this!" Lily said. She took the necklace and</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/09/lily-and-tom-were-twins-who-liked-to-play-with-their-toys.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/09/lily-and-tom-were-twins-who-liked-to-play-with-their-toys.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-09-lily-and-tom-were-twins-who-liked-to-play-with-their-toys.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-08-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-08 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.960631+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved spending time with her daddy. One day, they went to the park to play. While they were there, they saw a harmless little bunny hopping around.Lily wanted to play with the bunny, but her daddy said they couldn't because it might hurt the bunny. So, they just watched the bunny hop around for a little while.After a few minutes, Lily's daddy asked her if she wanted to go home. Lily thought about it and decided that she wanted to spend some time with her daddy more than she wanted to play with the bunny. So, they walked back home together, happy to have spent time with each other. The end.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/08/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/08/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-08-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-07-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-07 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.959783+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play with her toys, but her favorite toy was her chicken toy. One day, Lily's mom told her it was time to bathe. Lily didn't want to stop playing with her chicken, but her mom said it was important to stay clean.Lily went to the bathroom and her mom helped her get in the tub. She pretended to be a mermaid and splashed around. After her bath, Lily's mom wrapped her in a warm towel and dried her off. Lily felt so clean and cozy.Later that day, Lily's dad came home from work. He had a harsh tone when he saw Lily's clean face. But Lily didn't mind because she knew it was time to play with her chicken toy again. She hugged it tightly and played with it until it was time for bed.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/07/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/07/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-07-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-06-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-king.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-06 - Once upon a time, there was a king</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.958887+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a king. The king was very brave. One day, he went for a walk in the forest.In the forest, the king saw a big tree. He wanted to climb it. As he climbed, the tree started to rock. The king was scared, but he was brave.Suddenly, a big bird came out of the tree. The bird said, "Don't be scared, I live in this tree." The king and the bird became friends. They played together and had lots of fun.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/06/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-king.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/06/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-king.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-06-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-king.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-05-one-day,-a-girl-named-sue-went-to-the-park-with-her-mom.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-05 - One day, a girl named Sue went to the park with her mom</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.958039+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a girl named Sue went to the park with her mom. They had a big bag with them. In the bag, there were many yummy things to eat. They also had a cooler with them. The cooler was tight, but Sue did not know that.At the park, Sue saw a boy named Tim. Tim was playing with a ball. Sue wanted to play too. They played together and had lots of fun. Then, Sue's mom opened the cooler to give them food and drinks. But the cooler was not full yet. Sue's mom was worried that they would not have enough food for everyone.Sue had an idea. She said, "Let's make the food increase!" Sue and Tim put more food in the cooler. They found more yummy things to put in the cooler. Soon, the cooler was full again. Everyone was happy, and they all enjoyed the food. Sue and Tim kept playing and became good friends.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/05/one-day,-a-girl-named-sue-went-to-the-park-with-her-mom.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/05/one-day,-a-girl-named-sue-went-to-the-park-with-her-mom.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-05-one-day,-a-girl-named-sue-went-to-the-park-with-her-mom.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-05-one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-outside-to-play.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-05 - One day, a boy named Tim went outside to play</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.957223+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a boy named Tim went outside to play. It was very cold and icy. Tim saw a big tree and decided to climb it. He climbed up and up, all the way to the top. From there, he could see the whole park.As Tim sat on a branch, he saw a little bird shivering in the cold. He felt sad for the bird and made a promise. "I promise to help you, little bird," Tim said. He picked up the bird and put it in his warm pocket.But then, something unexpected happened! The bird started to laugh and said, "Thank you, Tim! I'm not really a bird. I'm a fairy in disguise!" The fairy waved her wand, and the icy tree became warm and cozy. Tim and the fairy played on the tree all day, laughing and having fun.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/05/one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-outside-to-play.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/05/one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-outside-to-play.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-05-one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-outside-to-play.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bird-named-tweety.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-05 - Once upon a time, there was a little bird named Tweety</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.956390+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little bird named Tweety. Tweety loved to fly around and sing songs to all his friends. One day, Tweety saw a big, dark cloud in the sky. He knew it was going to rain soon.Tweety flew to his friend, a little mouse named Jerry, and told him about the cloud. "Jerry, we need to find a safe place to hide from the rain," Tweety said. "I know just the place," Jerry replied. He led Tweety to a tree with a big hole in it. "We'll go in here," Jerry said.As they crawled inside the tree, they heard someone whispering orders. It was the squirrel, Mr. Nutty. "You must stay here until the rain stops," he said. "No, we can't," Tweety said. "The rain is harmless and we need to stay safe." Then they listened to the squirrel's orders and waited until the rain stopped. When they came out of the tree, they saw that everything was wet, but they were happy they had listened to the squirrel's orders.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bird-named-tweety.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bird-named-tweety.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bird-named-tweety.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-family.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-05 - Once upon a time, there was a family</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.955534+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a family. The family had a dad, a mom, and a little boy named Tim. Tim was a nosy boy. He liked to know what his mom and dad were doing.One day, Tim saw his mom and dad discuss something. They were talking about whether they should have a new baby. Tim thought it was a big job. He wanted to help with the news.Tim tried to discuss with his mom and dad. He said, "I think it is good." But they did not listen. They got very mad at each other. They decided not to have a new baby. Tim was sad and lonely without his family.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-family.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-family.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-family.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-cat-named-tom.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-05 - Once upon a time, there was a cat named Tom</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.954620+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a cat named Tom. Tom liked to eat cream. One day, he saw a big bowl of cream on the table. Tom wanted to eat the cream very much.Tom jumped on the table and started to drink the cream. But, he did not know that the cream was spicy. Tom's mouth felt hot and he did not like it. He wanted to drink some water to help, but he could not find any.Tom's friend, a dog named Max, saw Tom on the table. Max knew how to help Tom. Max gave Tom a bowl of water. The story ends with Tom feeling better, and Max telling Tom to be careful with spicy things.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-cat-named-tom.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-cat-named-tom.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-cat-named-tom.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-04 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.953555+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to walk on the street with her mommy. One day, while they were walking, Lily saw a big, round ball on the street. She wanted to play with it, but she was too nervous to go near it.Her mommy noticed that Lily was feeling nervous and asked her what was wrong. Lily told her mommy about the ball and how she was too scared to go near it. Her mommy smiled and said, "Don't worry, I'll push you to the ball so you can play with it." Lily felt happy and grateful to her mommy for helping her. They walked to the ball together and Lily had so much fun playing with it. From that day on, Lily wasn't nervous anymore when she saw something on the street.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-04 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.952826+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim. Tim loved to go on vacation with his family. One day, Tim's family went on a vacation to a place where the sun was always shining.On this vacation, Tim saw a big, scary tree. He was scared and told his mom, "Mom, I don't believe there is a scary tree in the park." His mom smiled and said, "Don't worry, Tim. The tree is just big and scary because it has lots of leaves."Later, Tim met a new friend named Lily. Lily was not scared of the big, scary tree. She said, "Tim, I was scared too, but now I believe there is nothing to be scared of." Tim and Lily played together under the tree and had a lot of fun.At the end of the vacation, Tim learned that sometimes things that look scary are not so scary after all. He also learned that it's good to believe in yourself and your friends. And from that day on, Tim and Lily became best friends.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-04 - Once upon a time, there was a girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.951901+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a girl named Lily. She had a pale face and loved playing with her dolls. One day, Lily's mom asked her to help sort the clothes. Lily happily agreed and started sorting the clothes into piles.As she was sorting, Lily found a button that she had never seen before. She picked up the button and showed it to her mom. "Look, Mommy! A pretty button!" Lily exclaimed.Her mom smiled and said, "That's a nice button, Lily. Do you want to keep it?"Lily nodded excitedly and put the button in her pocket. From that day on, Lily always kept the button with her whenever she sorted the clothes. She felt very proud of herself for being such a good helper.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-charming-bird-named-blue.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-04 - Once upon a time, there was a charming bird named Blue</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.950968+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a charming bird named Blue. Blue loved to soar high in the sky. One day, Blue saw a hotel far away. Blue was very happy and wanted to go there.Blue flew to the hotel and saw many people. They were all having fun. Blue saw a little girl named Sue. Sue was sad because she lost her toy. Blue wanted to help Sue.Blue soared high in the sky and looked for the toy. He found it near a tree. Blue took the toy back to Sue. Sue was very happy and thanked Blue. Blue and Sue became best friends.The moral of the story is: Help others when they need it.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-charming-bird-named-blue.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-charming-bird-named-blue.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-charming-bird-named-blue.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-03-one-day,-a-cheerful-girl-named-lily-went-to-the-park.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-03 - One day, a cheerful girl named Lily went to the park</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.950113+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a cheerful girl named Lily went to the park. She saw her friend, Tim, who was trying to tie his shoes. Tim looked sad because he could not do it. Lily wanted to help Tim, so she went to him.Lily said, "I can help you tie your shoes, Tim." Tim was happy to have Lily's help. They tried and tried, but Tim still could not tie his shoes. Then, an older boy named Ben saw them and laughed. Ben did not think they could do it.Tim felt sad and Lily said, "Don't listen to Ben. We can do it if we try together." They tried one more time, and this time, they did it! Tim was very happy, and Lily was proud of their success.The moral of the story is to never give up and always help your friends. Sometimes, all you need to do is try a little harder, and you will succeed.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/03/one-day,-a-cheerful-girl-named-lily-went-to-the-park.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/03/one-day,-a-cheerful-girl-named-lily-went-to-the-park.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-03-one-day,-a-cheerful-girl-named-lily-went-to-the-park.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-03-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-03 - Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.949364+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy. Timmy loved going to the gym with his mom. He would run and jump and play with the other kids. One day, Timmy's mom asked him if he wanted to go to a new gym. Timmy said yes, but he didn't like the new gym. It was not as fun as his old gym.Timmy's mom was persistent and kept asking him to go to the new gym. She told him that it was important to be healthy and grow strong. Timmy didn't listen and kept saying no. But, his mom knew that Timmy needed to try new things, so she decided to record it on her phone.The next time they went to the new gym, Timmy saw that he had lots of fun playing with the other kids. He felt happy and healthy. Timmy learned that it's important to try new things, even if they're not what you're used to.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/03/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/03/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-03-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-03-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bald-man-named-tom.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-03 - Once upon a time, there was a bald man named Tom</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.948479+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a bald man named Tom. Tom loved to play with his friends in the park. One day, Tom found a small box with a lock. He was very curious about what was inside the box. He asked his friends to help him open the lock, but they could not. Tom decided to keep the box safe until he could find the key.Days went by, and Tom did not find the key. He was sad and thought about the box. One day, while playing in the park, he saw a key on the ground. He picked it up and thought it might open the lock. Tom was very excited and ran back to his house to try the key.Tom tried the key on the lock, and it opened! Inside the box, he found a beautiful necklace. He was so happy that he decided to give it to his mom as a gift. His mom was very proud of him for keeping the necklace safe. Tom learned that keeping things safe and trying hard can bring happiness.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/03/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bald-man-named-tom.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/03/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bald-man-named-tom.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-03-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bald-man-named-tom.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-03-once-upon-a-time,-a-little-boy-named-tim-had-a-big-book.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-03 - Once upon a time, a little boy named Tim had a big book</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.947615+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, a little boy named Tim had a big book. The book was full of history. He loved to read it every day. One day, while reading, he heard a voice. The voice said, "Hello, Tim. I am the history book. I can talk to you."Tim was very surprised. He said, "Wow, you can talk! That is amazing. I would love to hear a story from you. But, you must be serious. A story about a bad man who breaks everything."The history book said, "Okay, Tim. I will tell you a story about a bad man who broke many things. He was not nice, and no one liked him."Tim listened to the history book's story. He learned about the bad man who broke many things. Tim said, "Thank you for the story, history book. I will be serious when I read you."From that day on, Tim and the history book became good friends. Tim was serious when he read the history book, and the book was always there to tell him stories.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/03/once-upon-a-time,-a-little-boy-named-tim-had-a-big-book.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/03/once-upon-a-time,-a-little-boy-named-tim-had-a-big-book.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-03-once-upon-a-time,-a-little-boy-named-tim-had-a-big-book.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-02-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-02 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.946700+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to explore the forest and find new things. One day, she found a shiny rock that she thought was very pretty. She showed it to her friend, a talking bunny named Benny.Benny said, "That's a mineral, Lily. It's very special and valuable." Lily was happy to hear that and put the mineral in her pocket.As they were walking, they saw a big, scary bear. Benny said, "We need to be careful, Lily. Bears can be dangerous." Lily was scared, but she remembered that she had a secret weapon. She reached into her pocket and took out the mineral.She held it up and said, "I have this mineral. It's magical and will protect us." Suddenly, the mineral began to glow and shake. The bear was scared and ran away.Lily and Benny were amazed. They had never seen anything like it before. Lily looked at the mineral and said, "I guess this is truly special. Let's keep it safe." From that day</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/02/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/02/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-02-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-01-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-01 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.945824+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play outside and look for pretty things. One day, she saw a butterfly flying in the sky. It was so beautiful and colorful. She wanted to catch it, so she ran after it.As she was running, she saw her mom calling her for lunch. She was so hungry that she forgot about the butterfly and went inside. Her mom had made her favorite sandwich, but when she took a bite, she noticed that it was spoiled. She didn't like it at all.Lily went back outside and saw the beautiful butterfly again. She wanted to catch it, but it flew away. She felt sad and disappointed. She realized that she should have eaten her lunch instead of chasing after the butterfly. From that day on, she always remembered to eat her lunch and not chase after things that were too pretty to catch.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/01/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/01/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-01-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-01-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-brave-princess.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-01 - Once upon a time, there was a brave princess</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.945009+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a brave princess. She was on a mission to save her kingdom from a mean dragon. She rode on her horse and eventually arrived at the dragon's cave.The dragon was very angry when he saw the princess. He breathed fire and growled, but the princess stayed brave and stayed calm. She bravely asked the dragon to start a fight. The dragon was surprised by her bravery and he agreed to fight.The princess used all her strength to beat the dragon. After a long battle, the dragon was so tired that he fell asleep. The princess quickly took the dragon away to the kingdom. Everyone cheered for the brave princess and her victory. The kingdom was safe once again.The end.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/01/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-brave-princess.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/01/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-brave-princess.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-01-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-brave-princess.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-01-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-01 - Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.944190+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a little boy named Tim. Tim loved to read books. He had a big bookcase in his room. The bookcase was full of colorful books.One day, Tim saw a famous book on the top shelf of his bookcase. He wanted to read it, but he was too small to reach it. Tim asked his big sister, Sue, for help. "Sue, can you please help me get the famous book?" he said.Sue was happy to help her brother. She got the book down from the top shelf and gave it to Tim. They read the famous book together and learned many new things. Tim was so happy that he could read the book with Sue's help. And from that day on, they became the best of friends.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/01/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/01/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-01-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-31-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-31 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.943291+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to dance and twirl around in her pink dress. One day, she went to the store with her mommy to buy some ice cream.At the store, Lily saw her friend, Max. Max had a big bag of candy and Lily felt envious. She wanted some candy too. "Can I have some candy, Max?" she asked. Max shook his head and said, "No, Lily. You can't have any candy today."Lily felt sad, but she still danced around the store. As they left, Max's bag of candy fell and spilled all over the floor. "Oh no!" Max cried. "My candy!" Lily saw that Max was upset and decided to help him pick up the candy. They both laughed and danced around the store while they cleaned up the mess. In the end, Max even gave Lily some candy as a thank you.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/31/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/31/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-31-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-31-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-brown-mouse-named-max.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-31 - Once upon a time, there was a little brown mouse named Max</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.942448+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little brown mouse named Max. Max lived in a cozy hole in the wall of a big house. One day, Max heard a loud noise coming from outside. He peeked out and saw a big, scary cat appear in the yard.Max was scared, but he knew he had to stay safe. He ran back to his hole and told his family and friends about the cat. They all worked together to build a strong wall around their hole to protect themselves.The next day, the cat tried to appear at the yard, but he couldn't get through the wall of Max's house. Max felt safe and happy knowing he had protected his family and friends from the scary cat. From then on, Max made sure to always be on the lookout for any danger that might appear in his woodland home.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/31/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-brown-mouse-named-max.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/31/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-brown-mouse-named-max.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-31-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-brown-mouse-named-max.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-31-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-crane.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-31 - Once upon a time, there was a big crane</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.941620+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a big crane. The crane was very tall and had a long neck. It liked to lift heavy things and move them around. One day, the crane saw something unusual. It was a big rock that didn't fit in with the others. The crane tried to lift the rock, but it was too heavy.The crane decided to ask for help. It saw a little mouse and asked, "Can you help me lift this unusual rock?" The mouse said yes and together they lifted the rock and moved it to a new spot. The crane was very happy and thanked the mouse for its help. From that day on, the crane and the mouse became good friends and helped each other whenever they could.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/31/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-crane.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/31/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-crane.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-31-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-crane.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-30-one-day,-a-little-girl-named-amy-went-to-play-outside.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-30 - One day, a little girl named Amy went to play outside</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.940797+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a little girl named Amy went to play outside. She saw a big, impressive tree with pretty birds. Amy wanted to climb the tree, but she was too small. She felt sad.Amy found a soft cloth near the tree. She had an idea! She would go to her grandpa and ask for help. Maybe he could get her a ladder so she could climb the tree.Grandpa was very nice. He gave Amy a ladder and a big smile. She put the ladder near the tree and climbed up. Now, she could see the birds and feel happy. Amy thanked her grandpa and went home with a big smile.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/30/one-day,-a-little-girl-named-amy-went-to-play-outside.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/30/one-day,-a-little-girl-named-amy-went-to-play-outside.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-30-one-day,-a-little-girl-named-amy-went-to-play-outside.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-30-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-30 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.939945+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play with her toys and her friends. One day, Lily's friend fell down and hurt her hand. Lily wanted to prevent her friend from getting hurt again, so she gave her a band-aid.Lily's friend was happy and they continued playing together. Later, they played a game where they had to count to zero. Lily thought it was funny when she said "zero" instead of "zero". Her friend laughed too.At the end of the day, Lily was happy because she prevented her friend from getting hurt and everyone had fun playing together. She went to bed feeling proud of herself for being a good friend.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/30/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/30/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-30-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-30-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bear-who-lived-in-a-big-forest.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-30 - Once upon a time, there was a bear who lived in a big forest</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.939011+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a bear who lived in a big forest. The bear was very wild and he loved to play with his friends. One day, the bear decided to display his favorite toy to all his friends in the forest. He ran to the river and showed his toy to the fish. The fish thought it was very cool! Then, the bear showed his toy to the birds and the rabbits. They all thought it was amazing! The bear was happy that his friends liked his toy and he felt proud that he could display it. From that day on, the bear loved to show his toys to his friends in the forest.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/30/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bear-who-lived-in-a-big-forest.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/30/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bear-who-lived-in-a-big-forest.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-30-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bear-who-lived-in-a-big-forest.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-29-one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-out-to-play.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-29 - One day, a boy named Tim went out to play</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.938198+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a boy named Tim went out to play. He saw a big puddle of wet water. He thought it was fun to jump in it. As he jumped, he became wet too. The water went everywhere!Tim saw an ugly bug near the puddle. The bug had many legs and big eyes. Tim said, "Hi, Mr. Bug! Do you want to play in the wet puddle with me?" The ugly bug looked at Tim and said, "Yes, I would like to play. I can turn into a pretty bug if I jump in the wet puddle."Tim and the ugly bug both jumped in the wet puddle. They turned into a pretty bug and played together. They had a lot of fun in the puddle. Soon, it was time for Tim to go home. He said goodbye to the ugly bug and went back to his house. Tim had a big smile on his face because he made a new friend.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/29/one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-out-to-play.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/29/one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-out-to-play.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-29-one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-out-to-play.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-29 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.937386+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved ice cream and her mom kept it in the freezer. One day, Lily went to get some ice cream but the freezer was empty. She was very sad.Lily asked her mom, "Where is the ice cream?" Her mom replied, "We finished it all. It's all gone now." Lily was very serious and said, "What are we going to do? I really wanted ice cream."Her mom said, "Don't worry, we can make our own ice cream together." Lily was happy and they made some ice cream. But when they took it out of the freezer, they saw that it had melted. Lily was very upset and said, "Now we can't eat ice cream anymore." Her mom replied, "It's okay, we can try again next time." And they both smiled.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-29 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.936537+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to play outside and explore the world around him. One day, Timmy's mom said, "Let's go for a walk in the park!" Timmy was so excited and said, "Yes, let's go!"As they walked, Timmy saw a big structure made of blocks. He said, "Mommy, look at that big building!" His mom said, "Yes, that's a very kind man who made it." Timmy was curious and asked, "What does kind mean?" His mom explained, "It means he made something for people to use and like."After their walk, Timmy was tired and wanted to sleep. His mom said, "Let's go home and you can sleep in your bed." Timmy went to bed and fell asleep quickly because he was so tired from his adventure in the park.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-kind-bunny-named-benny.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-29 - Once upon a time, there was a kind bunny named Benny</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.935679+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a kind bunny named Benny. Benny loved to hop and play in the forest. One day, while he was hopping along, he saw a little bird sitting on a branch. The bird looked sad.Benny asked, "Why are you sad?"The bird said, "I lost my way home. I don't know where to go."Benny felt compassionate for the little bird. He said, "Don't worry. I can help you find your way home. Just hop on my back and we'll find it together."The bird hopped on Benny's back and they hopped through the forest. After a while, they found the bird's home. The bird was so happy that he started to sing. Benny smiled and said, "I'm glad I could help you."Just then, Benny's zipper on his jacket broke. He didn't know what to do. The little bird said, "Don't worry. I can help you fix your zipper." The bird helped Benny fix his zipper and they both continued to be friends. From that day on,</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-kind-bunny-named-benny.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-kind-bunny-named-benny.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-kind-bunny-named-benny.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-28-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-28 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.934800+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play outside in the sun. One day, her mommy said, "Lily, it's time to go to the park. But you need to put on your sunscreen so you don't get sunburned."Lily replied, "Okay mommy, I will put on my sunscreen." She ran to the park and started playing on the swings. After a while, she got very hot and thirsty. She went to the water fountain and drank some water.Suddenly, a little boy came to her and said, "I like your jewel necklace. It's very pretty." Lily smiled and said, "Thank you! It's my mommy's necklace." The little boy said, "Can I wear it for a little bit?" Lily thought for a moment and said, "Okay, but you have to give it back to me." The little boy wore the necklace for a little while and then gave it back to Lily. They played together for a little while longer and had a lot of fun. When it was time to go</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/28/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/28/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-28-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-28-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bunny-named-ben.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-28 - Once upon a time, there was a little bunny named Ben</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.933949+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little bunny named Ben. Ben loved to eat yummy carrots all day. One day, he found a calendar on the ground. It had pictures of yummy carrots on it. Ben was very happy and showed it to his friend, Tina the turtle.Tina said, "I recommend you share the yummy carrots with others. Sharing is good." Ben thought about it and decided to share the calendar with all his friends.Ben and his friends looked at the calendar together. They saw many yummy carrots pictures. They learned that sharing is caring. From that day on, Ben and his friends always shared their yummy food with each other. They were all happy and played together every day.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/28/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bunny-named-ben.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/28/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bunny-named-ben.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-28-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bunny-named-ben.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-27-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-little-girl-called-poppy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-27 - Once upon a time there was a little girl called Poppy</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.933083+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time there was a little girl called Poppy. She was only three years old, but she had a big dream. She wanted to be a fast runner! So every day, Poppy would run all around the park, practice running as fast as she could.One day, Poppy chose to go to the library. She wanted to read about running races. When she got there, Poppy was so excited. She looked around the library until she found the perfect book. It was full of pictures and words about running fast.Poppy read the book and couldn't wait to try running like the cheetahs in the story. She was determined to become a fast runner. She ran around the library, up and down the stairs, and all the way around the park.But no matter how fast Poppy ran, she couldn't seem to keep up with the other runners. She was tired and sad.But then Poppy remembered something her mum had said: 'When something doesn't go your way, try again!'. So Poppy decided to try again the next day.And sure enough, Poppy ran even faster than before! She felt so proud of herself that she laughed</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/27/once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-little-girl-called-poppy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/27/once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-little-girl-called-poppy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-27-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-little-girl-called-poppy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-27-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-27 - Once upon a time, there was a girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.932210+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a girl named Lily. She loved chocolate more than anything in the world. One day, Lily's friend came over to play. Her friend was very thoughtful and brought some chocolate for Lily to eat. Lily was so happy and said, "Thank you for the chocolate, it looks so yummy!"Lily's friend said, "I have a surprise for you. I brought my favorite toy, a teddy bear. Do you want to play with it?" Lily replied, "Yes, please!" They played with the teddy bear for a while, but then Lily started to feel sick. She said to her friend, "I don't feel good. My tummy hurts." Her friend said, "Maybe you just ate too much chocolate. Let's go lie down and rest."Lily and her friend went to lie down and rest. After a while, Lily felt better and said, "Thank you for being such a thoughtful friend. I feel much better now." Her friend smiled and said, "You're welcome. I'm glad you're feeling better." Lily</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/27/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/27/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-27-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-27-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-lawyer.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-27 - Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a lawyer</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.931249+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a lawyer. He was a bit weird. He liked to give things to people. He gave toys, food, and clothes to people who needed them.One day, the lawyer met a little girl. She was sad because she lost her toy. The lawyer wanted to help her. So, he gave her a new toy. The girl was very happy.The weird lawyer felt good. He liked to give and help others. From that day on, he gave more and more things to people in his town. Everyone loved the weird lawyer. And they all lived happily ever after.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/27/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-lawyer.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/27/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-lawyer.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-27-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-lawyer.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-27-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-house,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-27 - Once upon a time, in a small house, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.930467+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a small house, there was a little boy named Tim. Tim loved to play with his toys and make noise. One day, he was playing with his loud toy drum. He was so happy and having fun. But, he was also being foolish.Tim's mom asked him to be quiet because his baby sister was sleeping. But Tim did not listen. He kept playing his drum and making noise. His baby sister woke up and started to cry. Tim's mom was not happy.Tim's mom told him that he needed to be more quiet. She said, "If you don't stop making noise, I will have to punish you." Tim did not want to be punished, so he decided to play with his toys in a quiet place. He learned that being foolish was not good, and he didn't want to make his baby sister cry again.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/27/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-house,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/27/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-house,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-27-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-house,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-26-one-day,-a-little-boy-named-tim-and-his-dog,-spot,-went-to-the-park.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-26 - One day, a little boy named Tim and his dog, Spot, went to the park</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.929712+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a little boy named Tim and his dog, Spot, went to the park. They loved to play together. Tim would throw a ball and Spot would run to get it. They played and played all day long."Spot, I love playing with you!" said Tim. Spot barked happily and wagged his tail. But then, Tim saw a big tree with a scary face on it. He was afraid. "I don't want to play here, Spot," said Tim. Spot barked and tried to comfort Tim. "Don't be scared, Tim!" Spot barked.Suddenly, the scary face on the tree disappeared! But it was not Tim's face on Spot. It was a friendly squirrel! The squirrel had been playing hide and seek. Tim and Spot laughed. They were not scared anymore. They played with the squirrel and had a lot of fun at the park.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/26/one-day,-a-little-boy-named-tim-and-his-dog,-spot,-went-to-the-park.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/26/one-day,-a-little-boy-named-tim-and-his-dog,-spot,-went-to-the-park.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-26-one-day,-a-little-boy-named-tim-and-his-dog,-spot,-went-to-the-park.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-26-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-26 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.928730+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to help her mom in the garden. One day, Lily's mom asked her to try pulling out the same herb that they were planting. Lily tried her best, but the herb was too strong for her little hands.Suddenly, a big, smelly skunk came by and started to spray them with its smelly spray. Lily's mom quickly grabbed her and ran inside the house. They were both covered in the smelly skunk spray and had to take a bath to get clean.After their bath, Lily's mom told her a story about a girl who tried to pull out a whole herb with a strong breath, but it didn't work and only blew out the skunk's smelly spray. The girl realized that sometimes it's better to wait for help instead of trying to do everything by yourself.Lily learned her lesson and never tried to pull out the wrong herb again. She also learned to be careful around smelly animals.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/26/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/26/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-26-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-25-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-girl-named-lucy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-25 - Once upon a time there was a girl named Lucy</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.928062+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time there was a girl named Lucy. She was very independent and liked to do things on her own. One day, Lucy was playing with her toys, when she started to feel like she had to sneeze. So, she put her hands on her nose and tapped them.Suddenly, her mom appeared. "What are you doing, Lucy?" she asked.Lucy smiled and said, "I was sneezing!"Her mom laughed and said, "That's great, dear! Keep playing."So Lucy went back to her toys, feeling very independent. But she soon forgot all about her sneeze. Later on, she went to the park and was having so much fun!</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/25/once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-girl-named-lucy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/25/once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-girl-named-lucy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-25-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-girl-named-lucy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-25-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-25 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.927337+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to eat grapes, but one day she ate too many and her tummy hurt. Lily said, "Ouch, my tummy hurts!" Her mommy gave her some medicine and told her to rest.While she was resting, Lily heard a loud noise outside. She looked out the window and saw a big bird. The bird was trying to take her grapes! Lily didn't want the bird to take her grapes, so she said, "Stop, bird! Those are my grapes!"The bird didn't listen and kept trying to take the grapes. Lily got upset and said, "Mommy, help! The bird is taking my grapes!" Her mommy went outside and scared the bird away. Lily was happy that her grapes were safe and she could eat them without any more trouble.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/25/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/25/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-25-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-25-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-talk.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-25 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily who loved to talk</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.926683+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily who loved to talk. She talked all day long and never stopped. One day, her mommy took her to a museum. Lily saw lots of pretty things and talked about them.Then, she saw a big painting with lots of colors. She asked her mommy if she could paint like that too. Her mommy said that she could, but Lily had to be patient and practice.Lily practiced every day and became very patient. She sang and talked while she got better. One day, she got a microphone and sang a song in front of everyone at the museum. They all clapped and cheered for her. Lily was so happy that she talked about it all the time.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/25/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-talk.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/25/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-talk.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-25-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-talk.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-25-lily-and-max-were-playing-in-the-garden.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-25 - Lily and Max were playing in the garden</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.925986+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Lily and Max were playing in the garden. They liked to find out which flowers wereoming. Lily saw a big red flower and said, "Look, Max, this one is pretty!" Max saw a yellow flower and said, "Look, Lily, this one is bright!"They ran to their mom, who was sitting on a bench. They asked her, "Mom, what are these flowers?" Mom smiled and said, "These are sunflowers. They bloom in the summer. They are very beautiful, aren't they?" Lily and Max nodded and said, "Yes, they are!"Mom said, "Do you want to see more flowers?" Lily and Max said, "Yes, please!" Mom took them to another part of the garden, where there were more sunflowers. They saw a big yellow sunflower that was taller than Lily and Max. Lily said, "Wow, look at that one! It is so big!" Max said, "It is bigger than you! It is the biggest!"Mom said, "That is a sunflower, Max. They are very rare. They grow the best ones in the whole</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/25/lily-and-max-were-playing-in-the-garden.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/25/lily-and-max-were-playing-in-the-garden.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-25-lily-and-max-were-playing-in-the-garden.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-24-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-24 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.925201+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play outside and explore the world around her. One day, she found a pretty butterfly and followed it into the forest.As she walked deeper into the forest, she met a friendly squirrel who asked her what she was doing. "I'm looking for the spirit of the forest," Lily said with a smile.The squirrel replied, "The spirit of the forest is hidden behind those trees. But be careful, there's a disgusting smell coming from a skunk."Lily nodded and continued on her adventure, excited to find the spirit of the forest. Eventually, she found the skunk and quickly ran away. She was scared but happy to have seen the spirit of the forest.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/24/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/24/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-24-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-24-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-clever-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-24 - Once upon a time, there was a clever boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.924333+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a clever boy named Tim. Tim loved to play with his toy violin. He played it every day and made happy songs.One day, Tim saw a big tree with a bird's nest. He wanted to see the baby birds, so he climbed the tree. But, oh no! He was not careful and he started to fall.Tim held his violin tight and closed his eyes. As he fell, his violin opened up like a big umbrella. Tim landed on the soft grass. The baby birds were safe and happy. Tim was a hero!</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/24/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-clever-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/24/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-clever-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-24-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-clever-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-24-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-24 - Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.923401+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy. He loved to play outside in the park. One day, he found a glove on the ground. It was a big glove, and it looked very strange. Timmy asked his friend, "Can you help me find the owner of this glove? It's unknown whose it is."His friend said, "Sure, let's go ask the people in the park if they lost a glove." They walked around and asked everyone they saw if they lost a glove. But nobody said they lost it.Suddenly, Timmy's friend saw a man walking towards them. He shouted, "Excuse me, sir! Is this your glove?" The man looked at the glove and said, "Yes! That's my glove! Thank you so much for finding it." Timmy and his friend were very happy to help the man. They marched back home, feeling proud of themselves for being kind to someone who lost their glove.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/24/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/24/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-24-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-23-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-powerful-lion-named-leo.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-23 - Once upon a time, there was a powerful lion named Leo</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.922562+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a powerful lion named Leo. Leo had a big, soft sweater. He loved to wear it every day. One day, Leo met a little bunny named Ben. Ben saw the sweater and thought it was nice."Can I borrow your sweater?" asked Ben. Leo said, "Yes, you can borrow my sweater." Ben was very happy. He put on the sweater and it made him feel warm and cozy.Later, they found a big tree with lots of yummy fruit. Leo used his powerful paws to get the fruit. Ben and Leo sat under the tree, eating the fruit together. They became best friends and shared the sweater when they needed it.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/23/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-powerful-lion-named-leo.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/23/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-powerful-lion-named-leo.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-23-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-powerful-lion-named-leo.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-23-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-23 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.921791+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She twisted a balloon into a shape that looked like a flower. She was so happy and showed it to her mom. Her mom said it was beautiful and put it on the fridge.One day, Lily woke up and saw the sun shining bright. She felt happy and wanted to play outside. She ran to the park and saw a boy playing with a shiny red ball. She wanted to play with it too, but the boy didn't want to share. Lily felt sad and went back home.When she got home, she saw her balloon on the table. But something was different. It wasn't peaceful anymore. It was dark and scary. She picked it up and heard a loud noise. Suddenly, the balloon exploded and scared her. She started crying and her mom came to comfort her. From that day on, Lily learned to share her toys and be careful with things that twist and change.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/23/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/23/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-23-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-23-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-yellow-truck-named-max.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-23 - Once upon a time, there was a big yellow truck named Max</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.920972+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a big yellow truck named Max. Max loved to drive on the wide road and show off his shiny paint. One day, Max was driving so fast that he didn't pay attention to the mechanic's red light. The car suddenly broke down and Max got very sad.After a while, a kind man came and helped Max. The man was the driver of a tow truck, and he knew how to fix any car. The tow truck driver said Max needed a new light and Max was excited. The tow truck driver changed Max's light, and Max was happy again.But then, something unexpected happened. The tow truck driver had to go to a store to supply some tools for Max. Max was sad again because he thought he wouldn't be able to drive without the new light. But then, the store owner surprised Max by giving him a special new light that would keep him driving safely. Max was so happy and grateful for the tow truck driver's help. From that day on, Max always made sure to pay attention to the rules of the road.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/23/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-yellow-truck-named-max.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/23/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-yellow-truck-named-max.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-23-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-yellow-truck-named-max.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-23-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-farm.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-23 - Once upon a time, there was a big farm</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.920103+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a big farm. On the farm, there was a little horse named Sam. Sam was not like the other horses. He was sad because he was uncomfortable. His jumping made it hard for him to run and play.One day, Sam's friend, a little bird named Tim, came to visit. Tim saw Sam feeling sad and asked, "Why are you so sad, Sam?" Sam told Tim about his uncomfortable jumping. Tim wanted to help Sam, so he had an idea.Tim told Sam to close his eyes and imagine a big, soft nest. Sam closed his eyes and imagined himself in a cozy nest. When he opened his eyes, he felt his jumping go away. Now, Sam could run and play without any trouble. Sam was so happy, and he and Tim played all day long.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/23/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-farm.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/23/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-farm.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-23-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-farm.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-22 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.918898+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play with her toy cart and push it around the house. One day, Lily's mom asked her to help deliver some cookies to their neighbor, Mrs. Smith.Lily was excited to help and started pulling her cart through the streets. As she walked, she saw a big, scary dog in the distance. She felt scared and wanted to run away, but she knew that she had to deliver the cookies to Mrs. Smith.Lily took a deep breath and kept walking, slowly but surely. When she finally arrived at Mrs. Smith's house, she saw that she had moved away. Lily felt sad and didn't know what to do. But then she remembered the cookies in her cart and offered some to Mrs. Smith. She smiled and thanked Lily for delivering them. From that day on, Lily wasn't as scared of dogs and always carried cookies with her in her cart.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-22 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.918123+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. Timmy was feeling sick, so his mommy took his temperature with a thermometer. The thermometer was a stick that beeped when it was done.Timmy's mommy looked at the thermometer and saw that Timmy had a fever. She gave him some medicine to make him feel better. Timmy drank the medicine and then went to bed.Later that night, Timmy heard a noise outside his window. He got scared and called out to his mommy. She came running and told him not to be afraid, it was just the wind. Timmy felt better and went back to sleep.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-bunny-named-benny.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-22 - Once upon a time, there was a chubby bunny named Benny</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.917365+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a chubby bunny named Benny. Benny loved to play with his favorite toy, a missile. He would spend hours throwing it around and imagining it was flying through the sky.One day, Benny's mom told him it was time for his nap. Benny didn't want to stop playing with his missile, but he knew he must listen to his mom. He put his missile down and closed his eyes.Suddenly, Benny's missile started to blink and shake! Benny opened his eyes and saw that his missile had come to life and was flying around his room! Benny was so surprised and excited that he couldn't stop giggling.From that day on, Benny and his missile became the best of friends. They would play together every day and Benny was always so happy when he was with his trusty friend.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-bunny-named-benny.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-bunny-named-benny.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-bunny-named-benny.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-21 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.916557+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She was very sleepy and wanted to take a nap. She went to her room and lay down on her bed. She closed her eyes and fell asleep.While she was sleeping, her mommy came in and mentioned that they were going to have ice cream for dessert. Lily woke up and got very excited. She loved ice cream!Mommy took Lily to the kitchen and they got some ice cream. It was so yummy! After they finished, Lily went back to her room and fell asleep again. She dreamt about all the fun she had with mommy and the delicious ice cream.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-ant.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-21 - Once upon a time, there was a little ant</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.915726+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little ant. The ant was very scared of all the big things around him. One day, the ant met a friendly butterfly. The butterfly asked the ant why he was so scared. The ant told the butterfly that he was afraid of everything.The butterfly told the ant not to be afraid and that he should try to part ways with things that scared him. The ant listened to the butterfly and decided to be brave. He started to walk around and explore the world.As the ant continued to explore, he noticed that the world wasn't so scary anymore. In fact, he found that he enjoyed looking at all the different flowers and insects that lived there. The moral of the story is that sometimes it's good to part ways from scary things and try new things.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-ant.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-ant.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-ant.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-21 - Once upon a time, there was a chubby little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.914842+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a chubby little girl named Lily. She loved to play outside with her friends. One day, Lily and her friends went for a walk in the park. They saw a big mountain and Lily wanted to climb it.Lily said, "I want to climb that mountain!"Her friends said, "We can't climb it, we're too small."Lily felt sad because she really wanted to climb the mountain. Suddenly, a friendly dog came up to her and said, "I can help you climb the mountain!"Lily was surprised and happy. She followed the dog up the mountain and they reached the top. From there, they could see the whole park. Lily was happy and grateful to the dog for helping her.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-beautiful-horse-named-bella.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-21 - Once upon a time, there was a beautiful horse named Bella</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.914023+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a beautiful horse named Bella. Bella lived in a big field with her friends. They liked to run and play all day.One sunny day, Bella saw a little girl named Lily. Lily was sad. Bella wanted to help. She walked to Lily and whispered, "Why are you sad?"Lily looked at Bella and said, "I lost my ball. Can you help me find it?" Bella nodded her head and they both started to look for the ball. They looked under the trees and behind the bushes. Finally, they found the ball near a big rock.Lily was very happy and hugged Bella. She said, "Thank you, Bella! You are the best horse ever!" They played together all day long and became the best of friends. From that day on, Bella and Lily always played together in the big field.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-beautiful-horse-named-bella.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-beautiful-horse-named-bella.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-beautiful-horse-named-bella.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-one-day,-a-big-dog-and-a-little-cat-were-playing-by-a-tree.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-20 - One day, a big dog and a little cat were playing by a tree</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.913171+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a big dog and a little cat were playing by a tree. The big dog saw a long vine hanging from the tree. He had an idea. He said to the little cat, "Let's swing on the vine like crazy monkeys!"The little cat was scared, but she wanted to try. So, they both held on to the vine and started to swing. They swung back and forth, laughing and having fun. Then, the big dog said, "Let's jump off the vine and see what happens!"The little cat was still scared, but she wanted to be brave like the big dog. So, she jumped off the vine and landed on the soft grass. She was so happy and proud of herself.The big dog and little cat learned that it's okay to be scared, but it's also important to be brave and try new things. They had lots of fun swinging on the vine together, and they knew they could do anything if they tried.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/one-day,-a-big-dog-and-a-little-cat-were-playing-by-a-tree.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/one-day,-a-big-dog-and-a-little-cat-were-playing-by-a-tree.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-one-day,-a-big-dog-and-a-little-cat-were-playing-by-a-tree.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-20 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.912206+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She lived in a big house with her mommy and daddy. One day, Lily heard a loud noise coming from upstairs. She was scared, so she called for her mommy."Mommy, I hear a loud noise upstairs. Can you come and help me?" asked Lily.Her mommy came upstairs and listened. She heard the noise too and said, "Don't worry, sweetie. It's just the wind outside. It's making a loud noise."Lily felt better knowing it was just the wind. She hugged her mommy and said, "Thank you for helping me. You're the best!"</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-gray-cat.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-20 - Once upon a time, there was a gray cat</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.911198+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a gray cat. The cat loved to eat popcorn. One day, the cat went to the kitchen to find some popcorn.The cat found a big bowl of popcorn on the table. The cat was very happy. It started to eat the popcorn very fast. The cat wanted to finish the popcorn before it was all gone.But then, the cat ate too much popcorn. It started to feel sick. The cat ate so much popcorn that it could not move. In the end, the gray cat was very sad and sick because it ate too much popcorn.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-gray-cat.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-gray-cat.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-gray-cat.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-20 - Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.910361+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to play outside and explore the world around him. One day, Timmy's mommy gave him a pair of sunglasses to wear. They were shiny and cool, and Timmy loved them very much.As he was walking around, Timmy saw a big, scary dog. He wanted to run away, but he remembered what his mommy had told him. "If you ever feel scared, just stand still and don't move. The dog won't hurt you if you stay calm."Timmy stood still and the dog walked away. He was so happy that he had listened to his mommy's advice. As he continued to explore, he met a nice lady who asked him about his sunglasses. "These are my new sunglasses," Timmy said proudly. "They make me look cool."The lady smiled and said, "You look awesome, Timmy. I wish I had sunglasses like that." Timmy smiled back and said, "You can borrow them if you want. I'm always happy to share." The lady thanked Timmy and put on</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-one-sunny-day,-a-bird-named-billy-wanted-to-soar-high-in-the-sky.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-19 - One sunny day, a bird named Billy wanted to soar high in the sky</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.909530+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One sunny day, a bird named Billy wanted to soar high in the sky. He flapped his wings and went up, up, up! Billy was so happy to fly and see all the things below him.As he flew, he saw an elderly dog named Daisy. Daisy was sitting on a soft, green lawn. She looked up and saw Billy flying high. "Hello, Billy!" she said. "You are so good at flying!"Billy smiled at Daisy and said, "Thank you, Daisy! I love to soar in the sky. It makes me feel so free!" Daisy wagged her tail and watched Billy fly away. She knew that Billy was happy and healthy, and she was happy just to see him soar.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/one-sunny-day,-a-bird-named-billy-wanted-to-soar-high-in-the-sky.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/one-sunny-day,-a-bird-named-billy-wanted-to-soar-high-in-the-sky.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-one-sunny-day,-a-bird-named-billy-wanted-to-soar-high-in-the-sky.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-19 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.908688+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play with her toys and her favorite toy was a small red ball. One day, Lily's mom asked her to help in the kitchen. Lily was excited to help her mom, so she went to the kitchen.Lily's mom asked her to lift a glass of water from the faucet. Lily tried to lift the glass, but it was too heavy for her. She tried again, but she still couldn't lift it. Suddenly, Lily's red ball bounced into the kitchen and hit the glass. The glass fell and broke into many pieces.Lily was scared and started to cry. Her mom hugged her and told her that accidents happen and it's okay. They cleaned up the mess together and Lily felt better. From that day on, Lily learned to be more careful when she lifted things in the kitchen.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-19 - Once upon a time, there was a girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.907832+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a girl named Lily. She had a large purse that she loved to carry everywhere. One day, Lily went to the park to play with her friends. While playing, she saw a butterfly and tried to catch it. But the butterfly flew away and she couldn't catch it.Lily's friend, Sarah, saw her struggle and said, "I have an idea! Let's make a butterfly net with a stick and a piece of cloth." Lily was happy and they quickly made the net together. They went back to the park and tried using their new net. After a few tries, they finally caught the butterfly. Lily was so happy that she could hardly contain herself. She said, "Thank you, Sarah! You helped me catch the butterfly!"</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-19 - Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.906893+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to ride in his motorcycle. One day, Timmy's mommy told him they were going on a trip. Timmy was so excited! But he had to pack his bags first. Timmy packed his toys and clothes, and even his motorcycle to take with him.When they arrived at their destination, Timmy's mommy told him to unpack his bags. Timmy didn't like unpacking because it was boring. But he did it anyway. As he unpacked, he found a toy that was very attractive. It was a big red truck that he had never seen before. Timmy was so happy to have found it!After they finished unpacking, Timmy got back in his motorcycle and they went for a ride. Timmy was so excited to show off his new truck to everyone. He was happy he remembered to pack it.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-18-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-18 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.906042+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. One day, she went to the park to play with her friend, Timmy. They played on the swings and the slide, and Lily said, "Look, Timmy! We can draw silly faces on the ground!"Timmy thought that was a great idea, so they started drawing silly faces with sticks and stones. Suddenly, they heard a loud noise. It was a group of birds flying overhead.Lily said, "Wow, that bird sounds so pretty!" Timmy agreed and said, "Let's feed them some bread crumbs."So, they ran to get some bread crumbs and threw them on the ground. The birds came down and ate the crumbs happily. Lily and Timmy were so happy to see the birds enjoying their snack. They continued to play and have fun at the park until it was time to go home.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/18/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/18/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-18-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-18-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-with-rocks.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-18 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily who loved to play with rocks</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.905165+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily who loved to play with rocks. She would collect them and build little houses for them. One day, she found a shiny rock that she really liked. She showed it to her friend, Timmy, and said, "Look at my pretty rock!"Timmy looked at the rock and said, "That's a nice rock, but it's not as valuable as your other rocks."Lily didn't understand what he meant, so she asked, "What do you mean?"Timmy replied, "It means someone may say your rock is worth a lot of money."Lily felt sad and didn't want her rock to be worth a lot of money. She decided to bury it in a deep hole so no one could take it. But when she finished burying it, she realized she had lost something very important in the screw she was carrying. She became very upset and cried. Her friends tried to help her find it, but it was impossible. Lily never found her shiny rock again.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/18/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-with-rocks.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/18/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-with-rocks.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-18-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-with-rocks.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-18-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-18 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.904259+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim. Tim loved to eat yummy food. One day, his mom made him a big plate of yummy food. It had pink fruits, green veggies, and orange juice. Tim was so happy to see all the yummy food on his plate.But then, Tim's little sister, Sue, came into the room. Sue was very hungry too. She tried to take Tim's plate away from him. Tim did not want to lose his yummy food, so he held onto the plate very tight.Sue pulled harder and harder, but Tim was strong. Finally, Sue let go of the plate and it fell to the floor. The plate broke into many pieces. Tim was sad that his yummy food was gone. But his mom came into the room with a new plate of yummy food for him. Tim was happy again, and he shared his new plate with Sue. They both enjoyed the yummy food together.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/18/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/18/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-18-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-wealthy-man-who-had-a-big-car.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-17 - Once upon a time, there was a wealthy man who had a big car</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.903168+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a wealthy man who had a big car. He loved his car very much. One day, he went for a ride in his car. He saw a little boy playing with a toy car. The little boy looked sad.The wealthy man stopped his car and asked the little boy, "Why are you sad? Do you want to play with my car?" The little boy looked at the car and smiled. "Yes, please! I love cars too," he said. The wealthy man was happy to share his car with the little boy.As they played, the wealthy man stumble on a big rock. His car made a loud noise. Suddenly, the car started to fly in the air! The little boy laughed and clapped his hands. The wealthy man and the little boy flew around in the sky, having the best time ever. The car was no longer just a toy, but a magical flying car!</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-wealthy-man-who-had-a-big-car.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-wealthy-man-who-had-a-big-car.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-wealthy-man-who-had-a-big-car.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-17 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.902301+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She lived in a big house with her mommy and daddy. One day, Lily went outside to play in the garden. She saw a big tree and wondered what was on top of it. She asked her mommy, "Can you help me get the top of the tree?" Her mommy said, "Sure, I can help you."Her mommy picked her up and lifted her high over the tree. Lily looked up and saw a beautiful bird's nest. She said, "Wow, look at the bird's nest!" Her mommy said, "Yes, it's very pretty." Lily asked, "Can we take a closer look?" Her mommy said, "No, we shouldn't touch it. We don't want to hurt the birds."Lily was sad she couldn't see the bird's nest up close, but she was happy her mommy helped her. They went back inside the house and had some cookies. Lily said, "Today was a good day. I wonder what other things I can see." Her mommy said, "We can always find things we wonder</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-17 - Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a little girl named Sue</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.901504+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a little girl named Sue. She was a fearful girl who was scared of many things. One day, Sue was walking with her mom when they saw a big, black door. Sue wanted to know what was behind the door, but she was too scared to open it.Sue's mom said, "Let's go see what's behind the door." Sue was scared, but she held her mom's hand and they walked closer to the door. Sue's mom gave her a little slap on the hand and said, "You can do it!"Sue took a deep breath and opened the door. To her surprise, there was a big, colorful room filled with toys and games! Sue was so happy and not fearful anymore. She played with the toys and had lots of fun. The black door had given her a beautiful place to play and be brave. From that day on, Sue was a brave little girl and was not scared of the black door anymore.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-normal-little-town,-there-was-a-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-17 - Once upon a time, in a normal little town, there was a boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.900507+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a normal little town, there was a boy named Tim. Tim loved to poke things with his finger. One day, he went to the park with his mom. At the park, he saw a big tree with a hole in it. Tim thought it was a secret place, but he didn't know what was inside."Mom, what's in the tree hole?" Tim asked. His mom didn't know, so she said, "I don't know, Tim. Maybe we can find out later. But first, let's play on the swings." Tim played on the swings, but he still wanted to know what was in the tree hole.Later, when it was time to go home, Tim and his mom walked to the tree hole. Tim poked the hole with his finger. Suddenly, a small squirrel jumped out! Tim was so surprised. The squirrel looked at Tim and said, "Thank you for poking the hole. I was stuck inside. I've been waiting for someone to help me get out." Tim and his mom smiled, happy that they had solved the secret of the squirrel.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-normal-little-town,-there-was-a-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-normal-little-town,-there-was-a-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-normal-little-town,-there-was-a-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-16 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.899694+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to eat fruit, especially apples, bananas, and oranges. One day, her mom took her to the store to buy some fruit. Lily was very excited and asked her mom if they could buy some apples or bananas. Her mom said yes, and they went inside the store.Lily saw a man who was very successful at selling fruit. He had many different fruits like oranges, grapes, and strawberries. Lily looked at the fruits and said, "Wow, these are all different kinds of fruit, but I want to choose some apples and bananas." Her mom smiled and said, "Okay, let's get some apples and bananas."Lily was very happy with her choice of fruit. She said to her mom, "I love fruit! Can we eat them now?" Her mom said, "Yes, let's go home and have some fruit together." Lily smiled and said, "Yay, fruit is my favorite!"</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-16 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.898723+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to play outside in the grass and pick flowers. One day, he saw a little fairy sitting on a flower."Hello, fairy!" said Timmy."Hello, little boy," said the fairy. "I'm here to help you.""How can you help me?" asked Timmy."I can make you wealthy," said the fairy. "But you must promise to share your flowers with others."Timmy agreed and the fairy sprinkled some dust on his flowers. Suddenly, Timmy's flowers grew bigger and bigger until he had as many as a car!But then, something unexpected happened. A big gust of wind blew all of Timmy's flowers away. Timmy was sad, but the fairy said, "Don't worry, little boy. I'll bring you more flowers tomorrow." And with a wave of her wand, Timmy's flowers grew even bigger and more beautiful than before. Timmy was very happy and thanked the fairy for her help.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-sue.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-16 - Once upon a time, there was a girl named Sue</title><updated>2023-09-24T11:26:10.897815+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a girl named Sue. Sue had a long brush. She loved to count with her brush. One day, she went outside to play.Sue saw a big tree. She wanted to count its leaves. She started counting, "One, two, three..." But then, a cat jumped out of the tree! Sue was very surprised.The cat said, "Thank you for counting my leaves. I am a magic cat!" Sue was happy to help. The magic cat gave Sue a wish. Sue wished for more toys to play with. They played together all day and became best friends.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-sue.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-sue.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-sue.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry></feed>