<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime</id><title>AI Daily Short Story</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.175455+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime" rel="self"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><logo>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/ai_generated_stories.png</logo><subtitle>A daily pod cast of an AI generated short story</subtitle><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-22 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.256016+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play with her toy cart and push it around the house. One day, Lily's mom asked her to help deliver some cookies to their neighbor, Mrs. Smith.Lily was excited to help and started pulling her cart through the streets. As she walked, she saw a big, scary dog in the distance. She felt scared and wanted to run away, but she knew that she had to deliver the cookies to Mrs. Smith.Lily took a deep breath and kept walking, slowly but surely. When she finally arrived at Mrs. Smith's house, she saw that she had moved away. Lily felt sad and didn't know what to do. But then she remembered the cookies in her cart and offered some to Mrs. Smith. She smiled and thanked Lily for delivering them. From that day on, Lily wasn't as scared of dogs and always carried cookies with her in her cart.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-22 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.255160+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to play outside, but he was afraid of the dark. One night, Timmy was playing with his friend Billy when they saw a glowing light in the distance."Wow, what is that?" Timmy asked."I don't know, let's go check it out!" Billy replied.As they got closer, they saw that the glowing thing was coming from a big, fierce dragon."Oh no, it's a dragon!" Timmy cried."Don't worry, I have a knife," Billy said, pulling out a small knife from his pocket.Billy bravely approached the dragon and cut it in half with his knife. The dragon roared in anger, but Billy explained that he just wanted to make friends.The dragon was surprised by the brave gesture and decided to be friends with Timmy and Billy. From that day on, they played together every night, and the dragon would always glow with joy whenever they saw it.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-21 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.254254+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She was very sleepy and wanted to take a nap. She went to her room and lay down on her bed. She closed her eyes and fell asleep.While she was sleeping, her mommy came in and mentioned that they were going to have ice cream for dessert. Lily woke up and got very excited. She loved ice cream!Mommy took Lily to the kitchen and they got some ice cream. It was so yummy! After they finished, Lily went back to her room and fell asleep again. She dreamt about all the fun she had with mommy and the delicious ice cream.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-ant.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-21 - Once upon a time, there was a little ant</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.253344+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little ant. The ant was very scared of all the big things around him. One day, the ant met a friendly butterfly. The butterfly asked the ant why he was so scared. The ant told the butterfly that he was afraid of everything.The butterfly told the ant not to be afraid and that he should try to part ways with things that scared him. The ant listened to the butterfly and decided to be brave. He started to walk around and explore the world.As the ant continued to explore, he noticed that the world wasn't so scary anymore. In fact, he found that he enjoyed looking at all the different flowers and insects that lived there. The moral of the story is that sometimes it's good to part ways from scary things and try new things.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-ant.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-ant.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-ant.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-21 - Once upon a time, there was a chubby little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.252517+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a chubby little girl named Lily. She loved to play outside with her friends. One day, Lily and her friends went for a walk in the park. They saw a big mountain and Lily wanted to climb it.Lily said, "I want to climb that mountain!"Her friends said, "We can't climb it, we're too small."Lily felt sad because she really wanted to climb the mountain. Suddenly, a friendly dog came up to her and said, "I can help you climb the mountain!"Lily was surprised and happy. She followed the dog up the mountain and they reached the top. From there, they could see the whole park. Lily was happy and grateful to the dog for helping her.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-beautiful-horse-named-bella.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-21 - Once upon a time, there was a beautiful horse named Bella</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.251623+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a beautiful horse named Bella. Bella lived in a big field with her friends. They liked to run and play all day.One sunny day, Bella saw a little girl named Lily. Lily was sad. Bella wanted to help. She walked to Lily and whispered, "Why are you sad?"Lily looked at Bella and said, "I lost my ball. Can you help me find it?" Bella nodded her head and they both started to look for the ball. They looked under the trees and behind the bushes. Finally, they found the ball near a big rock.Lily was very happy and hugged Bella. She said, "Thank you, Bella! You are the best horse ever!" They played together all day long and became the best of friends. From that day on, Bella and Lily always played together in the big field.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-beautiful-horse-named-bella.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-beautiful-horse-named-bella.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-beautiful-horse-named-bella.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-one-day,-a-big-dog-and-a-little-cat-were-playing-by-a-tree.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-20 - One day, a big dog and a little cat were playing by a tree</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.250731+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a big dog and a little cat were playing by a tree. The big dog saw a long vine hanging from the tree. He had an idea. He said to the little cat, "Let's swing on the vine like crazy monkeys!"The little cat was scared, but she wanted to try. So, they both held on to the vine and started to swing. They swung back and forth, laughing and having fun. Then, the big dog said, "Let's jump off the vine and see what happens!"The little cat was still scared, but she wanted to be brave like the big dog. So, she jumped off the vine and landed on the soft grass. She was so happy and proud of herself.The big dog and little cat learned that it's okay to be scared, but it's also important to be brave and try new things. They had lots of fun swinging on the vine together, and they knew they could do anything if they tried.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/one-day,-a-big-dog-and-a-little-cat-were-playing-by-a-tree.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/one-day,-a-big-dog-and-a-little-cat-were-playing-by-a-tree.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-one-day,-a-big-dog-and-a-little-cat-were-playing-by-a-tree.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-20 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.249880+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She lived in a big house with her mommy and daddy. One day, Lily heard a loud noise coming from upstairs. She was scared, so she called for her mommy."Mommy, I hear a loud noise upstairs. Can you come and help me?" asked Lily.Her mommy came upstairs and listened. She heard the noise too and said, "Don't worry, sweetie. It's just the wind outside. It's making a loud noise."Lily felt better knowing it was just the wind. She hugged her mommy and said, "Thank you for helping me. You're the best!"</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-gray-cat.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-20 - Once upon a time, there was a gray cat</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.249024+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a gray cat. The cat loved to eat popcorn. One day, the cat went to the kitchen to find some popcorn.The cat found a big bowl of popcorn on the table. The cat was very happy. It started to eat the popcorn very fast. The cat wanted to finish the popcorn before it was all gone.But then, the cat ate too much popcorn. It started to feel sick. The cat ate so much popcorn that it could not move. In the end, the gray cat was very sad and sick because it ate too much popcorn.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-gray-cat.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-gray-cat.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-gray-cat.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-20 - Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.248157+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to play outside and explore the world around him. One day, Timmy's mommy gave him a pair of sunglasses to wear. They were shiny and cool, and Timmy loved them very much.As he was walking around, Timmy saw a big, scary dog. He wanted to run away, but he remembered what his mommy had told him. "If you ever feel scared, just stand still and don't move. The dog won't hurt you if you stay calm."Timmy stood still and the dog walked away. He was so happy that he had listened to his mommy's advice. As he continued to explore, he met a nice lady who asked him about his sunglasses. "These are my new sunglasses," Timmy said proudly. "They make me look cool."The lady smiled and said, "You look awesome, Timmy. I wish I had sunglasses like that." Timmy smiled back and said, "You can borrow them if you want. I'm always happy to share." The lady thanked Timmy and put on</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-one-sunny-day,-a-bird-named-billy-wanted-to-soar-high-in-the-sky.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-19 - One sunny day, a bird named Billy wanted to soar high in the sky</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.247484+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One sunny day, a bird named Billy wanted to soar high in the sky. He flapped his wings and went up, up, up! Billy was so happy to fly and see all the things below him.As he flew, he saw an elderly dog named Daisy. Daisy was sitting on a soft, green lawn. She looked up and saw Billy flying high. "Hello, Billy!" she said. "You are so good at flying!"Billy smiled at Daisy and said, "Thank you, Daisy! I love to soar in the sky. It makes me feel so free!" Daisy wagged her tail and watched Billy fly away. She knew that Billy was happy and healthy, and she was happy just to see him soar.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/one-sunny-day,-a-bird-named-billy-wanted-to-soar-high-in-the-sky.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/one-sunny-day,-a-bird-named-billy-wanted-to-soar-high-in-the-sky.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-one-sunny-day,-a-bird-named-billy-wanted-to-soar-high-in-the-sky.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-19 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.246691+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play with her toys and her favorite toy was a small red ball. One day, Lily's mom asked her to help in the kitchen. Lily was excited to help her mom, so she went to the kitchen.Lily's mom asked her to lift a glass of water from the faucet. Lily tried to lift the glass, but it was too heavy for her. She tried again, but she still couldn't lift it. Suddenly, Lily's red ball bounced into the kitchen and hit the glass. The glass fell and broke into many pieces.Lily was scared and started to cry. Her mom hugged her and told her that accidents happen and it's okay. They cleaned up the mess together and Lily felt better. From that day on, Lily learned to be more careful when she lifted things in the kitchen.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-19 - Once upon a time, there was a girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.245990+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a girl named Lily. She had a large purse that she loved to carry everywhere. One day, Lily went to the park to play with her friends. While playing, she saw a butterfly and tried to catch it. But the butterfly flew away and she couldn't catch it.Lily's friend, Sarah, saw her struggle and said, "I have an idea! Let's make a butterfly net with a stick and a piece of cloth." Lily was happy and they quickly made the net together. They went back to the park and tried using their new net. After a few tries, they finally caught the butterfly. Lily was so happy that she could hardly contain herself. She said, "Thank you, Sarah! You helped me catch the butterfly!"</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-19 - Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.245130+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to ride in his motorcycle. One day, Timmy's mommy told him they were going on a trip. Timmy was so excited! But he had to pack his bags first. Timmy packed his toys and clothes, and even his motorcycle to take with him.When they arrived at their destination, Timmy's mommy told him to unpack his bags. Timmy didn't like unpacking because it was boring. But he did it anyway. As he unpacked, he found a toy that was very attractive. It was a big red truck that he had never seen before. Timmy was so happy to have found it!After they finished unpacking, Timmy got back in his motorcycle and they went for a ride. Timmy was so excited to show off his new truck to everyone. He was happy he remembered to pack it.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-18-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-18 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.244359+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. One day, she went to the park to play with her friend, Timmy. They played on the swings and the slide, and Lily said, "Look, Timmy! We can draw silly faces on the ground!"Timmy thought that was a great idea, so they started drawing silly faces with sticks and stones. Suddenly, they heard a loud noise. It was a group of birds flying overhead.Lily said, "Wow, that bird sounds so pretty!" Timmy agreed and said, "Let's feed them some bread crumbs."So, they ran to get some bread crumbs and threw them on the ground. The birds came down and ate the crumbs happily. Lily and Timmy were so happy to see the birds enjoying their snack. They continued to play and have fun at the park until it was time to go home.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/18/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/18/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-18-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-18-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-with-rocks.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-18 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily who loved to play with rocks</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.243545+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily who loved to play with rocks. She would collect them and build little houses for them. One day, she found a shiny rock that she really liked. She showed it to her friend, Timmy, and said, "Look at my pretty rock!"Timmy looked at the rock and said, "That's a nice rock, but it's not as valuable as your other rocks."Lily didn't understand what he meant, so she asked, "What do you mean?"Timmy replied, "It means someone may say your rock is worth a lot of money."Lily felt sad and didn't want her rock to be worth a lot of money. She decided to bury it in a deep hole so no one could take it. But when she finished burying it, she realized she had lost something very important in the screw she was carrying. She became very upset and cried. Her friends tried to help her find it, but it was impossible. Lily never found her shiny rock again.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/18/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-with-rocks.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/18/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-with-rocks.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-18-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-with-rocks.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-18-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-18 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.242666+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim. Tim loved to eat yummy food. One day, his mom made him a big plate of yummy food. It had pink fruits, green veggies, and orange juice. Tim was so happy to see all the yummy food on his plate.But then, Tim's little sister, Sue, came into the room. Sue was very hungry too. She tried to take Tim's plate away from him. Tim did not want to lose his yummy food, so he held onto the plate very tight.Sue pulled harder and harder, but Tim was strong. Finally, Sue let go of the plate and it fell to the floor. The plate broke into many pieces. Tim was sad that his yummy food was gone. But his mom came into the room with a new plate of yummy food for him. Tim was happy again, and he shared his new plate with Sue. They both enjoyed the yummy food together.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/18/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/18/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-18-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-wealthy-man-who-had-a-big-car.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-17 - Once upon a time, there was a wealthy man who had a big car</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.241848+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a wealthy man who had a big car. He loved his car very much. One day, he went for a ride in his car. He saw a little boy playing with a toy car. The little boy looked sad.The wealthy man stopped his car and asked the little boy, "Why are you sad? Do you want to play with my car?" The little boy looked at the car and smiled. "Yes, please! I love cars too," he said. The wealthy man was happy to share his car with the little boy.As they played, the wealthy man stumble on a big rock. His car made a loud noise. Suddenly, the car started to fly in the air! The little boy laughed and clapped his hands. The wealthy man and the little boy flew around in the sky, having the best time ever. The car was no longer just a toy, but a magical flying car!</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-wealthy-man-who-had-a-big-car.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-wealthy-man-who-had-a-big-car.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-wealthy-man-who-had-a-big-car.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-17 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.241044+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She lived in a big house with her mommy and daddy. One day, Lily went outside to play in the garden. She saw a big tree and wondered what was on top of it. She asked her mommy, "Can you help me get the top of the tree?" Her mommy said, "Sure, I can help you."Her mommy picked her up and lifted her high over the tree. Lily looked up and saw a beautiful bird's nest. She said, "Wow, look at the bird's nest!" Her mommy said, "Yes, it's very pretty." Lily asked, "Can we take a closer look?" Her mommy said, "No, we shouldn't touch it. We don't want to hurt the birds."Lily was sad she couldn't see the bird's nest up close, but she was happy her mommy helped her. They went back inside the house and had some cookies. Lily said, "Today was a good day. I wonder what other things I can see." Her mommy said, "We can always find things we wonder</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-17 - Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a little girl named Sue</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.240216+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a little girl named Sue. She was a fearful girl who was scared of many things. One day, Sue was walking with her mom when they saw a big, black door. Sue wanted to know what was behind the door, but she was too scared to open it.Sue's mom said, "Let's go see what's behind the door." Sue was scared, but she held her mom's hand and they walked closer to the door. Sue's mom gave her a little slap on the hand and said, "You can do it!"Sue took a deep breath and opened the door. To her surprise, there was a big, colorful room filled with toys and games! Sue was so happy and not fearful anymore. She played with the toys and had lots of fun. The black door had given her a beautiful place to play and be brave. From that day on, Sue was a brave little girl and was not scared of the black door anymore.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-normal-little-town,-there-was-a-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-17 - Once upon a time, in a normal little town, there was a boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.239398+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a normal little town, there was a boy named Tim. Tim loved to poke things with his finger. One day, he went to the park with his mom. At the park, he saw a big tree with a hole in it. Tim thought it was a secret place, but he didn't know what was inside."Mom, what's in the tree hole?" Tim asked. His mom didn't know, so she said, "I don't know, Tim. Maybe we can find out later. But first, let's play on the swings." Tim played on the swings, but he still wanted to know what was in the tree hole.Later, when it was time to go home, Tim and his mom walked to the tree hole. Tim poked the hole with his finger. Suddenly, a small squirrel jumped out! Tim was so surprised. The squirrel looked at Tim and said, "Thank you for poking the hole. I was stuck inside. I've been waiting for someone to help me get out." Tim and his mom smiled, happy that they had solved the secret of the squirrel.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-normal-little-town,-there-was-a-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-normal-little-town,-there-was-a-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-normal-little-town,-there-was-a-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-16 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.238455+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to eat fruit, especially apples, bananas, and oranges. One day, her mom took her to the store to buy some fruit. Lily was very excited and asked her mom if they could buy some apples or bananas. Her mom said yes, and they went inside the store.Lily saw a man who was very successful at selling fruit. He had many different fruits like oranges, grapes, and strawberries. Lily looked at the fruits and said, "Wow, these are all different kinds of fruit, but I want to choose some apples and bananas." Her mom smiled and said, "Okay, let's get some apples and bananas."Lily was very happy with her choice of fruit. She said to her mom, "I love fruit! Can we eat them now?" Her mom said, "Yes, let's go home and have some fruit together." Lily smiled and said, "Yay, fruit is my favorite!"</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-16 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.237695+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to play outside in the grass and pick flowers. One day, he saw a little fairy sitting on a flower."Hello, fairy!" said Timmy."Hello, little boy," said the fairy. "I'm here to help you.""How can you help me?" asked Timmy."I can make you wealthy," said the fairy. "But you must promise to share your flowers with others."Timmy agreed and the fairy sprinkled some dust on his flowers. Suddenly, Timmy's flowers grew bigger and bigger until he had as many as a car!But then, something unexpected happened. A big gust of wind blew all of Timmy's flowers away. Timmy was sad, but the fairy said, "Don't worry, little boy. I'll bring you more flowers tomorrow." And with a wave of her wand, Timmy's flowers grew even bigger and more beautiful than before. Timmy was very happy and thanked the fairy for her help.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-sue.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-16 - Once upon a time, there was a girl named Sue</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.236749+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a girl named Sue. Sue had a long brush. She loved to count with her brush. One day, she went outside to play.Sue saw a big tree. She wanted to count its leaves. She started counting, "One, two, three..." But then, a cat jumped out of the tree! Sue was very surprised.The cat said, "Thank you for counting my leaves. I am a magic cat!" Sue was happy to help. The magic cat gave Sue a wish. Sue wished for more toys to play with. They played together all day and became best friends.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-sue.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-sue.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-sue.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-15-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-man-who-lived-in-a-big-house.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-15 - Once upon a time, there was a man who lived in a big house</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.235736+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a man who lived in a big house. He loved to play with his dog and run around in the yard. One day, he found a puzzle on the ground. It was very hard, but he was determined to solve it.He tried and tried, but he couldn't figure out how to put the pieces together. He felt frustrated and angry with himself. He decided to rest and think about it. While he was resting, the dog came over and started playing with the puzzle pieces.The man watched as the dog solved the puzzle and put the pieces together. He was so happy and proud of his dog. But then, the dog accidentally knocked over the puzzle and it broke into many pieces. The man was devastated and cried.He realized that sometimes things don't go the way we want them to. He hugged his dog and thanked him for trying to help. Even though he was sad, he knew that he still had his best friend.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/15/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-man-who-lived-in-a-big-house.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/15/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-man-who-lived-in-a-big-house.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-15-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-man-who-lived-in-a-big-house.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-15-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-15 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.234867+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play outside in the park with her friends. One day, they went to play on the swings. Lily's friend, Sarah, was pushing her on the swing. Lily thought the swing was amazing and swung higher and higher.Suddenly, Lily saw a shiny red berry on the ground. She picked it up and showed it to Sarah. "Look, Sarah! I found a berry!" Lily exclaimed. Sarah looked at the berry and said, "That berry looks yummy. Can I have a bite?"Lily thought for a moment and then said, "Okay, but be careful. Don't chew on the berry too hard." Sarah took a small bite and said, "Mmm, this berry is delicious! Thank you, Lily!" They both smiled and continued to swing and play in the park.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/15/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/15/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-15-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-15-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-kind-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-15 - Once upon a time, there was a kind little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.234095+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a kind little girl named Lily. She lived in a small village with her mom and dad. One day, Lily went for a walk in the forest. She saw a big log on the ground and decided to climb on it.Suddenly, she heard a voice. "Hello there!" said a little mouse. "What are you doing here?""I'm just exploring," said Lily. "What are you doing?""I'm studying," said the mouse. "I'm learning about the forest and all the animals that live here."Lily was amazed. She had never seen a mouse study before. "That's so cool!" she said. "Can I study too?"The mouse smiled. "Of course you can! We can study together and learn about the forest and all the creatures that live here." And so, Lily and the mouse spent the rest of the day studying and having fun.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/15/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-kind-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/15/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-kind-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-15-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-kind-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-15-lily-was-very-excited.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-15 - Lily was very excited</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.233231+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Lily was very excited. Today was her birthday and she was going to have a party with her friends. She helped her mom make a cake and blow up balloons. She put on her pink dress and her shiny shoes.Soon, the doorbell rang and Lily ran to open it. She saw her friends waving and smiling. They gave her hugs and said, "Happy birthday, Lily!" Lily thanked them and invited them in.They went to the living room, where there was a big table with a lot of plates and cups. On each plate, there was a cup of juice, a cookie, a piece of cake, and an empty glass. Lily's mom said, "Who wants some juice?"Lily's friend Ben said, "I do!" He ran to the table and grabbed a cup. He drank some juice and smiled. He said, "Thank you, Lily! You are a good friend."Lily smiled too. She said, "You are welcome, Ben! You are a good friend too!" Then she picked up her last cup and said, "I have some</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/15/lily-was-very-excited.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/15/lily-was-very-excited.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-15-lily-was-very-excited.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-14-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-14 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.232373+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play outside with her friends. One day, she saw a shooting star in the sky and shouted, "Wow, look at the star! It's so pretty!"Her friend Timmy said, "I want to catch the star and keep it forever." But Lily said, "No, we can't catch the star, it's too far away."Suddenly, a friendly bird flew down and said, "I can help you catch the star, but we need to decorate my nest first." So, Lily and Timmy helped the bird decorate its nest with pretty flowers and shiny stars. The bird was so happy that it gave them a ride on its back to catch the star. They reached the star and brought it back to the bird's nest. The bird was so grateful that it gave them a ride back home. From that day on, Lily and Timmy always looked up at the stars and remembered their friendly bird friend.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/14/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/14/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-14-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-14-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-14 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.231588+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. He loved playing with his toy cars and trucks. One day, he found a big box in his backyard. He was curious and wondered what was inside.Timmy asked his mom, "What's in the box?" His mom replied, "I don't know, let's open it and find out!" They opened the box and found a shiny steel chain. Timmy thought it looked cool and wanted to touch it. But suddenly, the chain started to shake and move all by itself!Timmy and his mom were surprised and scared. They didn't know what to do. The chain turned into a big steel robot! The robot looked grumpy and didn't say anything. But then, the robot started to move and dance. Timmy and his mom were amazed and started to laugh. The robot became their new friend and they played together every day.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/14/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/14/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-14-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-13-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-13 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.230603+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim. He loved to play outside in the sun. One day, he found a long strip of paper on the ground. It had a big, red heart on it. Tim wanted to help, so he decided to fold the paper.Tim was very careful when he folded the paper. He did not want to rip it or make it dirty. He folded the paper one time, then twice, and then one more time at a time. The paper became flat and neat. Tim felt happy that he could make something nice with the paper.Tim showed the folded strip to his mom. She was very proud of him for being careful and kind. She hung the strip on the wall for everyone to see. Tim learned that being careful and kind made him feel good. And from that day on, he always tried to help others and be careful with the things he found.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/13/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/13/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-13-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-13-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-busy-bee-named-benny.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-13 - Once upon a time, there was a busy bee named Benny</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.229784+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a busy bee named Benny. Benny loved to fly around and collect nectar from flowers. One day, Benny saw a bird perched on a tree branch. Benny wanted to say hello, so he flew closer.Suddenly, the bird flew towards Benny and knocked him off the branch! Benny dropped his honeycomb and it spilled all over the ground. Benny was sad because he worked hard to collect his honey. But then, the bird did something unexpected. He flew down and started to help Benny pick up the honeycomb.After they finished, the bird gave Benny a journal to write in. Benny was surprised and happy. He never expected a bird to be so kind. From that day on, Benny and the bird became good friends and they always helped each other out.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/13/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-busy-bee-named-benny.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/13/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-busy-bee-named-benny.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-13-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-busy-bee-named-benny.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-13-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-mountain.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-13 - Once upon a time, there was a big mountain</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.228934+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a big mountain. On the mountain, there was a small house. In the house, lived a boy named Tim and his mom. They were very happy. One day, Tim saw a ball in the sky. It was the sun. The sun would rise every day."Mom, look!" Tim said. "The sun is rising! It is so pretty!" His mom looked at the sky and smiled. "Yes, Tim. The sun is rising. It is a good day for a walk."Tim and his mom went for a walk on the mountain. They saw many trees, flowers, and animals. They saw a big, spicy-smelling flower. Tim picked it up and smelled it. "Mom, it smells spicy!" he said. His mom laughed and said, "That's a special flower, Tim. It will make our walk more fun!"They walked and walked, and the sun kept rising. Tim and his mom had a great day on the mountain. They saw many new things and had lots of fun. When they went back home, they put the spicy flower in their garden. It made their days even more special.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/13/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-mountain.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/13/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-mountain.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-13-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-mountain.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-13-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-house,-there-lived-a-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-13 - Once upon a time, in a small house, there lived a boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.228078+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a small house, there lived a boy named Tim. Tim had an amazing toy. It was a red car. He loved to play with his car all day.One day, Tim saw a big TV in the living room. He thought it would be fun to make his car go fast on the TV. He pushed the car very hard, but it did not move. Tim tried again and again, but the car still would not go fast on the TV.Tim's mom saw him trying hard and said, "Tim, pushing the car on the TV is not nice. It might break something." Tim did not listen to his mom. He pushed the car harder, and then, the car hit the TV. The TV fell down and broke. Tim was very sad.Mom said, "I told you not to push the car on the TV. Now the TV is broken, and we cannot watch our favorite shows." Tim knew he should have listened to his mom. He felt bad for not listening. The day ended sadly because Tim did not listen to his mom.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/13/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-house,-there-lived-a-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/13/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-house,-there-lived-a-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-13-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-house,-there-lived-a-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-12-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-12 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.227143+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play outside in her backyard. One day, she saw a big, tall tree. It was leaning to one side and looked like it might fall down.Lily was curious about the tree, so she went closer to take a look. Suddenly, she heard a noise coming from the tree. It sounded like a little bird chirping!Lily was so excited to see the bird, but she didn't know that it was sick. She was ignorant of how the bird was feeling. She wanted to help the bird, so she called her mommy and they took the bird to the vet.The vet made the bird feel better and Lily learned that sometimes we need to ask questions and not just do whatever we want. She also learned that trees need to be careful and lean to one side, like the tree did. From that day on, Lily made sure to always take care of the trees and animals in her backyard.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/12/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/12/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-12-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-12-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-12 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.226278+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. Timmy had a toy train with a black engine. He loved playing with it every day. One day, Timmy went outside to play with his train, but he couldn't find it. He looked everywhere, but it was nowhere to be found.Timmy asked his mom, "Mommy, where is my train? I can't find it." His mom replied, "Did you check your toy box?" Timmy looked in his toy box and found his train. He was so happy and said, "Mommy, I found my train! It's black and has a black engine."His mom said, "That's great, Timmy. I'm glad you found it. Now you can play with it all day long." Timmy was so happy and played with his train until it was time for dinner. From that day on, Timmy made sure to put his train back in its box so he wouldn't lose it again.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/12/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/12/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-12-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-12-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-thick-tree.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-12 - Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a thick tree</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.225461+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a thick tree. The tree had big, green leaves. A little boy named Tim loved to play around the tree.One day, Tim found a big shield under the tree. He picked it up and saw a girl named Sue. Sue was sad because her toy box was empty. Tim wanted to help Sue feel happy again.Tim said, "Let's fill your toy box with toys!" Tim and Sue put many toys in the box. They played together all day. The thick tree and the big shield made them very happy.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/12/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-thick-tree.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/12/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-thick-tree.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-12-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-thick-tree.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-11-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-11 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.224634+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play with her toys and talk to her friends. One day, she went to the kitchen to get some water and saw her mommy cooking. "What are you making, mommy?" she asked. "I'm making soup, Lily. It's ready to eat," her mommy replied.Lily went back to her room to play, but she heard a knock on the door. It was her friend, Tommy. "Can I come in and play with you, Lily?" Tommy asked. "Sure!" Lily said happily. They played with their toys and talked about what they wanted to do when they grew up.Suddenly, they heard Lily's mommy call them for lunch. "Come on, kids! The soup is ready!" she said. They ran to the kitchen and saw the delicious soup on the table. "Yummy!" they both said. They ate the soup and talked about their plans for the world to come. It was a fun day for Lily and Tommy.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/11/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/11/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-11-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-11-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-big-forest,-there-was-a-little-mushroom.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-11 - Once upon a time, in a big forest, there was a little mushroom</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.223752+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a big forest, there was a little mushroom. The mushroom felt helpless because it was all alone. It wanted to find friends to play with, but it could not move.One sunny day, a tiny bug came by. The bug saw the helpless mushroom and wanted to be its friend. The bug said, "Hi, mushroom! Do you want to play with me?" The mushroom was very happy and said, "Yes, I want to play with you!"So, the bug and the mushroom played all day long. They laughed and had lots of fun. The mushroom was not helpless anymore because it had a new friend. The bug helped the mushroom get stronger, and they were best friends forever.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/11/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-big-forest,-there-was-a-little-mushroom.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/11/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-big-forest,-there-was-a-little-mushroom.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-11-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-big-forest,-there-was-a-little-mushroom.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-10-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-10 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.222862+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to walk in the park with her mommy. One day, as they were walking, they saw a big, colorful rainbow in the sky. Lily thought it was the prettiest thing she had ever seen.Suddenly, they heard a loud noise. It was a big, scary monster! Lily was scared and didn't know what to do. But her mommy told her to be brave and stand tall. They decided to walk towards the monster to see if it was a friendly monster or a scary monster.As they got closer, they saw that the monster was actually a big, friendly dog that had gotten lost in the park. Lily was so happy to find the dog and even more excited to give it a big hug. From that day on, Lily and the dog would walk in the park together and look for more colorful rainbows.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/10/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/10/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-10-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-10-ben-was-a-boy-who-liked-to-play-with-his-toy-soldiers.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-10 - Ben was a boy who liked to play with his toy soldiers</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.221893+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Ben was a boy who liked to play with his toy soldiers. He had many soldiers of different colors and sizes. He liked to make them fight and march and shoot. He pretended he was his brave soldier and had to save the other soldiers from the bad guys.One day, he had a new friend on his birthday. Her name was Lily and she was his age. She came to his house with a big smile and a gift. Ben was very happy to see her. He gave her a hug and said thank you. He opened the gift and saw a new soldier. It was bigger and shinier than his old one. He was very attractive.Lily liked the new soldier too. She said he was very brave and strong. She wanted to play with him. Ben said yes and they went to his room. They set up the fight and the soldiers on the floor. They said "bang" and "bang" and "bang" and "bang" and "bang". They had a lot of fun. Ben liked to share his toys with Lily. He made her laugh and cry. He was a good friend.But then, something happened. One of the soldiers was</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/10/ben-was-a-boy-who-liked-to-play-with-his-toy-soldiers.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/10/ben-was-a-boy-who-liked-to-play-with-his-toy-soldiers.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-10-ben-was-a-boy-who-liked-to-play-with-his-toy-soldiers.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-09-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-09 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.221145+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She had a cute puppy named Max. One day, Lily took Max for a walk in the park. Max was so excited to go outside and play.When they got to the park, Lily saw a big wheel that could whirl round and round. She asked Max if he wanted to go on it with her. Max barked happily and wagged his tail.Lily put Max on the wheel and they started to spin around and around. It was so much fun! When they got off, Max was a little dizzy and smelly. Lily said, "Max, you need a bath!" Max replied, "Woof woof, okay!"Lily and Max went back home and Max took a nice bath. Lily snuggled up with Max and said, "Goodnight, Max. You are my best friend." Max wagged his tail and licked Lily's face. They both fell asleep, happy and tired from their fun day at the park.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/09/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/09/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-09-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-09-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-09 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.220263+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim. He had a big wish. He wanted a toy car that he saw in the store. But Tim was poor and did not have enough money to buy the car.One day, Tim met a kind old man. The old man said, "I can help you get the toy car. But first, you must do something for me." Tim was happy to help. The old man asked Tim to go to the park and find a lost dog. Tim did as the old man asked.At the park, Tim saw the lost dog. He picked up the dog and took it to the old man. The old man was very happy and said, "You did a good thing. Now, I will give you the toy car." Tim was so happy to receive the toy car from the old man. From that day on, Tim learned that helping others can bring good things to you too.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/09/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/09/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-09-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-09-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-09 - Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.219426+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to pick berries in the forest. One sunny day, Lily put on her red shoes and went to the forest to find some berries.As she walked, she saw her friend Tim. Tim had a long stick. He said, "Look, Lily! I have a stick. I can use it to shoot the berries down." Lily thought that was a fun idea. So, they took turns shooting the berries down from the tree.Soon, they had a big basket full of colorful berries. Lily said, "This was a successful berry- shooting adventure!" They laughed and went home to eat their yummy berries. And they lived happily ever after.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/09/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/09/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-09-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-08-once-upon-a-time-there-was-an-old-guard.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-08 - Once upon a time there was an old guard</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.218514+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time there was an old guard. Every day he would hold a big, heavy rock. He would look around and make sure everyone was safe.One day the guard was feeling very tired and he wanted to sit down. He looked around and saw a very old tree. He went over to the tree and sat down underneath it.The guard felt better and he smiled. He looked up and saw something very unusual - a little bird was flying by! The bird had bright blue feathers and was singing a sweet song.The guard heard the bird singing and it made him feel happy. He stayed under the tree and watched the bird, holding the old rock tight. He enjoyed the sunshine and the sound of the birds song all day.The old guard knew he could always come back to the tree when he needed to rest. And he was so happy to have found such a special place.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/08/once-upon-a-time-there-was-an-old-guard.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/08/once-upon-a-time-there-was-an-old-guard.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-08-once-upon-a-time-there-was-an-old-guard.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-08-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-lively-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-08 - Once upon a time, there was a lively little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.217611+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a lively little boy named Tim. Tim loved to play with his toy, a big magnet. One day, Tim went to the store with his mom. At the store, they saw a lot of toys. Tim was very happy.Tim's mom said, "You can pick one toy, Tim." But Tim saw his big magnet and wanted it. He said, "Mom, can I have the magnet?" His mom looked at the magnet and said, "Yes, Tim. Let's buy the magnet."Tim and his mom went to pay for the magnet. But Tim did not want to pay. He wanted the magnet. So, Tim took the magnet and ran out of the store. His mom was very angry and sad.The next day, Tim went to play with his magnet. But it was not fun anymore. It was lost because Tim did not pay for it. Tim cried and wished he had listened to his mom. The end.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/08/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-lively-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/08/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-lively-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-08-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-lively-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-08-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-08 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.216715+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play with her dolls and toys all day long. One day, Lily's mom asked her to clean up her toys before dinner. Lily didn't want to clean up, so she ignored her mom and kept playing.When it was time for dinner, Lily's mom saw that her toys were still scattered on the floor. She was very angry and told Lily that she couldn't play with her toys anymore. Lily was sad and didn't understand why her mom was so upset.The next day, Lily's mom took her on a walk in the park. They saw a beautiful pill on the ground and her mom picked it up. She told Lily that it was not safe to touch and that they should leave it alone. Lily was thoughtful and understood that her mom was trying to keep her safe.But then, Lily saw a squirrel and ran after it. She didn't listen to her mom and went too far away. When she turned around, she couldn't see her mom anymore. She started to cry and called out for her mom, but her</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/08/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/08/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-08-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-08-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-08 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.215847+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim. Tim had a toy car that he loved to play with. One day, Tim saw a wallet on the floor. He wanted to lift the wallet, but it was too heavy for him. He felt scared because he thought someone might be looking for it.Tim went to his friend, Sam. He said, "Sam, I found a wallet, but it is too heavy. Can you help me lift it?" Sam was not scared, so he said, "Yes, I will help you, Tim." They went to the wallet and lifted it together.As they lifted the wallet, a big man came running. He saw the wallet and got very angry. He said, "That is my wallet! Give it back!" Tim and Sam were scared and gave the wallet back to the man. The man took his wallet and went away. Tim and Sam were sad because they did not find out whose wallet it was.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/08/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/08/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-08-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-07-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-07 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.214988+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play outside in the park with her friends. One day, she found a shiny rock and put it in her pocket. She loved the texture of the rock because it was smooth and cool.Later that day, Lily's mommy told her that they were going to the store. Lily was excited to go, but as they walked, she started to get impatient. She wanted to go to the park again and play with her friends.When they got back to the park, Lily remembered the shiny rock in her pocket. She took it out and showed it to her friends. They all thought it was pretty cool too. Lily put the rock back in her pocket and they continued playing.As they were leaving the park, Lily realized that the shiny rock was gone. She looked in her pocket, but it wasn't there. She was sad, but then she looked down and saw a shiny coin on the ground. She picked it up and showed it to her friends. They all smiled and knew that Lily had found something special.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/07/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/07/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-07-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-07-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-dog-named-spot.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-07 - Once upon a time, there was a little dog named Spot</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.214120+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little dog named Spot. Spot had a different collar than his friends. It was red and blue. Spot liked to play near the pond. One day, Spot saw a big frog near the pond."Hi frog, I like your big hat!" said Spot. The frog looked at Spot and said, "Thank you, Spot. Do you want to play with me?" Spot was happy and jumped into the water. They played together, splashing and having fun.After playing, Spot and the frog were tired. They sat near the pond to rest. The sun was warm, and they felt good. Spot looked at his different collar and smiled. He was happy to have a new friend.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/07/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-dog-named-spot.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/07/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-dog-named-spot.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-07-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-dog-named-spot.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-07-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-07 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.213314+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to play with dough and make funny shapes. One day, Timmy's mommy asked him to help her make a pizza. Timmy was so excited and asked, "What do we need?".Mommy said, "We need dough, flour, sauce, and cheese. Can you measure out the ingredients for me?"Timmy was happy to help and got the measuring cup. He measured the flour and sugar and carefully poured it into the dough. Then, they rolled out the dough and mommy helped Timmy make the pizza dough by rolling it out and cutting out the dough shapes.As they were making the pizza dough, Timmy said, "Mommy, I'm ready to put the cheese on the pizza". Mommy smiled and said, "Great job, Timmy! Now let's put it in the oven and wait for it to bake". They put the pizza in the oven and waited patiently for it to cook. Finally, the pizza was ready and they sat down to eat</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/07/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/07/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-07-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-06-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-an-obedient-dog-named-spot.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-06 - Once upon a time, there was an obedient dog named Spot</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.212454+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was an obedient dog named Spot. Spot loved to play with his lime ball. One day, he saw a cat pass by with his lime ball. Spot was sad and wanted his ball back.Spot's friend, a bird named Sky, saw that Spot was sad. Sky wanted to help Spot get his lime ball back. So, Sky flew up high and took the lime ball from the cat. The cat and Spot were both surprised.Spot was very happy to have his lime ball back. But then, something unexpected happened. The cat and Sky started to play with the lime ball together! They became best friends and had lots of fun playing with the lime ball.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/06/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-an-obedient-dog-named-spot.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/06/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-an-obedient-dog-named-spot.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-06-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-an-obedient-dog-named-spot.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-06-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-06 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.211594+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to bounce on her pink bed, but her mom did not give her a chair to sit on. Lily was frustrated because she wanted to bounce on the bed, but she didn't want to sit on the floor.One day, Lily's mom took her to the store and they bought a big pink couch for her room. Lily was so happy! She bounced on the couch and it was so much fun. She could bounce on the couch and it was like jumping on a trampoline.But then, Lily's mom had to go to work and Lily was sad. She wanted to keep bouncing on the couch. So, she put the couch back in its place and sat on the floor. She bounced on the couch and it felt so good. Lily was happy again and she forgot all about being frustrated.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/06/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/06/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-06-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-05 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.210674+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. One day, she was playing outside in the park when she saw a lost puppy. The puppy looked very lonely and sad.Lily went up to the puppy and said, "Hi there, little puppy. Are you lost?" The puppy barked and wagged its tail, and Lily knew that the puppy needed help.Lily asked around the park if anyone was missing a puppy, but no one was. So, Lily decided to take the puppy home with her. She was very happy to have a new friend to play with.From that day on, Lily and the puppy were inseparable. They played together every day and the puppy was never lonely again. Lily was very happy that she could help the puppy find a new home with her.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-amy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-05 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Amy</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.209871+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Amy. She loved to paint. She would paint all day with her big brush and bright colors. One day, she painted a big, round sun and some pretty flowers.Amy's friend, Tom, came over to play. He saw the paintings and said, "Wow! I like your paintings, Amy!" Amy smiled and said, "Thank you, Tom! Do you want to paint with me?" Tom nodded, and they painted together.As they painted, a spicy smell filled the air. They looked around and saw Amy's mom cooking dinner. She was making spicy soup for them. Amy and Tom ran to the kitchen and said, "We love spicy soup!" They ate the soup and painted more pictures together. They had a lot of fun that day.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-amy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-amy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-amy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-05 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.209058+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to play outside with his friends. One day, Timmy's friend Billy saw a toy car that he really wanted. Billy was envious of Timmy's toy car and asked if he could play with it. Timmy said yes and gave Billy the toy car to play with.As they were playing, Timmy observed something strange. He saw a bird flying in the sky with a mark on its wing. Timmy told Billy about the mark on the bird's wing and Billy wanted to see it too. They both watched the bird fly away and wondered what it was looking at.After a while, it was time for Timmy to go home. He said goodbye to Billy and started walking home. On his way, Timmy observed a butterfly flying in the flowers. He thought it was very pretty and followed it for a little while before continuing on his way home. When he got home, he told his mom about the mark on the bird's wing and the butterfly he saw. His mom was happy to hear about his adventures and gave him a big hug.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-05 - Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.208295+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to play outside and run around. One day, he saw his friend Billy playing with a ball."Can I play with you?" asked Timmy."Sure!" said Billy. "Let's see who can throw the ball the farthest."Timmy threw the ball as hard as he could and it went very far. Billy was impressed. "Wow, you're really good at throwing!"Suddenly, Timmy saw something shiny on the ground. "Look, Billy! There's glue over there. Let's use it to make a picture!"They picked up the glue and started gluing different shapes together. They made a beautiful picture of a bird.After they finished, Timmy's mom came outside and saw the picture. "That's amazing!" she said. "You two are so good at making things together. I'm proud of you."Timmy and Billy smiled and felt happy. They knew they had done something special.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-04 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.207271+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. One day, Lily went to the park with her mom. While playing, she saw a filthy dog.Lily: "Mommy, look at that dirty dog. He needs a bath."Mom: "Yes, he does. Let's go see if we can find him a home."They walked around the park and found a cute little dog in the distance.Lily: "Mommy, can we take him home with us?"Mom: "I don't think we can. He has a license to be in our backyard."The dog had an urge to come home with them, but they knew it was important to follow the rules. So they decided to adopt him and give him a good home. From that day on, Lily and the dog became the best of friends.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-04 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.206537+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. Timmy loved trains, especially the big ones that went choo-choo. One day, Timmy went to the train station with his mommy and daddy. They saw a big train waiting for them.Timmy was so excited to see the train that he ran towards it. But his mommy said, "Stop, Timmy! It's not safe to run on the tracks." Timmy stopped and looked at the train. He thought it was so big and cool.Suddenly, the train conductor saw Timmy and his parents. He said, "Would you like to come on the train and see the inside?" Timmy's eyes got big and he nodded his head. He and his family got on the train and saw all the different parts. It was the best day ever!</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-friendly-cat-named-tom.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-04 - Once upon a time, there was a friendly cat named Tom</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.205846+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a friendly cat named Tom. Tom liked to play with his toy mouse near the toilet. One day, Tom saw the toilet door open. He thought, "I can guess who is inside!"As Tom looked in, he saw a big frog! The frog said, "Hi, I am Fred. Do you want to play with me?" Tom was surprised and said, "Yes, let's play!" They played and had a lot of fun.But then, something unexpected happened. Fred the frog jumped into the toilet and turned into a beautiful fish! Tom was so surprised. Fred said, "I am a magic fish! When I jumped in, I turned into a frog." Tom and Fred became best friends and played together every day.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-friendly-cat-named-tom.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-friendly-cat-named-tom.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-friendly-cat-named-tom.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-03-one-day,-tom-and-sue-went-to-play-in-the-park.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-03 - One day, Tom and Sue went to play in the park</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.205139+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, Tom and Sue went to play in the park. They saw a big tree and wanted to act like monkeys. So, they put on monkey hats and jumped from tree to tree. They were having so much fun.But then, they saw a little bird stuck in the tree. The bird was wearing a fake wing with a hook on it. Tom and Sue wanted to help the bird. They tried to pull the hook away from the bird's wing, but it was stuck.Tom and Sue worked together to get the hook out. They pulled and pulled until the hook came off. The little bird was free and flew away happily. Tom and Sue felt good that they helped the bird. They went back to playing and had a great day.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/03/one-day,-tom-and-sue-went-to-play-in-the-park.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/03/one-day,-tom-and-sue-went-to-play-in-the-park.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-03-one-day,-tom-and-sue-went-to-play-in-the-park.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-03-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-03 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.204368+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play outside in the garden. One day, she found a beautiful flower with deep colors. She picked it up and showed it to her mom."Mommy, look at this pretty flower I found!" Lily said."That's lovely, Lily. You can hold it and take care of it," her mom replied.Lily held the flower in her hand and continued to play. Later that day, she saw a bird with a broken wing. She remembered the flower and how she held it close. She thought about the bird and how important it was to be kind to animals.So, she gently held the bird in her hands and brought it to her mom. Her mom helped the bird and soon it was able to fly again. Lily felt happy knowing that she helped the bird. She learned that holding something gently and kind to others is important.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/03/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/03/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-03-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-03-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-fisherman-named-jack.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-03 - Once upon a time, there was a fisherman named Jack</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.203505+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a fisherman named Jack. He loved to fish in the river every day. One day, Jack caught a big fish. He was so happy that he shouted, "Wow, this is a big fish!"Suddenly, the fisherman's face became pale. He realized that he had forgotten to put the hook on the fish's mouth. "Oh no!" he said. "I forgot to put the hook on the fish's mouth."Just then, a little girl walked by and saw Jack's problem. "Don't worry, Mr. Fisherman," she said. "I can help you." She took the fish and put the hook on its mouth. The fish was so hungry that it ate all the other fish in the river.Jack was so grateful to the little girl. "Thank you so much for helping me," he said. "You are so kind." From that day on, Jack always made sure to put the hook on the fish's mouth before he went fishing.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/03/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-fisherman-named-jack.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/03/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-fisherman-named-jack.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-03-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-fisherman-named-jack.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-02-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-sleepy-cat-named-kitty.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-02 - Once upon a time, there was a sleepy cat named Kitty</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.202542+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a sleepy cat named Kitty. Kitty loved to take naps under the big tree in the park. Every day, she would go to the tree, curl up in her soft bed, and sleep.One sunny day, Kitty found a quiz on the ground. She was curious and wanted to play. Kitty asked her friend, Doggy, to play with her. They took turns asking each other questions. They laughed and had fun.After they finished the quiz, Kitty and Doggy felt happy and not sleepy anymore. They learned that playing together is more fun than playing alone. The moral of the story is that sharing and playing with friends can make you feel refreshed and happy.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/02/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-sleepy-cat-named-kitty.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/02/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-sleepy-cat-named-kitty.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-02-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-sleepy-cat-named-kitty.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-02-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-02 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.201722+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim. Tim was a sleepy boy who loved to play with his toy cars. One day, Tim's mom said, "Tim, it's time for your nap." Tim didn't want to nap, but he knew he had to listen to his mom.Before Tim went to bed, he asked his mom, "Can you record me playing with my cars in my room?" His mom smiled and said, "Of course, Tim!" She went to get her phone and recorded Tim playing with his cars.That night, Tim had a dream. In his dream, he saw a big hospital with many rooms. In one room, he met a sleepy doctor. The doctor said, "Hello, Tim! Are you feeling okay in here?" Tim said, "Yes, I am just a little sleepy." The doctor smiled and said, "Don't worry, you'll feel better soon." Tim woke up feeling happy and ready to play with his cars again.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/02/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/02/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-02-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-02-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bald-man.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-02 - Once upon a time, there was a bald man</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.200521+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a bald man. He loved to play with his drum. One day, he went to the park with his drum to play for the kids.As soon as he arrived, he felt a big drop of water on his head. He looked up and saw dark clouds in the sky. He knew it was going to rain soon. The bald man was worried that his drum would get wet and ruined.The bald man and the kids played and played. But then, the rain came pouring down. The rain made the ground very wet and slippery. The drum started to slip from the bald man's hands. Just in time, the drum landed in a puddle, but it was still okay. The bald man was happy and the kids clapped for him. They all laughed and played in the water until the sun came out again.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/02/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bald-man.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/02/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bald-man.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-02-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bald-man.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-02-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-big-forest,-there-lived-a-little-deer.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-02 - Once upon a time, in a big forest, there lived a little deer</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.199685+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a big forest, there lived a little deer. The little deer liked to play with his friends. They would run and jump all day long.One day, while playing, the little deer saw a big tree. He wanted to lean on the tree to rest. As he leaned on the tree, he heard a loud noise. The little deer was scared.But then, something unexpected happened. The big tree was not a tree at all! It was a giant, friendly bear who was just sleeping. The bear woke up and smiled at the little deer. They became best friends and played together in the forest every day.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/02/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-big-forest,-there-lived-a-little-deer.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/02/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-big-forest,-there-lived-a-little-deer.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-02-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-big-forest,-there-lived-a-little-deer.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-01-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-weak-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-01 - Once upon a time, there was a weak little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.198783+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a weak little boy named Tim. He had a toy car that he loved to play with. Tim wanted to add more fun to his toy car, so he asked his mom for help."Mom, can you help me add more fun to my car?" Tim asked. His mom thought for a moment and said, "Yes, Tim. Let's add more wheels to make it go faster!"Tim and his mom went to find more wheels for the toy car. They found a red one, a blue one, and a yellow one. Tim was very happy. He put the wheels on his car and started to play with it.As Tim played with his toy car, he saw a big hill. He thought it would be fun to make his car go down the hill. He pushed the car down the hill, and it went very fast. Tim was so excited that his weak little car could now go faster than ever before. And that's how Tim discovered the power of adding more fun to his toy car.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/01/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-weak-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/01/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-weak-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-01-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-weak-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-01-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-01 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Sue</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.197923+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Sue. She was very excited because she was going to the store with her mom to buy a toy. Sue could not wait to get there and pick out the best toy.When they got to the store, Sue saw a toy puppy that she wanted. But her mom told her it was a fake puppy, not a real one. Sue was sad but then she saw a bright red ball. She picked it up and it made her happy again.Sue and her mom bought the red ball and went home. Sue played with her new ball all day. She loved her new ball and was very happy that she got to go to the store with her mom.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/01/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/01/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-01-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-01-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-01 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.197086+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play outside in the garden and look at all the animals. One day, she saw a little fox running around. The fox looked sad and Lily felt bad for him.Lily wanted to make the fox happy, so she decided to provide him with some food. She went inside and got some carrots and apples for the fox. When she came back outside, the fox was gone!Lily was sad and didn't know what to do. Suddenly, she heard a noise behind her. She turned around and saw the little fox hiding behind a tree. He had been playing a trick on her! Lily was surprised but happy that the fox was okay. From that day on, Lily and the little fox became good friends and played together every day in the garden.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/01/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/01/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-01-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-01-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-01 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.196236+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to play with his blocks and build tall towers. One day, Timmy's big sister Sarah came over to play. "What are you building, Timmy?" she asked. "I'm building a big tower," Timmy replied.As Timmy was building his tower, he accidentally knocked over a cup of juice. "Oh no!" he cried. "I'm sorry, Sarah." "It's okay, Timmy," Sarah said. "Let's clean it up." They used a towel to wipe up the juice and then went back to building the tower.Suddenly, they noticed that there was a leak in the tower. "Oh no!" Timmy said. "We have to fix it." Sarah helped Timmy wrap his hands around the tower and they used some glue to put it back together. "We did it!" Timmy said, feeling proud of their tower."That was a fun day," Sarah said. "Let's build something else tomorrow!" Timmy smiled and said, "Okay!" They hugged each other and went inside for dinner</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/01/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/01/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-01-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-31-one-day,-a-little-boy-named-tim-went-to-the-park-with-his-mom.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-07-31 - One day, a little boy named Tim went to the park with his mom</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.195382+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a little boy named Tim went to the park with his mom. At the park, he saw a big pond. Tim liked to play in the pond, so he asked his mom, "Can I play in the pond, please?" His mom said, "Yes, but be careful not to step in the water."Tim ran to the pond and saw a frog. The frog was green and slimy. Tim thought the frog looked disgusting, but he wanted to talk to the frog. He said, "Hello, Mr. Frog. Why do you look so disgusting?" The frog said, "I don't like to be dirty. I like to be clean and pretty."Tim wanted to help the frog. He took his hands and started to wash the frog. As he washed the frog, something unexpected happened. The frog turned into a beautiful butterfly! The butterfly said, "Thank you, Tim! You made me clean and pretty again. Now, I will help you." The butterfly helped Tim climb the slide, and he had so much fun. In the end, Tim made a new friend, and they played together at the park all day.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/31/one-day,-a-little-boy-named-tim-went-to-the-park-with-his-mom.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/31/one-day,-a-little-boy-named-tim-went-to-the-park-with-his-mom.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-31-one-day,-a-little-boy-named-tim-went-to-the-park-with-his-mom.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-31-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-07-31 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.194488+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She had a teddy bear that she loved very much. One day, her mommy told her that this toy was very expensive.Lily didn't understand what "expensive" meant, so her mommy explained that it meant the toy cost a lot of money. Lily didn't care about that, she just wanted to play with the teddy bear.Later that day, Lily and her teddy bear went outside to play. Suddenly, Lily fell down and hurt her knee. She started to cry. Her mommy came to comfort her and gave her a big hug.Lily's mommy told her that sometimes we don't care about expensive things, we just want to get help and care for our loved ones. She also reminded her that her teddy bear was just a toy and that she loved him very much. From that day on, Lily realized that her mommy was right and that her teddy bear was more important than any expensive toy she wanted.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/31/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/31/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-31-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-31-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-07-31 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.193602+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim. He liked to play with his ball outside. One day, while playing, he saw a loop on the ground. It was hard and looked like a big loop. Tim thought it was fun to play with.Tim picked up the loop and started to roll it on the ground. It was a hard loop, but he liked it a lot. He rolled it up and down the green grass. He rolled it over the fence, and it was fun to see how far it went.After a while, Tim's mom called him to come inside. Tim picked up his ball and walked back home. He showed his mom the hard loop he found. She smiled and said, "What a fun toy to play with!" Tim was happy and couldn't wait to play with his loop again the next day.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/31/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/31/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-31-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-31-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-helpful-girl-named-amy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-07-31 - Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a helpful girl named Amy</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.192672+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a helpful girl named Amy. She liked to help everyone. One day, she found a hidden symbol on the ground. The symbol was a big, shiny star. Amy knew the star was special.Amy showed the symbol to her friend, Tom. "Look, Tom!" she said. "I found a special star. Do you think it's magic?" Tom thought for a moment. "Maybe," he said, "but we should be careful with it."Amy and Tom decided to keep the star safe, but they didn't know that the star was magical. One day, when they were playing near the woods, the star began to glow. Suddenly, Tom picked it up and a big, friendly giant appeared.The giant thanked Amy and Tom for finding his lost symbol. He had lost it in the woods while he was playing. As a thank you gift, the giant gave both Amy and Tom a magic wand. From that day on, they could help even more people with their new magic wand. And they lived happily ever after.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/31/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-helpful-girl-named-amy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/31/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-helpful-girl-named-amy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-31-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-helpful-girl-named-amy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-31-lily-was-a-girl-who-liked-to-play-with-her-doll.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-07-31 - Lily was a girl who liked to play with her doll</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.191813+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Lily was a girl who liked to play with her doll. She gave her doll a name, Anna, and a dress, pink. Lily and Anna did everything together. They had tea parties, read books, and sang songs. Lily loved Anna very much.One day, Lily's mom said, "Lily, we are going to visit grandma. She has a big house and a garden. Do you want to go?" Lily nodded. She liked grandma. She had a cat, a dog, and a bird. Lily wanted to bring Anna. She asked her mom, "Can I bring Anna, please?"Mom smiled. "Yes, you can, Lily. Anna can come too. But you have to be careful. Anna is fragile. She has a lot of style. She likes to wear different clothes and hats. If you squeeze her too hard, her dress will tear. If you squeeze her too hard, she might get a hole or a stain."Lily agreed. She put Anna on her bed and gave her a hug. "Don't be scared, Anna. I won't squeeen more people with their new magic wand. And they lived happily ever after.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/31/lily-was-a-girl-who-liked-to-play-with-her-doll.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/31/lily-was-a-girl-who-liked-to-play-with-her-doll.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-31-lily-was-a-girl-who-liked-to-play-with-her-doll.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-30-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-07-30 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Sue</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.190806+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Sue. Sue had a big dog named Max. They liked to play in the open yard. One day, they saw a big cobweb in the yard. Sue and Max were scared.Sue said to Max, "Max, let's hurry and move away from the cobweb." Max nodded and they ran away from the cobweb. They found a new hiding spot and felt safe.Later, Sue and Max went back to the cobweb. They saw a tiny spider named Sam. Sam said, "Thank you for not touching my cobweb." Sue and Max were happy they did not touch the cobweb. They made a new friend that day.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/30/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/30/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-30-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-30-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-07-30 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.189957+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. He had a toy car that he loved to play with every day. One day, Timmy's friend Billy came over to play. Billy wanted to play with Timmy's toy car, but Timmy didn't want to share."I don't want to share my car," Timmy said."But I want to play too," Billy replied.Timmy thought about it and realized that he could solve the problem by sharing his car with Billy. He climbed up high on a swing and gave the car to Billy."Here you go," Timmy said.Billy was happy and played with the car in the silence, making it his second turn to another. The two friends had a great time playing together and sharing their toys.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/30/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/30/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-30-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-30-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-great-big-bear.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-07-30 - Once upon a time, there was a great big bear</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.189104+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a great big bear. He was so big that he needed a large frame to live in. One day, he went to the forest to find a frame. He looked around and found a large frame! He was so happy!The bear went to the frame to mind it. He wanted to keep it nice and safe. But then something bad happened. The bear was so excited to have the frame that he forgot to mind it. The frame fell to the ground and broke into many pieces.The bear was sad that he couldn't keep the frame safe. He felt very disappointed. He had learned his lesson and was very scared that he might not be able to mind it ever again.The bear never got to fix the frame. He was so sad and his bad ending meant he had to get a new frame that was always safe.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/30/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-great-big-bear.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/30/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-great-big-bear.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-30-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-great-big-bear.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-30-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-cat.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-07-30 - Once upon a time, there was a big cat</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.188242+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a big cat. The cat was very good at laying a big ball of yarn. The yarn was on the ground and the cat loved to play with it.One day, a little girl came along and saw the cat playing with the yarn. She thought it was very attractive with its bright colors. The cat came over to the little girl and let her play too.The two cats played together for a long time, rolling the yarn back and forth. When they were done, they lay down together and cuddled up with the yarn. They were very happy and became good friends.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/30/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-cat.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/30/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-cat.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-30-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-cat.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-29-one-day,-a-little-girl-named-mia-wanted-to-visit-the-pond.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-07-29 - One day, a little girl named Mia wanted to visit the pond</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.187390+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a little girl named Mia wanted to visit the pond. She asked her mom, "Can I go to the pond, please?" Her mom said, "Yes, but be careful and stay safe."Mia went to the pond and saw a little duck. The duck was lost and was helpless. Mia wanted to help the duck. She said, "Don't be scared, I will help you."Mia picked up the duck and walked around the pond. She found the duck's family on some other side of the pond. The duck was happy and said, "Thank you, Mia!" Mia felt good because she helped the duck and went to visit the pond.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/29/one-day,-a-little-girl-named-mia-wanted-to-visit-the-pond.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/29/one-day,-a-little-girl-named-mia-wanted-to-visit-the-pond.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-29-one-day,-a-little-girl-named-mia-wanted-to-visit-the-pond.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-29-one-day,-a-little-boy-named-tim-went-for-a-walk-with-his-mom.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-07-29 - One day, a little boy named Tim went for a walk with his mom</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.186486+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a little boy named Tim went for a walk with his mom. They saw a big car on the side of the road. The car was red and shiny. Tim liked the car very much. He wanted to see it up close."Mom, can we go see the car?" Tim asked. His mom said yes, and they walked to the car. Tim looked inside and saw that the door was locked. A key was on the ground near the door. Tim picked it up and showed it to his mom."Good job, Tim! We will try to open the door," his mom said. They put the key in the door and turned it. The door opened, and they went inside the car. The car was fake. It was a toy car with wheels. Tim was happy to have the real car. They went home and played with the car all day.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/29/one-day,-a-little-boy-named-tim-went-for-a-walk-with-his-mom.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/29/one-day,-a-little-boy-named-tim-went-for-a-walk-with-his-mom.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-29-one-day,-a-little-boy-named-tim-went-for-a-walk-with-his-mom.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-raven-who-loved-to-fly-high-in-the-sky.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-07-29 - Once upon a time, there was a raven who loved to fly high in the sky</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.185658+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a raven who loved to fly high in the sky. One day, the raven saw a little girl who was playing in the park. The raven felt happy and wanted to play with her too.The little girl saw the raven and ran towards him. She hugged him tightly and they played together. The raven felt so happy and loved. He felt warm and safe in the little girl's arms.As the sun began to set, the little girl's mom came to pick her up. The raven said goodbye to the little girl and flew away. The little girl felt sad but also felt happy because she made a new friend. The raven felt happy too and felt tight in his heart.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-raven-who-loved-to-fly-high-in-the-sky.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-raven-who-loved-to-fly-high-in-the-sky.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-raven-who-loved-to-fly-high-in-the-sky.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-07-29 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.184794+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She was very curious and loved to explore. One day, she went for a walk in the park and found a big tunnel. She felt excited and decided to go inside.As she walked through the tunnel, she saw many different animals like birds, rabbits, and squirrels. They all looked happy and friendly. Lily felt a little bit unsure, but decided to keep going.Suddenly, she heard a loud noise and felt herself falling. She was scared and didn't know what to do. But then, a kind lady approached her and helped her back up. Lily felt relieved and grateful. She learned that sometimes it's okay to be curious, but it's also important to ask for help when you need it.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-07-29 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.183943+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. Timmy liked to play outside and explore. One day, he went for a walk near a stream. He saw a fish swimming in the stream and wanted to catch it.But Timmy's mom said, "Be careful, Timmy. The stream is not easy to catch fish like this. You need to enjoy the walk and not get too excited."Timmy listened to his mom and walked carefully. He saw some rocks by the stream and decided to collect them instead. He put them in a bucket and went back home.When he got home, Timmy showed his mom the rocks he collected. She was very happy and proud of him. Timmy learned that it's important to enjoy the walk and not get too excited.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-grumpy-cat-named-max.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-07-29 - Once upon a time, there was a grumpy cat named Max</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.182967+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a grumpy cat named Max. Max lived in a small house with a girl named Lily. Lily loved Max, but Max did not like to play with Lily. One day, Lily felt sick and her mom had to take her to the hospital.At the hospital, Lily met a nurse named Sarah. Sarah was nice and made Max feel better. Max's paw got better, and he even played with Sarah. "Max, you can go home now," said Sarah. Max was happy, so he followed Sarah home.When they got home, Max saw a big box in the living room. He was curious and jumped inside. Lily heard Max and came inside too. "Max, come out!" she said. Max tried to escape, but he could not. Suddenly, the box opened, and Max vanished. Lily's mom was surprised and said, "Silly Max, he was just playing hide and seek!" Lily laughed, and they all played together until it was time for Max to be a grumpy cat again.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-grumpy-cat-named-max.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-grumpy-cat-named-max.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-grumpy-cat-named-max.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-colorful-chicken-named-chickie.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-07-29 - Once upon a time, there was a colorful chicken named Chickie</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.182042+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a colorful chicken named Chickie. Chickie lived on a farm with other animals. One day, Chickie met a mule named Molly. Molly was big and had long ears."Hello, Chickie!" said Molly. "Welcome to our farm!""Thank you, Molly!" said Chickie. "I like your colorful tails!"Suddenly, a big storm came and the wind blew all the leaves off the trees. Chickie got scared and hid under a pile of hay.Molly saw Chickie hiding and said, "Don't be afraid, Chickie. I'll help you feel better."Molly used her long ears to lift up the hay and helped Chickie feel safe. Chickie felt happy and grateful to have a new friend like Molly.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-colorful-chicken-named-chickie.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-colorful-chicken-named-chickie.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-colorful-chicken-named-chickie.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-29-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-village,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-07-29 - Once upon a time, in a small village, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.181347+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a small village, there was a little boy named Tim. Tim had a fun idea to play on the swings. He loved to swing high in the sky, but his mom always told him to be careful.One day, when Tim was swinging, he saw a big ball stuck in a tree. He wanted to get the ball down, but the tree was very tall. Tim was scared, but he had a brave face. He knew he could do it if he tried. So, he just let a little push on the swing, and the ball started to fall.As the ball fell, Tim's mom saw what happened and ran over to help him. She looked up at the tree and saw the big ball stuck in its branches. She reached up and got the ball down for Tim. He was so happy and thanked his mom. From that day on, Tim always remembered to be careful when he played on the swings.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/29/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-village,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/29/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-village,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-29-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-village,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-29-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-big-slide.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-07-29 - Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a big slide</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.180571+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a big slide. All the kids loved to play on the slide. One day, a new boy came to the town. He wanted to play on the slide too, but he was scared. He thought he would not be successful at it.The new boy's friend, a girl named Sue, saw that he was scared. She said, "Don't worry, I will help you!" So, Sue and the new boy went to the slide together. They climbed up and sat down. They held hands with their hands, and they slid down the slide. They laughed and had fun.But then, another boy, named Jim, came and said, "I want to play too!" This made Sue sad. Sue told Jim, "It's okay, we can all play together!" So, Sue, Spin the new boy, and Jim all played on the slide. They were all happy and successful in having fun.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/29/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-big-slide.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/29/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-big-slide.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-29-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-big-slide.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-29-once-there-was-a-lady-who-had.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-07-29 - "Once there was a lady who had an important meal to feed."</title><updated>2023-08-22T07:10:08.179611+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once there was a lady who had an important meal to feed. She was busy in the kitchen when suddenly, the phone rang. She stopped what she was doing and quickly answered the phone. It was her friend and she said it was time to feed the meal.The lady went to grab all the ingredients she would need and put them on the counter. She was counting down the spices and spices.When she was done, she looked up at the phone. It had yielded to her and she realized it was broken.She ran to the store to get a new handkerchief. But when she arrived she found out the old one was too tight! She couldn't find the right part.The lady shrugged her shoulders, feeling sad and frustrated. She needed to find a way to feed her meal. But it was too early to do so.So she went home and set the milk stood straight. She tried wiping the bowl but nothing looked right.Then she had an idea. She decided to try stepping on the top, to see if it had the right support. So she did, and sure enough it worked! She was so happy she could finally feed her meal.The end.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/29/once-there-was-a-lady-who-had.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/07/29/once-there-was-a-lady-who-had.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-07-29-once-there-was-a-lady-who-had.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry></feed>