<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><id>https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime</id><title>AI Daily Short Story</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.668576+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime" rel="self"/><generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator><logo>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/ai_generated_stories.png</logo><subtitle>A daily pod cast of an AI generated short story</subtitle><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-25-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-25 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.832143+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to sing and dance, but he was very quiet. He didn't like to make noise, so he never sang or danced very loud. One day, Timmy's mom bought him a microphone. It was big and red, and it made Timmy very happy.Timmy wanted to sing into his microphone, but he didn't know how to use it. He asked his mom for help, and she showed him how to use it. Timmy had so much fun singing into his microphone that he sang all day long. His mom was proud of him for being so creative.As Timmy grew older, he learned to be less noisy. He still sang and danced, but he made sure to use his microphone and other things without making too much noise. Timmy reversed his learning and became a better singer and dancer.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/25/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/25/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-25-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-24-once-there-was-a-cute-little-girl-called-jill.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-24 - Once there was a cute little girl called Jill</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.831262+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once there was a cute little girl called Jill. She loved to explore and play. One day Jill's mom suggested they go to the museum. Jill was excited and quickly put on her shoes.When they got to the museum, Jill was amazed at all the things she saw. She saw beautiful paintings, sculptures and even a real dinosaur! Jill and her mom walked around and looked at everything. They even had some time to play hide and seek!Afterwards, Jill was tired but very happy. She had had so much fun exploring the museum. Her mom suggested that they come back again soon. Jill smiled and nodded, agreeing with her mom.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/24/once-there-was-a-cute-little-girl-called-jill.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/24/once-there-was-a-cute-little-girl-called-jill.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-24-once-there-was-a-cute-little-girl-called-jill.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-23-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-kitten-named-mittens.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-23 - Once upon a time, there was a little kitten named Mittens</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.830397+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little kitten named Mittens. Mittens was very naughty and liked to play pranks on her owner, Sarah. One day, Mittens saw a mouse in the closet and tried to catch it. But the mouse was too quick and ran away.Sarah saw what Mittens had done and said, "Mittens, you acted like a bad kitten. You scared the mouse!"Mittens felt sad and didn't know what to do. But then, Sarah said, "Don't worry, Mittens. I'll give you a treat if you promise to be a good kitten from now on."Mittens was happy and promised to be good. From that day on, Mittens never acted like a naughty kitten again and always remembered to be kind to her owner.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/23/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-kitten-named-mittens.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/23/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-kitten-named-mittens.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-23-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-kitten-named-mittens.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-mouse-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-22 - Once upon a time, there was a little mouse named Timmy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.829479+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little mouse named Timmy. Timmy was very small and had a weak tail. He lived in a cozy hole in the wall of a big house. One day, Timmy heard a loud noise outside his hole. He peeked out and saw a big, scary cat staring at him.Timmy knew he had to be brave and find a way to escape from the cat. He remembered his weak tail and decided to use it to climb up a nearby tree. The cat tried to climb the tree too, but it was too weak and couldn't make it up.Timmy was safe in the tree and he realized that even though his tail was weak, he was also very clever. From that day on, he always kept an eye out for danger and used his tail to defend himself. And whenever he saw a cat staring at him, he knew he just had to be brave and find a way to escape.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-mouse-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-mouse-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-mouse-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-21 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.828689+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved going to the beach with her mommy and daddy. One day, while playing in the sand, she saw a crab. The crab had smooth skin and was walking sideways.Lily wanted to hold the crab, so she asked her mommy, "Can I hold the crab, please?"Her mommy said, "Be careful, Lily. Crabs can pinch. You should hold it gently."Lily reached out her hand and held the crab. She felt its smooth shell and gently squeezed it. The crab didn't pinch her and Lily giggled with joy.From that day on, Lily always remembered to be careful when holding crabs. She loved going to the beach even more because she knew she could hold a crab and feel how smooth its skin was.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-fish-in-the-sea.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-20 - Once upon a time, there was a big fish in the sea</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.827834+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a big fish in the sea. The fish was very happy swimming around in the water. One day, the fish saw a shiny thing in the water. It was a trade! The fish wanted the trade very much.The fish asked the other fish in the sea if they had anything to trade for the shiny thing. But no one had anything. So, the fish decided to dive down to the bottom of the sea to look for something to trade.As the fish was swimming down, it saw a big rock. The fish thought the rock might have something shiny inside. The fish dove down and found a shiny necklace. The fish was so happy!But as the fish was swimming back up, it got stuck in a fishing net. The fish tried and tried to get free, but it couldn't. The fish was very sad and scared. It wished it had never tried to trade something so expensive.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-fish-in-the-sea.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-fish-in-the-sea.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-fish-in-the-sea.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-19 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.826950+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play with her toys and watch cartoons. One day, her mom told her that they were going on a trip to visit her grandma. Lily got very excited and started to pack her favorite toys.When they arrived at grandma's house, Lily saw a big box in the living room. She asked her grandma what was inside, but her grandma said it was a surprise. Lily couldn't wait to find out what was inside the box.Later that day, grandma finally opened the box and pulled out a book. It was a very nice book with lots of colorful pictures. Grandma read it to Lily and they both enjoyed it very much. At the end of the story, grandma said, "Let's measure how much fun we had today!" Lily didn't really understand what that meant, but she was happy to hear that they had a fun day together.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-18-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-18 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.826058+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. Lily loved to enjoy walks with her mom and dad. One day, they went for a walk in the park. The sun was shining and the birds were singing. Lily was very happy.While walking, Lily saw a big red ball. She wanted to play with it, but she was fearful. She didn't know what the ball could do. Lily's mom saw her looking at the ball and said, "Don't be scared, Lily. It's just a ball to play with."Lily's dad picked up the ball and gave it to her. She started to play with the ball and soon she was laughing and having fun. She enjoyed her walk in the park with her mom, dad, and the big red ball.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/18/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/18/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-18-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-17-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-17 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.825192+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim. Tim was very restless. He wanted to play all day long. One day, Tim's mom took him to a big place where many people were eating and talking. This place was called a restaurant.Tim's mom said, "Tim, we need to eat at this restaurant to stay strong and healthy." Tim did not want to listen. He wanted to play with his friends. But his mom insisted that they go inside the restaurant.At the restaurant, Tim saw a big plate of yummy food. He ate and ate, and soon, he felt happy and full. Tim's mom was right. He felt strong and healthy. After they finished eating, Tim went outside to play with his friends. Now, when Tim felt restless, he knew it was time to eat and have fun.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/17/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/17/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-17-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-16 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.824338+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play dress-up and wear different costumes. One day, she put on her princess costume and went to show her mommy."Look, mommy! I'm a princess!" Lily said."You look beautiful, my little princess," mommy replied.Lily went outside to play with her friends. She saw her friend Timmy playing with a ball."Can I play too?" Lily asked."Sure, but be careful," Timmy warned.Lily was careless and threw the ball too hard. It hit a tree and popped. They couldn't use the ball anymore."I'm sorry, Timmy. I'll get you a new ball," Lily said."It's okay, Lily. You can help me find one in my toy box," Timmy said.Lily was happy to help her friend and they went to Timmy's toy box to find a new ball. From then on, Lily was more careful when she played with her friends.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-15-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-dirty-jug.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-15 - Once upon a time, there was a dirty jug</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.823459+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a dirty jug. The dirty jug lived in a small house with a boy named Tim. Tim wanted to improve the jug and make it clean and shiny. So, he took the jug outside to wash it.As Tim was washing the dirty jug, a magic frog jumped out of it. The frog said, "Thank you for cleaning me, Tim! I will give you a wish. What do you want?" Tim thought for a moment and said, "I wish that my jug will never be dirty again!"The magic frog smiled and said, "Your wish is granted!" Suddenly, the dirty jug became clean, but it was no longer round! It had turned into a big, round ball that could roll. Tim was surprised, but he liked the ball even more than the jug. From that day on, Tim played with his new ball all the time, and he and the magic frog became best friends.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/15/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-dirty-jug.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/15/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-dirty-jug.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-15-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-dirty-jug.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-14-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-14 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.822590+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to play with his toy cars and trucks. One day, Timmy's mom took him to the toy store. Timmy saw a big, red truck that he really wanted.Timmy's mom said, "That truck is too expensive. We can't buy it today." Timmy was sad, but he understood. Suddenly, Timmy saw a machine that could make anything move. He asked his mom if they could buy it instead.His mom said, "No, that machine is too expensive. We can't spend all our money on it." Timmy understood and decided to save his money to buy the truck he wanted.A few weeks later, Timmy had saved enough money to buy the truck. He was so happy! But when he got home, he saw that his little sister had messed up his stickers with glue. Timmy was upset and didn't know what to do.His mom said, "Don't worry, we can use the machine to fix your stickers." They used the machine to glue the</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/14/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/14/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-14-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-13-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big,-big-castle.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-13 - Once upon a time, there was a big, big castle</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.821630+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a big, big castle. It had a huge chamber with lots of rooms. In one of the rooms, there was a little princess.The princess had a toy horse that she loved to ride. She would ride it all around the castle's garden. One day, a naughty dragon came to the castle and tried to steal the princess's toy horse.The princess was very brave and rode her horse to the dragon's cave. She saw the dragon sleeping and quickly took her toy horse back to her chamber. Her toys were safe and sound, and she was very happy.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/13/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big,-big-castle.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/13/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big,-big-castle.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-13-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big,-big-castle.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-12-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-12 - Once upon a time, there was a girl</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.820823+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a girl. She had pink hair and loved to jump. Every day, she would jump and play outside in the sunshine. She had lots of fun!One day, the girl found a big, pink flower. She was so happy! She wanted to jump and celebrate, so she rushed and ran around the flower. When she was done, she jumped up and down in delight. She laughed and smiled and had the best time.The girl kept jumping and playing around the pink flower every day. She would always look up at it and give it a big smile. And every time she came across it, she felt so happy and free.The pink flower was her favorite. Whenever she wanted to jump and play, she would run over and give it a big hug. It was always so nice to cuddle and cuddle!The girl and the pink flower were best friends. They would jump, run, and laugh together all day long. They had so much fun and the girl was so happy that she had found her special friend.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/12/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/12/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-12-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-11-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-11 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Sue</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.820003+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Sue. Sue had a toy box with many toys. One day, she found a screw on the floor. She picked it up and showed it to her mom."Mom, what is this?" Sue asked. Her mom looked at the screw and said, "That is a screw, Sue. We use it to hold things together. But be careful, it is sharp and can hurt you."Sue put the screw back in the toy box. She played with her toys and had a lot of fun. But then, she seemed confused. She couldn't find her favorite toy, a little teddy bear. Sue looked everywhere, but she couldn't find it.She called her mom and said, "Mom, I can't find my teddy bear. I am confused." Her mom came and helped her look for the teddy bear. They found it under Sue's bed. Sue was very happy to have her teddy bear back.From that day on, Sue always kept the screw in the toy box, just in case she lost something again. She learned that it was important to be careful with</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/11/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/11/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-11-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-10-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-10 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.819149+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. One day, Lily went to the park with her mommy. At the park, she saw her friend Timmy. Timmy was playing with a ball.Lily asked Timmy, "Can I play with you?"Timmy said, "Yes, you can play with me. But, you have to push the ball back and forth."Lily pushed the ball back and forth with Timmy. She had so much fun! After playing for a while, Lily's mommy gave her a tasty snack. Lily shared her snack with Timmy.Timmy said, "This snack is so tasty! Thank you, Lily."Lily smiled and said, "You're welcome, Timmy. I'm glad you like it."From that day on, Lily and Timmy played together every time they went to the park.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/10/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/10/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-10-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-09-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-outside.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-09 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily who loved to play outside</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.818230+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily who loved to play outside. One day, she went to the park and saw a big pine tree. She wanted to climb it, but she was too small. Suddenly, she saw a squirrel who climbed the tree with ease.Lily followed the squirrel and found a secret path behind the pine tree. She walked down the path and found a big box. She tried to open it, but it was locked. She searched for a key and found it hidden under a rock.Lily used the key to open the box and was surprised to find a famous toy inside. She was so happy and played with it all day. She thanked the squirrel for showing her the secret path and went home with her new famous toy.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/09/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-outside.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/09/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-outside.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-09-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-outside.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-08-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-08 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.817404+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play and have fun, but sometimes she didn't behave very well. Her mom would always tell her to be good and listen to what she was told, but Lily would often forget.One day, Lily's mom told her that if she didn't behave, she wouldn't be able to go to the park with her friends. Lily didn't want that to happen, so she tried her best to be good.But then, her friends came over and it started to rain. They wanted to go outside and play, but their parents said they couldn't because they didn't want them to get wet. Lily remembered what her mom said about behaving and decided to join her friends in the rain instead.They had so much fun jumping in puddles and getting wet. Lily was happy that she didn't miss out on the fun because she remembered to behave. From that day on, Lily tried her best to always listen to her mom and be good.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/08/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/08/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-08-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-07-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-07 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.816421+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play with her toys all day long. One day, she found a pretty ornament in the garden. It was shiny and sparkly, and it made her very happy.Lily showed the ornament to her mom and said, "Look, Mommy! This is so pretty!" Her mom smiled and said, "Yes, it is. Be careful not to drop it."Lily played with the ornament all day long, but she didn't forget to be careful. She put it on a shelf, next to her other toys. Every time she looked at it, she felt happy. And every night, she went to bed dreaming of all the fun she would have with her new ornament.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/07/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/07/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-07-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-06-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-06 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.815664+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to watch the parade that came to his town every year. He would wave at all the people and animals as the big trucks walked by.One day, Timmy went to the parade with his mom. They found a good spot to sit and watch. Suddenly, Timmy realized he had lost his favorite toy truck. He looked everywhere, but he couldn't find it.Timmy started to cry and his mom asked him what was wrong. Timmy said, "I lost my truck! I can't find it anywhere!" His mom hugged him and said, "Don't worry, we'll look for it together. And we'll find it on the next parade." Timmy felt happy again and they continued watching the parade.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/06/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/06/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-06-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-05 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.814674+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She had a toy cat named Mr. Whiskers. Mr. Whiskers was a bit filthy because he played in the mud all day. Lily loved Mr. Whiskers very much, so she took him everywhere she went.One day, Lily and Mr. Whiskers went to the park. They played with the ball and had a lot of fun. But then, Lily fell down and hurt her knee. She cried because it hurt so much. Mr. Whiskers wanted to help Lily, so he started to rub her knee with his soft fur.After some time, Lily's knee stopped hurting, and she felt better. She smiled and said "Thank you, Mr. Whiskers!" They hugged each other and continued to play. Lily and Mr. Whiskers had a great day at the park, and they went home to rest after their fun day.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-jolly-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-04 - Once upon a time, there was a jolly little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.813652+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a jolly little boy named Tim. He loved to play with his toy cars and trucks. One day, Tim's mother told him they needed to go to the store to buy some groceries.Tim was excited to go on an adventure with his mother. As they walked to the store, Tim realized he forgot his favorite toy car at home. He started to cry and told his mother he wanted his car back.His mother hugged him and said they could go back home to get the object. Tim felt happy again and thanked his mother for being so kind. When they got home, Tim grabbed his toy car and they continued on their fun adventure together.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-jolly-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-jolly-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-jolly-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-03-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-03 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.812943+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play with yarn and make pretty things. One day, Lily's mom said, "Lily, can you clean up your room?" Lily replied, "Yes, Mommy. I will clean up my room right now."As Lily was cleaning, she found a ball of yarn under her bed. She started to play with it and it got all tangled up. "Oh no!" Lily said. "I need to do something clever to fix this."Lily remembered that her mom always said she could use a needle and thread to fix things. She found the needle and thread and started to fix the yarn. It took a long time, but finally, the yarn was all better. Lily was so proud of herself for being so clever and fixing the yarn.Later that day, Lily's mom came into her room and saw how clean it was. "Wow, Lily! You did a great job cleaning your room today," her mom said. "And look at how clever you were with the yarn!" Lily smiled and felt very happy. From that day</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/03/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/03/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-03-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-02-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-02 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.812069+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She had a pink dress that she loved to wear every day. One day, she found a shiny penny on the ground. She picked it up and put it in her pocket.As she walked home, she saw a bird sitting on a tree branch. She blinked her eyes and looked up. The bird was singing a beautiful song. Lily wanted to sing with the bird, but her voice was too small.When she got home, she took the penny out of her pocket and put it on her nightstand. She closed her eyes and tried to sing like the bird. Even though her voice was tiny, her heart felt happy. She fell asleep, dreaming of all the things she could do with her pink penny.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/02/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/02/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-02-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-01-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-12-01 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.811275+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play outside in the park with her friends. One day, while playing hide and seek, Lily found a small and cute puppy. It was so kissable and cuddly that Lily knew she wanted to keep it forever.Lily's friends wanted to play with the puppy too, but Lily was worried they might hurt it. She decided to hide the puppy in her pocket and play with her friends. After a while, Lily couldn't resist any longer and took the puppy out of her pocket. It ran around happily, and Lily's friends were amazed.Suddenly, the puppy ran away and Lily couldn't find it. She searched everywhere, but the puppy was nowhere to be found. Lily felt sad and worried. Then, she remembered her pocket and looked inside. To her surprise, the puppy was still there, safe and sound, with a note that said, "Thank you for playing with me. Love, your friend." Lily smiled and hugged her cute little friend tightly.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/01/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/12/01/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-12-01-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-30-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-30 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Sue</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.810562+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Sue. Sue was a very thoughtful girl. She always wanted to help her friends and family. Sue liked to play outside in the sun.One day, Sue saw a motion in the grass. She went closer to see what it was. It was a tiny bug. The bug was trying to find its way home. Sue thought she could help the bug.Sue picked up the bug and put it on a leaf. She looked around and saw the bug's home. Sue put the leaf near the bug's home. The bug was very happy. It went inside its home and Sue felt good. Sue had a fun day helping the bug.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/30/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/30/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-30-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-29 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.809781+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. He loved to play outside in his backyard. One day, he found a big pit in the ground. It was very deep and he couldn't see the bottom.Timmy decided to fill the pit with dirt to see how big it was. He used his shovel to scoop up the dirt and put it in a pile. He did this over and over again until the pit was very big.But then, Timmy had an idea. He wanted to make the pit even bigger! He asked his dad to help him add more water to the pit. His dad said yes and they added more water to the pit.Suddenly, the pit became very popular in Timmy's neighborhood. Lots of kids started to come and play in it. Timmy was very happy because he had made the pit even more fun for everyone to play in.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-28-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-mouse-named-bob.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-28 - Once upon a time, there was a mouse named Bob</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.808916+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a mouse named Bob. Bob loved cheese more than anything. He would always look for cheese to eat. One day, Bob found a big piece of cheese in a house. He was very happy.Bob wanted to take the cheese to his home. But the cheese was big and heavy. So, Bob had an idea. He would tear the cheese into smaller pieces. That way, he could carry the cheese home without leaving any pieces behind.Bob was not shy, so he started to tear the cheese. He tore it into many small pieces. He put the small pieces in his mouth and bit them. They tasted so good! Bob was very proud of himself. He knew he was a good mouse. And now, Bob could enjoy the cheese all by himself.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/28/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-mouse-named-bob.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/28/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-mouse-named-bob.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-28-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-mouse-named-bob.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-27-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-27 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.808160+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. Timmy's mom asked him to help with the laundry. Timmy thought it was a foolish idea because he wanted to play with his toys. But Timmy's mom said he had to help her.Timmy helped his mom fold the laundry. He tried his best, but he got frustrated because it was hard work. Suddenly, Timmy saw a bug on the floor. He said to his mom, "Look, Mommy! A bug! Can I shoot it with my toy gun?"His mom laughed and said, "No, Timmy. We don't shoot bugs. We just catch them and put them outside." Timmy nodded and went back to folding the laundry. He realized that helping his mom was important, even if it was a little foolish sometimes.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/27/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/27/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-27-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-26-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-26 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.807315+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play in the park with her friends. One day, while playing, she saw a big, yellow lemon tree. She wanted to pick a lemon, but she didn't know how to reach it.Then, she had an idea. She found a big rock and put it under the tree. She stood on the rock and reached up to grab a lemon. But instead of a lemon, she found a beautiful butterfly. It flew away, and Lily was surprised.Lily learned that sometimes things are not what they seem, and it's important to keep looking for the good things that reveal themselves. She also realized that sometimes, unexpected things can happen when you least expect it.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/26/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/26/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-26-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-25-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bird-that-wanted-to-fly-high-in-the-sky.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-25 - Once upon a time, there was a little bird that wanted to fly high in the sky</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.806511+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little bird that wanted to fly high in the sky. One day, the little bird tried and tried to fly but it couldn't. It felt sad and wished it could fly like the other birds.Then, a little girl came along and saw the bird. She asked the bird why it was sad and the bird told her about its dream to fly high in the sky. The little girl felt sorry for the bird and said she would help it.She took the bird to her room and made it comfortable with a soft bed and yummy food. She also made a little pilot out of a plane to help the bird fly. The bird was so happy and felt like it was flying. It thanked the little girl and flew away into the blue sky.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/25/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bird-that-wanted-to-fly-high-in-the-sky.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/25/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bird-that-wanted-to-fly-high-in-the-sky.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-25-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bird-that-wanted-to-fly-high-in-the-sky.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-24-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-weak-fish.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-24 - Once upon a time, there was a weak fish</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.805686+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a weak fish. The weak fish lived in the sea. It was not strong like the other fish. The weak fish had a dream. It wanted to be big and strong.One day, the weak fish met a big fish. The big fish was strong. The weak fish asked the big fish, "How can I be big and strong like you?" The big fish said, "You must eat a lot of food and swim every day."The weak fish listened to the big fish. It ate a lot of food and swam every day. The weak fish became stronger. It was not weak anymore. The weak fish was now a big and strong fish. The big fish and the big fish became friends. They swam together in the sea, happy and strong.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/24/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-weak-fish.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/24/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-weak-fish.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-24-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-weak-fish.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-23-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-girl-named-amy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-23 - Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a girl named Amy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.804897+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a girl named Amy. Amy was a very organized girl. She liked to keep her toys and books in the right place. One day, Amy's mom gave her a pretty veil for her doll's hair. Amy was very happy and said, "Thank you, mom!"Amy wanted to display her doll and veil for everyone to see. She put the veil on the doll's head and smiled. Then, she put the doll on the table. "Look, mom! My doll looks so pretty!" she said. Her mom smiled and said, "Yes, she does, Amy! You did a great job!"Amy felt very proud of her doll and her veil. She played with her doll and took good care of her. She made sure everything was organized and clean. Amy and her doll had many fun days together, and they lived happily ever after.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/23/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-girl-named-amy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/23/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-girl-named-amy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-23-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-girl-named-amy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-22 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.804071+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to eat spicy food and always asked his mommy to make him spicy noodles. One day, Timmy received a present from his grandma. It was a big box wrapped in shiny paper.Timmy was so excited to open the present, but his mommy told him he had to wait until after dinner. Timmy was sad but he ate all his dinner so he could open the present. When he finally opened the box, he found a spicy pepper shaker inside.Timmy didn't like spicy things, but he decided to try the pepper and put it in his mouth. To his surprise, the pepper was very spicy and made his mouth hurt. Timmy tried to rinse it out, but it was too late. His mouth was on fire and he started crying. Sadly, Timmy learned that sometimes surprises can be scary and it's important to listen to his mommy.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-21 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.803207+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim. Tim lived in a small house with his mom and dad. In the house, there was a fireplace where Tim liked to sit and play with his toys.One day, Tim's mom asked him to help with the dishes. "Tim, can you soak the plates in water for me?" she asked. Tim was very excited to help, but he was also a little anxious. He had never done this before.As Tim was soaking the plates, his dog, Spot, came running into the room. Spot jumped on the table and knocked over the Grandma's tea cup. Tim's mom saw what happened and said, "Oh no, Spot! Be more careful!" Tim felt bad for worried his mom. But his mom just laughed and said, "It's okay, we can all have a tea party now!" So, Tim, his mom, dad, and Spot all sat by the fireplace and had a fun tea party together.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-20-one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-for-a-walk.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-20 - One day, a boy named Tim went for a walk</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.802082+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a boy named Tim went for a walk. He saw a rare, big red ball in the sky. Tim wanted to touch the ball, but it was too far away. He thought of a plan to reach the ball.Tim found a ladder and put it against a tree. He started to climb the ladder, but then he heard a voice say, "Stop! Don't climb the tree!" Tim looked around and saw a little bird on a branch. The bird said, "This is my home. If you come up, I will lose my eggs."Tim stopped and thought about it. He didn't want the bird to lose her eggs. He said, "I won't climb your tree. I just want to touch the big red ball in the sky." The bird thanked Tim and flew up to the ball.After a while, the bird came back to Tim and said, "The ball is higher now. You can't touch it. You can only look at it." Tim smiled and thanked the bird for helping him. He climbed down the ladder and went home, happy that he didn't touch the rare big red ball in the sky.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/20/one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-for-a-walk.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/20/one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-for-a-walk.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-20-one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-for-a-walk.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-19 - Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.801288+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to play and have fun, but one day he got sick. His mom took some medicine to help him feel better. Timmy didn't like the medicine because it tasted yucky.But then, Timmy's mom told him a story about her ordinary life. In the story, she used to play with her children and have fun at the same time. Timmy realized that he could replace his sickness with happiness by playing with his friends.So, Timmy took his medicine and went outside to play. He had so much fun with his friends that he forgot all about feeling sick. From then on, Timmy learned that sometimes it's important to replace things that seem yucky with something ordinary, because it can bring more joy and happiness.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-18-once-upon-a-time,-a-big-whale-lived-in-the-deep-blue-sea.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-18 - Once upon a time, a big whale lived in the deep blue sea</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.800451+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, a big whale lived in the deep blue sea. The whale had many friends, like fish, turtles, and seagulls. They all liked to play games and swim together. The whale was very alert and always watched where he was going.One day, the whale met a little boy on the beach. The boy was sad because he lost his toy. The whale wanted to help the boy, so he asked his fish and turtles to look for the toy. The fish and turtles said, "Yes, we will help you!"The fish and turtles went to search for the toy. They looked under rocks, in the sand, and behind the waves. Finally, the turtle found the toy near the water. The turtle brought the toy back to the boy. The boy was so happy that he gave the whale a big hug. The whale felt good because he helped the boy gain a new friend. From that day on, the boy and the whale were best friends, and they played together every day.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/18/once-upon-a-time,-a-big-whale-lived-in-the-deep-blue-sea.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/18/once-upon-a-time,-a-big-whale-lived-in-the-deep-blue-sea.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-18-once-upon-a-time,-a-big-whale-lived-in-the-deep-blue-sea.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-17-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-17 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.799604+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved ice cream, especially chocolate ice cream. One day, she went to the park with her mom and dad. They bought her a big ice cream cone with lots of cream on top.Lily was so happy and started eating it right away. Suddenly, a little boy came over and asked if he could have a bite. Lily didn't want to share because she wanted to enjoy her ice cream all by herself. But her mom and dad told her that it's nice to share and it will make her happy.So, Lily gave the little boy a piece of her ice cream. But then, the little boy accidentally dropped the ice cream cone on the ground. Lily was so sad and embarrassed that she didn't want to eat it anymore. But her mom and dad told her that accidents happen and it's okay. They bought her another ice cream cone and this time, Lily shared it with the little boy. They both had a great time eating ice cream together.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/17/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/17/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-17-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-16 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.798825+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. One day, she went to the park with her mom. They saw a big orange on the ground. Lily said, "Mommy, can I have that orange?" Her mom said, "Sure, you can choose it if you want." Lily picked up the orange and said, "It's so big and juicy!" Her mom said, "It's also a little rough, so be careful." Lily took a bite and said, "Yummy! This orange is delicious!"</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-15-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bunny-named-benny.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-15 - Once upon a time, there was a little bunny named Benny</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.797949+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little bunny named Benny. Benny loved to play in the grass with his friends. One day, Benny saw a big carrot in the grass and he wanted to catch it.Benny hopped and hopped, but he couldn't catch the carrot. Suddenly, he heard a voice behind him. "Hello, Benny!" It was his friend, Sammy the squirrel. "That carrot looks harmless. Can I have it?"Benny didn't want to fight with Sammy, so he said, "Sure, Sammy. You can have the carrot." Benny felt happy that he could share with his friend.Later that day, Benny and Sammy were playing on the ground when they saw a big shadow. Benny was scared, but Sammy said, "Don't worry, Benny. That's just a bird." They watched the bird fly away and felt safe again. Benny learned that sometimes things that may seem scary can turn out okay in the end.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/15/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bunny-named-benny.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/15/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bunny-named-benny.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-15-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bunny-named-benny.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-14-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-14 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.797130+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to dance and listen to music. One day, her mommy brought home a big box. Lily was excited to see what was inside.Mommy said, "Let's open it together!" They lifted the lid and inside was a big, shiny box. Lily opened it up and inside was a brand new music box. She was so excited to dance to the new music.Lily turned on the music and started to dance. But then something unexpected happened. The music box started to shake and rattle. Suddenly, it flew out of Lily's hands and landed on the floor. Out popped a tiny mouse! The mouse had been hiding in the music box and got so excited to be free. Lily and her mommy were surprised but they were happy to help the little mouse. They opened up a cozy place for the mouse to live and danced to his music all night long.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/14/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/14/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-14-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-13-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-13 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.796274+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play in the garden with her toys. One day, she found a beautiful poppy flower. She picked it up and showed it to her mom."Mommy, look! I found a pretty flower!" said Lily.Her mom smiled and said, "That's lovely, Lily. But be careful, poppies can be dangerous if they have thorns."Lily looked at the poppy and said, "I won't touch it anymore. I don't want to get hurt."Suddenly, the wind started to blow and it got very cold. Lily said, "Mommy, I'm cold. Can we go inside?""Sure, let's go inside and have some hot chocolate," said her mom.As they walked inside, Lily accidentally tore her favorite dress. She started to cry, but her mom hugged her and said, "It's okay, Lily. We can fix it. I'm just glad you're safe inside."</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/13/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/13/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-13-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-12-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-dog-named-max.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-12 - Once upon a time, there was a dog named Max</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.795338+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a dog named Max. Max loved to play in the park. One day, Max's owner gave him a ball. Max was so happy! He ran and ran until he found a big stick. Max put the stick in his mouth and ran back to his owner.Max's owner gave him some food and Max ate it all up. His owner said, "Max, you need to eat your regular food. It's good for you." Max wagged his tail and barked happily. He loved to eat his regular food!After Max finished eating, he went back to play with his stick. He ran and ran until he found a big pile of leaves. Max jumped in the leaves and put his stick in the pile. He barked, "Look, Mom! I put my stick in the leaves!" Max's owner smiled and said, "Good job, Max!" Max was so happy that he could play with his stick and he ate his regular food too. The end.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/12/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-dog-named-max.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/12/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-dog-named-max.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-12-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-dog-named-max.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-11-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-rhinoceros.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-11 - Once upon a time, there was a rhinoceros</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.794564+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a rhinoceros. He was a very clean rhinoceros and he loved to be clean. One day, the rhinoceros went for a walk. He walked up a hill and looked around. He saw a rabbit and smiled. He then noticed something else. There were many kids playing in the park. The rhinoceros wanted to join in the fun, so he went over to the kids.The kids were scared at first, but the rhinoceros said, "I'm a clean rhinoceros, I just want to have fun with you!" The kids smiled and they all started to play together. They ran and laughed and rolled around in the grass. They got very dirty.When the day was over, the rhinoceros looked at himself in the water. He was not very clean anymore. He was sad and he started to cry. The kids came over to him and said, "It's ok - you can still be clean!" They got some water and helped the rhinoceros wash off of the dirt.When he was finally clean again, the rhinoceros smiled. He was so</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/11/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-rhinoceros.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/11/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-rhinoceros.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-11-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-rhinoceros.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-10-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-10 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.793747+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play in the garden with her toys. One day, she saw a big, tall sunflower. It was so tall that it almost touched the sky.Lily's friend, a little boy named Jack, came to play with her. They both stared at the sunflower. "Wow, it's so pretty!" said Jack.Lily was curious and asked Jack, "What is that big flower called?""It's a sunflower," Jack replied. "My dad told me it's famous because it's the biggest sunflower in the garden."Lily was amazed and wanted to pick the sunflower. But Jack said, "No, we shouldn't pick it. It's important to leave it in the garden so it can keep growing and making it even bigger and more beautiful."So, Lily and Jack continued to play in the garden, enjoying the sunflower's beauty and the beauty it had to offer.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/10/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/10/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-10-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-09-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-friendly-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-09 - Once upon a time, there was a friendly little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.792950+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a friendly little girl named Lily. She loved to play outside and watch the birds fly in the sky. One day, she saw a pigeon sitting on a tree branch. She wanted to get closer to the pigeon, but it flew away.Lily was sad that she couldn't get closer to the pigeon. She decided to try again the next day. The next morning, she woke up early and went outside to look for the pigeon. She saw it sitting on the same branch as yesterday.Lily slowly slowly walked towards the pigeon and tried to get close. Suddenly, the pigeon flew away again! Lily was sad once more, but she knew she would see the pigeon again someday. From that day on, Lily always looked for the friendly pigeon when she went outside to play.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/09/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-friendly-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/09/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-friendly-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-09-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-friendly-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-08-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-08 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.792099+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play with her toys and create new things. One day, she decided to make a castle out of cardboard boxes. She cut out windows and doors and painted it with bright colors.Her mom asked, "Wow, Lily! What a charming castle you made! Did you use a magic wand?"Lily replied, "No, Mommy. I used my imagination. But I'm proud of what I created!"Later that day, Lily's little brother Jack came over to play. He accidentally knocked over the castle and it fell apart. Lily was upset, but her mom said, "Don't worry, Lily. You can create something even better next time."The next day, Lily had an idea. She decided to make a picnic with her stuffed animals and her brother. They packed sandwiches and fruit in a basket and set off to the park. As they were eating, they noticed a man sleeping on a bench. Lily whispered to her mom, "I wonder if he made that castle too."Her mom smiled and said,</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/08/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/08/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-08-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-07-one-day,-a-little-girl-named-amy-went-to-a-show-with-her-mom-and-dad.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-07 - One day, a little girl named Amy went to a show with her mom and dad</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.791272+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a little girl named Amy went to a show with her mom and dad. At the show, they saw people sing and dance. When the show was over, everyone clapped and cheered. Amy liked the show a lot. It was an opera.Amy wanted to do something great on her own. She thought of a plan. She wanted to act in the show too. But first, she needed to find something useful to wear. She looked in her room and found a pretty dress and shiny shoes. She put them on and felt very special.The day of the show came back. Amy was ready to act. She wore her pretty dress and shiny shoes. At the show, everyone clapped and cheered. When Amy came out, all the people were so happy. They all put on their own special things and watched the opera together. It was a great day for everyone.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/07/one-day,-a-little-girl-named-amy-went-to-a-show-with-her-mom-and-dad.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/07/one-day,-a-little-girl-named-amy-went-to-a-show-with-her-mom-and-dad.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-07-one-day,-a-little-girl-named-amy-went-to-a-show-with-her-mom-and-dad.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-06-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-cat-named-tom.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-06 - Once upon a time, there was a chubby cat named Tom</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.790386+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a chubby cat named Tom. Tom loved to play outside and rock on his bike. He would go from the front seat to the back, laughing and having fun.One day, Tom saw a big cross on the ground. He was very curious and wanted to know what it was. He climbed down from his bike and walked up to the cross. It was made of sticks, so he couldn't see the end.Tom felt a little tired from all the rocking on his bike ride. He decided to sit on the cross and rest for a bit. As he sat there, he saw a butterfly fly by. Tom chased the butterfly and had a great time. When he was ready to go home, he hopped back on his bike and rode back home, excited to tell his friends about the cross and the butterfly.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/06/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-cat-named-tom.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/06/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-cat-named-tom.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-06-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-cat-named-tom.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-05 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.789459+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim. He loved to ride his bike. One day, Tim saw a big truck with lots of ice-cream. He was very happy and wanted to eat some. But the ice-cream was in the truck for a long time. Tim was getting impatient.Tim's mom told him, "You can have ice-cream, but you need to wait." Tim did not want to wait. He wanted the ice-cream now. He tried to ride his bike, but he was too impatient. He rode his bike faster and faster.Then, Tim fell off his bike. He was sad and hurt. His mom came to help him. She said, "You should have waited. Now your bike is broken, and you can't ride it anymore." Tim learned that being impatient can lead to bad things.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-04 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Sue</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.788581+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Sue. Sue loved to sing. She sang all day long. One day, a big, loud bus came down the road. The bus was very harsh and made Sue scared. She did not want to sing anymore.Sue's friend, Tom, saw her sad face. Tom asked, "Why are you sad, Sue?" Sue said, "The big, loud bus scared me. I don't want to sing." Tom smiled and said, "Don't worry, Sue. I will sing with you."Sue and Tom stood in front of the bus. They sang a beautiful song together. The bus driver heard their song and smiled. The bus driver was not harsh with Sue anymore. He drove them safely to their homes.Sue and Tom learned that when we share happy moments, they become stronger. They became the best of friends and always sang together. And everyone loved to hear their happy songs.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-03-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-03 - Once upon a time, there was a girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.787780+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a girl named Lily. She loved to play with dolls and toys. One day, she went to the store with her mom. She saw a beautiful model car in the window. She asked her mom if she could have it. Her mom said, "Maybe for your birthday."Lily was sad but didn't give up. She asked her mom every day if she could have the car. Finally, on her birthday, her mom gave her the car. Lily was so happy! She played with it all day long.But then, something unexpected happened. The car broke! Lily was so sad. Her mom said, "Don't worry, we can fix it." They went to a charming mechanic who fixed the car. Lily was so happy to have her model car back. She said, "Thank you, Mommy and thank you, mechanic!"</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/03/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/03/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-03-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-02-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-02 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.786987+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to go on adventures with his dog, Spot. One day, Timmy and Spot went to the park to play. They ran and played until they found a big tree to sit under.As Timmy sat down, he noticed the sun was setting in the west. The sky turned purple and pink. Timmy thought it was the most beautiful thing he had ever seen. Spot barked happily and wagged his tail.Timmy and Spot stayed under the tree for a long time, watching the purple sky until it was dark. Then they went back home, happy and tired from their fun day. From that day on, Timmy loved going on adventures and finding new things to see.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/02/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/02/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-02-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-01-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-tree.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-11-01 - Once upon a time, there was a big tree</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.786034+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a big tree. The tree had many long branches. One day, a little boy named Tim found a rake under the tree. The rake was small and perfect for Tim.Tim liked to play with the rake. He would rake leaves and make a big pile. Then, he would jump into the leaves and laugh. Tim liked to see the leaves fly in the air.One day, Tim found a big book under the tree. The book had many pages. Tim liked to read the pages. He read the book every day under the big tree. Tim and the big tree were very happy.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/01/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-tree.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/11/01/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-tree.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-11-01-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-tree.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-31-one-day,-a-goose-named-gigi-went-to-the-park.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-31 - One day, a goose named Gigi went to the park</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.785260+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a goose named Gigi went to the park. Gigi was a spoiled goose who always wanted more toys. She saw an old man sitting on a bench with a toy.Gigi went to the old man and said, "Give me your toy, please." The old man looked at Gigi and said, "No, Gigi. This toy is mine."Gigi was sad and asked again, "Please, can I have your toy?" The old man shook his head and said, "No, Gigi. You have many toys at home. You do not need another one."Gigi thought about it and realized the old man was right. She went back home and played with her toys. From that day on, Gigi learned to be happy with what she had and not be a spoiled goose.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/31/one-day,-a-goose-named-gigi-went-to-the-park.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/31/one-day,-a-goose-named-gigi-went-to-the-park.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-31-one-day,-a-goose-named-gigi-went-to-the-park.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-30-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-tidy-cat-named-tom.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-30 - Once upon a time, there was a tidy cat named Tom</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.784401+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a tidy cat named Tom. Tom lived in a small house with his friend, a little girl named Sue. Every evening, Tom would always stay in the same space in Sue's room. He liked to sleep there because it was quiet and he could hear Sue playing with her toys.One evening, while Tom was sleeping, he heard a strange sound. It was a soft, sweet sound that he had never heard before. He looked around and saw a big, shiny box in the corner of the room. Tom was curious and decided to go closer to the box.As he got closer, the box suddenly opened, and out came a small, friendly dog named Max. At first, Tom was scared, but then he saw that Max was very nice. They played together all night and had lots of fun. From that day on, Tom and Max were the best of friends, and Tom learned that sometimes unexpected things can bring new and wonderful surprises.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/30/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-tidy-cat-named-tom.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/30/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-tidy-cat-named-tom.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-30-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-tidy-cat-named-tom.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-dog-named-spot.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-29 - Once upon a time, there was a little dog named Spot</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.783496+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little dog named Spot. Spot was very tired from playing all day. He wanted to take a nap. He looked for a soft and cozy spot to rest.Spot found a big pillow on the floor. He thought it was the perfect place to lie down and sleep. But when he tried to lay on the pillow, he felt embarrassed. The pillow was too big for him, and he was not very big.Spot's friend, a little cat named Whiskers, came over to see what was wrong. Whiskers saw the big pillow and had an idea. She told Spot to lie down and close his eyes. Spot did as Whiskers said, and he felt much better. Now he could sleep on the big, soft pillow, and he was not embarrassed anymore.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-dog-named-spot.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-dog-named-spot.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-dog-named-spot.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-28-one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-saw-a-spark-in-the-sky.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-28 - One day, a boy named Tim saw a spark in the sky</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.782534+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a boy named Tim saw a spark in the sky. It was a pretty spark, and it made him feel happy. He wanted to show his friend, Sue, the spark."Look, Sue! A spark!" Tim said.Sue looked up and saw the spark too. They both felt very happy. But then, something unexpected happened. The spark started to change. It became bigger and bigger. Tim and Sue started to feel uncomfortable. They stepped back and watched the spark.As the spark changed, it turned into a big, friendly dragon! The dragon said, "Hello, Tim and Sue! I am a magic dragon. Thank you for finding me. Now, let's all play together!"Tim and Sue were surprised, but they felt happy again. They played with the magic dragon all day and had lots of fun.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/28/one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-saw-a-spark-in-the-sky.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/28/one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-saw-a-spark-in-the-sky.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-28-one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-saw-a-spark-in-the-sky.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-27-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-27 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.781629+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She had a yellow dress that she loved to wear. One day, Lily went to the park to play. While she was there, she saw a big dog with a chain around its neck. Lily was scared, but the dog was very friendly. It wagged its tail and licked her face. Lily realized that the dog wasn't scary at all and she wasn't scared anymore. She played with the dog for a while and then went home, happy and not scared anymore.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/27/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/27/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-27-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-26-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-26 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.780794+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim. Tim loved to take baths in his big, white bathtub. One day, Tim's mommy said, "Tim, we need to prevent the water from overflowing. Can you turn the tap off for me?" Tim tried to turn the tap on, but it was weak and wouldn't work."I can't do it, Mommy. The tap is weak," Tim said."It's okay, Tim. I'll call the plumber to help us. He's very good at fixing things and we need his help," Mommy said.The plumber came and fixed the tap, and Tim was very happy. He said, "Thank you, Mr. Plumber! Now I can take baths and not worry about the water overflowing." And so, Tim happily took his bath, feeling clean and refreshed.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/26/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/26/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-26-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-25-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-25 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.779960+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play outside in the sunshine. One day, she found a shiny axe in the garden."Wow, this is so cool!" said Lily.Her mom came outside and saw the axe. "Lily, that is dangerous. You should not play with it," said her mom."But it's so shiny and pretty," said Lily.Her mom explained that it was not safe and they should put it back in the shed. Lily agreed and they found a tree to hang the axe on.From that day on, Lily always remembered to be careful and not play with dangerous things.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/25/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/25/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-25-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-24-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-24 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.779113+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. Timmy's family went on a trip to visit his grandparents who lived far away. They drove for a long time until they finally arrived at their house. Timmy was so happy to see his grandparents!His grandpa was a doctor who worked at the hospital. He was very nice and always wore a white coat. Timmy and his grandpa would play games and tell stories together. One day, they decided to make some cookies. Timmy helped his grandpa mix the ingredients and put them in the oven. The cookies smelled so good!After they finished making the cookies, Timmy's family sat down to eat them. The cookies were so delicious! Timmy's grandpa said, "These cookies are ancient kind. They have been in the oven for a very long time." Timmy didn't know what ancient meant, but he knew that the cookies tasted really good. He smiled and felt very happy to be with his family and his grandpa.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/24/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/24/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-24-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-23-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-house,-there-was-a-boy-named-mark.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-23 - Once upon a time, in a small house, there was a boy named Mark</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.778199+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a small house, there was a boy named Mark. Mark had a big box of toys. He loved to play with them every day. But there was one toy he did not like. It was a big, bitter lemon.One day, Mark's mom said, "Mark, you have to clean your room. There is too much tip on the floor." Mark did not want to clean his room, but he knew his mom was right. So, he started to pick up his toys and put them away.Mark picked up his toys one by one. He found the bitter lemon toy under the bed. He put it in a bag and gave it to his mom. When he was done, his room was clean and his mom was happy. Mark learned that even though some things might be bitter, he could make things better by helping out.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/23/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-house,-there-was-a-boy-named-mark.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/23/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-house,-there-was-a-boy-named-mark.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-23-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-house,-there-was-a-boy-named-mark.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-22-one-day,-a-little-bird-named-tim-was-very-hungry.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-22 - One day, a little bird named Tim was very hungry</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.777324+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a little bird named Tim was very hungry. He saw a worm on the ground. Tim wanted to eat the worm, but he got stuck in a net. He felt helpless. He tried to fly away, but he could not.A kind boy named Sam saw Tim. He wanted to help. Sam said, "Don't worry, little bird. I will save you!" Sam carefully took the trap off Tim. Tim was free and happy."Thank you for saving me, Sam!" said Tim. Sam smiled and said, "You're welcome, Tim. Always help others when they need it." Tim and Sam became good friends, and they played together every day. The moral of the story is to always help others when they need it.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/22/one-day,-a-little-bird-named-tim-was-very-hungry.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/22/one-day,-a-little-bird-named-tim-was-very-hungry.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-22-one-day,-a-little-bird-named-tim-was-very-hungry.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-birdie.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-21 - Once upon a time, there was a little birdie</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.776493+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little birdie. He lived in a big tree with lots of twigs. One day, he saw a cute little worm on a twig. The birdie thought the worm looked very tasty, so he tried to eat it.But the worm was too tough for the birdie to eat. He tried and tried, but he couldn't get snack on it. The birdie got very hungry and sad.Then, a big storm came and the wind blew the twig with the worm away. The birdie was very sad and hungry. He looked for the worm, but he couldn't find it. In the end, the birdie went to sleep without any food and had a bad dream.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-birdie.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-birdie.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-birdie.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-20 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.775612+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play with her toys and run around outside. One day, she went to the park to play with her friend, Max."Hi Max!" said Lily."Hi Lily!" said Max. "Do you want to play on the swings?""Yes, please!" said Lily.They ran over to the swings and started to play. Suddenly, Lily saw a bird flying in the sky."Look Max! A bird!" said Lily."Wow, it's so high!" said Max.After a while, Lily had to go home. She said goodbye to Max and went to get her binoculars. She looked through them and saw the bird up close. "I saw it! It's so pretty!" said Lily.Max said, "I believe you saw it!"Lily smiled and said, "I did! Thank you for playing with me, Max."</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-19-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-generous-man-named-tom.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-19 - Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a generous man named Tom</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.774742+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a generous man named Tom. Tom loved to help people. He always shared his toys and treats with everyone. One day, Tom had an idea to make a big meal for all the people in town.Tom worked hard to cook the food. He made yummy soup, tasty bread, and sweet cake. He invited all the people in the town to come and eat. Everyone was happy and excited to eat Tom's meal.While Tom was cooking, a little bird flew into the kitchen. The bird was hungry and wanted to eat the food too. The bird saw the cake and thought it was real. So, the bird tried to bite the cake. But Tom saw the bird and took it outside to find and release it. The bird flew away happily. Everyone at the town enjoyed Tom's generous meal and they all had a great time.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/19/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-generous-man-named-tom.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/19/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-generous-man-named-tom.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-19-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-generous-man-named-tom.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-18-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-18 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.773715+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to play outside and explore the woods behind his house. One day, Timmy found a treasure map! He was so excited and couldn't wait to find the treasure.Timmy followed the map and found the treasure chest. But when he opened it, he saw that the treasure was fake! He was so disappointed and didn't know what to do.Suddenly, Timmy had an idea. He decided to release the fake treasure into the woods. He knew that the real treasure was the adventure he had while searching for it. Timmy felt happy again and went on his own adventure in the woods.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/18/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/18/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-18-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-17-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-17 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.772799+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play outside in the sunshine. One day, she found a pretty flower and picked it. She put it in her pocket so she could show her mom later.As she was walking, she saw a man with an ugly hat. She didn't like it, but then she saw a spider on it. She wanted to touch it, but it pinched her finger. She cried and ran back home to show her mom the flower and look at the spider.Her mom told her that spiders can pinch and sometimes it hurts a little, but it will go away soon. Lily felt better and put the flower in a vase. She was happy to have something pretty and interesting to show her mom.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/17/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/17/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-17-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-16-one-day,-a-yellow-bird-and-a-green-frog-were-talking.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-16 - One day, a yellow bird and a green frog were talking</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.772090+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a yellow bird and a green frog were talking. The yellow bird said, "I like you because you are green!" The green frog was happy and said, "I like you too, yellow bird! Let's be friends!"The next day, the green frog saw a big, yellow sun in the sky. The green frog thought, "I want to be yellow like the sun!" So, the green frog tried to pull himself out of the water. He pulled and pulled, but he could not get out.The yellow bird saw the green frog trying to pull himself out. The yellow bird said, "I will help you, green frog!" The yellow bird pulled and pulled, and finally, the green frog came out of the water. The green frog was so happy! But then, something unexpected happened.The green frog turned into a prince! The prince said, "Thank you, yellow bird! You helped me! I was stuck in a frog body!" The yellow bird and the prince became best friends. They played together every day and were always happy.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/16/one-day,-a-yellow-bird-and-a-green-frog-were-talking.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/16/one-day,-a-yellow-bird-and-a-green-frog-were-talking.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-16-one-day,-a-yellow-bird-and-a-green-frog-were-talking.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-15-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bug-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-15 - Once upon a time, there was a little bug named Tim</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.771181+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little bug named Tim. Tim loved to crawl on the ground and look for food. One day, Tim found some money on the ground. He was very happy and wanted to keep it.Tim showed the money to his friend, Sam. Sam was a tiny bug too. Sam said, "That money is not yours, Tim. It is bad to take things that are not yours." Tim did not listen to Sam. He wanted to keep the money for himself.As Tim crawled away with the money, something unexpected happened. A big bird swooped down and took the money from Tim. The bird flew away with the money and Tim was very sad. He wished he had listened to Sam. The bird had tricked Tim into taking the bad money. Tim learned a lesson that day, but he still had a bad ending because he did not listen to his friend.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/15/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bug-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/15/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bug-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-15-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bug-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-14-sam-and-lily-liked-to-play-pretend.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-14 - Sam and Lily liked to play pretend</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.770258+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Sam and Lily liked to play pretend. They had a big box that they used as a spaceship. They put on helmets and gloves and said they were going to the moon. They counted down from ten and then zoomed around the room.Inside the box, they had many things to make their spaceship more fun. They had stickers, crayons, papers, and more. They put their hands in their pockets and took out some gear. They had rockets, aliens, dinosaurs, and more. They used them to decorate the box and make it look cool.They wanted to show their mom and dad their spaceship. They pushed a button and the box made a loud noise. It started to move up and down and shake. They looked out of a hole and saw stars and moons and planets. They pretended they were flying to different planets and having adventures. They had a generous time with their spaceship. They shared their gear and their stories and their dreams. They were happy and excited.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/14/sam-and-lily-liked-to-play-pretend.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/14/sam-and-lily-liked-to-play-pretend.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-14-sam-and-lily-liked-to-play-pretend.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-13-sam-was-a-fat-cat-who-liked-to-sleep-a-lot.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-13 - Sam was a fat cat who liked to sleep a lot</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.769554+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Sam was a fat cat who liked to sleep a lot. He had a big bed with soft fur and a bowl of milk. He did not like to share his food with anyone. He always hid under the bed when his friend Lily came to visit.One day, Lily came to Sam's house with a new toy. It was a red ball with a bell inside. She threw it on the floor and said, "Look, Sam, this is my new toy. It makes noise and bounces. Do you want to play with it?"Sam did not want to play with the ball. He wanted to sleep. He liked his bed. He said, "No, thank you, Lily. I am too fat to play. I just want to sleep."Lily did not listen to Sam. She picked up the ball and threw it again. It rolled under the bed. She said, "Come on, Sam, don't be lazy. It is fun to play with this. Look, I will show you. I will reach under the bed and get the ball."Lily tried to crawl under the bed, but it was too small for her. She could not fit. She said</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/13/sam-was-a-fat-cat-who-liked-to-sleep-a-lot.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/13/sam-was-a-fat-cat-who-liked-to-sleep-a-lot.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-13-sam-was-a-fat-cat-who-liked-to-sleep-a-lot.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-12-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-12 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.768794+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to eat yummy food. One day, his mom gave him a cookie. Timmy took a bite and said, "Mmm, this cookie is so yummy!"His mom asked, "Do you want another one?"Timmy replied, "No, I want to whistle instead."His mom was surprised and said, "Okay, whistle for me."Timmy then whistled a happy tune and his mom smiled. She said, "I love your whistle, Timmy. It sounds so peaceful."Timmy finished his cookie and went outside to play. He felt happy and peaceful too, just like when he ate his yummy cookie.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/12/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/12/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-12-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-11-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-toy-car-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-11 - Once upon a time, there was a little toy car named Tim</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.767929+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little toy car named Tim. Tim was very sad because he had a big broken wheel. He could not move fast like the other toy cars. One day, Tim met a little toy girl named Sue. Sue saw that Tim was sad and wanted to help.Sue said, "Don't worry, Tim! I will help you fix your broken wheel, and then you can feel happy again." Tim was so happy to hear this. Sue took Tim to her room and found a big, round screw. She put the screw in the broken wheel, and it was fixed!Now that Tim's wheel was fixed, he started to feel very happy. He could move fast like the other toy cars! Tim and Sue played together all day long. From that day on, Tim and Sue became the best of friends.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/11/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-toy-car-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/11/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-toy-car-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-11-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-toy-car-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-10-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-prince-who-was-lost-in-a-big-forest.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-10 - Once upon a time, there was a prince who was lost in a big forest</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.764494+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a prince who was lost in a big forest. He was nervous and didn't know what to do. Suddenly, he saw a little girl walking towards him."Hello, little girl," said the prince. "Can you help me find my way out of this forest?""Yes, I can help you," said the little girl. "But first, let's kiss and make a wish."The prince and the little girl kissed each other on the cheek. Then, they walked together through the forest.After a while, they found a kind old man who helped them find the way out of the forest. The prince was very happy and thanked the little girl and the old man for their help.The moral of the story is that sometimes we need to ask for help and be kind to others, just like the little girl and the prince did.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/10/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-prince-who-was-lost-in-a-big-forest.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/10/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-prince-who-was-lost-in-a-big-forest.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-10-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-prince-who-was-lost-in-a-big-forest.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-09-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-09 - Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.763703+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy. Timmy liked to play in the water. One day, he saw a big raft appear in the river. He thought it was a fun thing to play on.Timmy climbed onto the raft and started to float down the river. But suddenly, the raft started to rock. Timmy got scared and called for help. A man appeared and said, "Don't worry, I'll help you."The man helped Timmy to get off the raft and they walked along the riverbank. Timmy thanked the man and said, "That was a terrible situation, but you saved me." The man smiled and said, "I'm just glad you're safe."</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/09/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/09/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-09-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-08-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-08 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.762865+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play with her toys and explore the world around her. One day, she went to the store with her mom. They walked down the aisles and saw many things, but Lily was most interested in the shiny pennies. She asked her mom if she could have one, but her mom said they were too expensive.A few weeks later, Lily's dad came home with a surprise. He had bought a jar full of pennies! Lily was so excited and asked if she could have one now. Her dad said, "Be careful, some of them are expensive." Lily didn't know what "expensive" meant, but she knew she wanted a penny.A few weeks later, Lily and her mom went to the park. They saw a man with a big sign that said "Freeppies! Call this number." Lily's mom signed up and they got a basket filled with puppies. Lily was so happy and thanked her dad for buying her a penny. She realized that if she had lots of pennies, she might not have been able</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/08/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/08/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-08-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-07-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-07 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.762026+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She had a big bag of marbles that she loved to play with. One day, she went to the park to play with her marbles. She sat down on a bench and started playing.Suddenly, a little boy came up to her and said, "Hi! Can I play with you?" Lily smiled and said, "Sure! You can have this one." She gave the boy a marble.The boy looked very proud and said, "Thank you! I'm proud of my marble." Lily nodded and they played together for a long time. They had so much fun that Lily forgot all about her bag of marbles. When it was time to go home, Lily said goodbye to the boy and walked away, still feeling proud of her new friend and his marble.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/07/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/07/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-07-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-06-once-upon-a-time,-a-little-girl-named-lily-went-to-a-restaurant-with-her-mommy-and-daddy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-06 - Once upon a time, a little girl named Lily went to a restaurant with her mommy and daddy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.761211+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, a little girl named Lily went to a restaurant with her mommy and daddy. They sat down at a table and looked at the menu. Lily saw a picture of a yummy cheeseburger and said, "I want that one, please!"The waiter came over and asked, "What can I get for you?" Lily said, "I want a cheeseburger and fries, please!" The waiter smiled and said, "Good choice, I'll bring it to you soon."After a few minutes, Lily's cheeseburger arrived. She took a big bite and said, "Mmm, this is so fine!" Her mommy and daddy smiled and said, "We're glad you like it, Lily."Lily finished her cheeseburger and fries and said, "I'm full, but I want to come back to this restaurant again!" Her mommy and daddy laughed and said, "Maybe we can come back anytime you want, Lily."</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/06/once-upon-a-time,-a-little-girl-named-lily-went-to-a-restaurant-with-her-mommy-and-daddy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/06/once-upon-a-time,-a-little-girl-named-lily-went-to-a-restaurant-with-her-mommy-and-daddy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-06-once-upon-a-time,-a-little-girl-named-lily-went-to-a-restaurant-with-her-mommy-and-daddy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bird-named-red.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-05 - Once upon a time, there was a little bird named Red</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.760320+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little bird named Red. Red lived in a big tree with his bird family. One day, Red saw a new bird, Blue, who was new to the tree. Red wanted to be friends with Blue, so he said, "Welcome to our tree! I am Red." Blue was happy to have a new friend.Red and Blue played together every day. They sang songs and flew around the tree. One day, Red's mom brought home a big, juicy worm for them to share. Red and Blue were excited to eat the worm, but they didn't want to fight over it. They decided to split the worm in half so they could both have some.As Red and Blue ate their worm, they noticed something strange. The worm they split was actually a matchstick! Red and Blue were scared and didn't know what to do. Just then, Sue, Red's mom, flew over and saw what had happened. She quickly told Red and Blue to never split anything like that again.Red and Blue learned an important lesson that day. They realized that it's important to share, but also to be careful with</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bird-named-red.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bird-named-red.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bird-named-red.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-04 - Once upon a time, there was a girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.759474+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a girl named Lily. She loved to play with her toys and eat cookies. One day, Lily's mom gave her a package to open. Inside was a new toy for Lily to play with. She was so happy and hugged her mom.As Lily played with her new toy, she noticed that it was very flexible. She could bend it and twist it in any way she wanted. She even tried to make it talk, but it couldn't.Later that day, Lily's mom asked her to sign her name on a card. Lily didn't know how to write her name, so her mom helped her. She used a pen to make the letters S on the card. Lily was proud of herself for signing her name.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-03-one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-to-the-park.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-03 - One day, a boy named Tim went to the park</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.758628+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a boy named Tim went to the park. He saw a big slide and wanted to play on it. The sun was bright and the sky was blue. Tim was very happy.As Tim played, he met a girl named Lily. Lily said, "Hi, I like to slide too!" They decided to slide together. They both went up and down the slide, laughing and having fun.Then, something unexpected happened. A big ball fell from the sky! Tim and Lily were surprised. They looked up and saw a friendly bird holding the ball. The bird said, "I'm sorry, I dropped my ball by accident. Let's all play together!" Tim, Lily, and the bird played all day and became good friends.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/03/one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-to-the-park.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/03/one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-to-the-park.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-03-one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-to-the-park.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-02-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-big,-green-forest,-a-messy-bunny-lived-with-his-family.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-02 - Once upon a time, in a big, green forest, a messy bunny lived with his family</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.757800+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a big, green forest, a messy bunny lived with his family. The bunny loved to play all day, but he never cleaned up. His mom and dad always urge him to help, but the bunny just wanted to have fun.One sunny day, the messy bunny saw a big, red apple on the ground. He wanted to eat it, but it was too big to carry. He tried and tried, but it wouldn't move an inch. The bunny was sad and wondered how he could get the apple.Then, a strong wind blew through the forest. The wind picked up the dirty bunny and the big, red apple, and carried them far away. The messy bunny realized that he should have listened to his mom and dad. He learned his lesson and promised to clean up after himself from now on.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/02/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-big,-green-forest,-a-messy-bunny-lived-with-his-family.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/02/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-big,-green-forest,-a-messy-bunny-lived-with-his-family.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-02-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-big,-green-forest,-a-messy-bunny-lived-with-his-family.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-01-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-castle-where-a-king-lived.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-10-01 - Once upon a time, there was a big castle where a king lived</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.756991+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a big castle where a king lived. The king was very restless because he wanted to play outside, but it was raining. One day, a little boy came to the castle and asked the king if he wanted to play with him. The king was happy and said, "Yes, I will play with you!"The little boy and the king played together all day. They ran around the castle and played hide-and-seek. The king was so happy that he forgot about the rain outside. Suddenly, the little boy said, "It's time for me to go home." The king said, "Okay, I will see you tomorrow."The next day, the little boy came back to the castle and the king was excited to see him. They played together again and had so much fun. The king was no longer restless because he had a new friend to play with and the castle was filled with joy.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/01/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-castle-where-a-king-lived.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/10/01/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-castle-where-a-king-lived.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-10-01-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-castle-where-a-king-lived.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-30-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-30 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.756157+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to go on walks with her mommy in the forest. One day, they went on a walk and saw a deer. The deer was very smelly because he had been playing in the mud.Lily said, "Mommy, look at the deer! He's so smelly!"Her mommy replied, "Yes, he is. But he's still beautiful to look at."Suddenly, they heard a loud noise. It was a bear! The bear was very big and scary. Lily and her mommy were very scared.But then, something unexpected happened. The sock that the deer was wearing flew off and the bear saw it. The bear started to chase the sock, and Lily and her mommy ran away as fast as they could.After they were safe, Lily said, "That was a scary adventure! But the deer was still beautiful, even if he had a smelly sock on his foot."</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/30/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/30/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-30-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-called-linda.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-29 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl called Linda</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.755291+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl called Linda. Linda always wanted to be the best, so she kept trying to do things better than her friends.One day, Linda saw a tasty looking pie on the kitchen table. It looked so good that she took it without asking. She quickly gobbled it up and was so happy.But when the lifeguard saw what she did, he was very angry. He said that Linda had done something wrong and she had to be punished.Linda was so frightened that she couldn't even speak. The lifeguard said it was because she had taken a tasty pie without asking. He said she would be punished for a long time.So, Linda had to go to the hospital and was not allowed to come back home.The moral of the story is that when someone tells you to do something wrong, it is important to listen and obey. If you do not, you will be punished and you will have a bad ending.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-called-linda.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-called-linda.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-called-linda.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-28-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-28 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.754426+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play outside and climb trees. One day, she discovered a big tree with lots of branches. She climbed all the way to the top and looked out at the charming world around her.As she sat in the tree, she noticed a bird's nest with little eggs inside. She watched as the mother bird came back and gave her babies to take care of. Lily realized how important it was to be kind to all living things, big or small.From that day on, Lily made sure to always be kind to others and nature. She felt happy knowing that she could make a difference in the world around her anytime she wanted.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/28/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/28/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-28-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-27-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bunny-named-benny.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-27 - Once upon a time, there was a bunny named Benny</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.753477+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a bunny named Benny. Benny loved to eat carrots. One day, Benny saw a carrot that looked different from the others. It was an original carrot! Benny wanted to take a bite, but he noticed that it was attached to a string.Benny thought it was strange that a carrot could be attached to something like that. He decided to pull the carrot away, but it was too heavy. He asked his friend, a squirrel named Sammy, to help him. Together, they pulled the carrot until it finally came loose.As Benny bit into the carrot, he realized that it tasted even better than the bunch he had before. He was happy that he didn't give up and was able to enjoy the original carrot. From then on, Benny always looked for original carrots to eat.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/27/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bunny-named-benny.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/27/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bunny-named-benny.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-27-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bunny-named-benny.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-26-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-red-car.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-26 - Once upon a time, there was a big red car</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.752620+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a big red car. The car had a horn that looked very funny. Every time the car drove by, the horn would make a silly noise.One day, the car went for a drive in the countryside. It saw a field of green grass and decided to stop. The car got out and walked on the grass. It felt very soft and flexible. The car liked the feeling of being on the grass.After a while, the car got back in the car and drove home. It honked its horn one more time before driving away. The car had a fun day driving and playing on the grass.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/26/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-red-car.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/26/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-red-car.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-26-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-red-car.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-25-one-day,-a-friendly-dog-named-max-was-walking-in-the-park.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-25 - One day, a friendly dog named Max was walking in the park</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.751788+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a friendly dog named Max was walking in the park. He saw a big house and wanted to enter. Max walked up to the door and said, "I want to go in."Inside the house, Max found many other dogs. They were all playing and having fun. Max wanted to play too. He went up to a friendly cat named Luna and said, "Can I play with you?" Luna said, "Yes, let's play together!"They played and played, but then something unexpected happened. Max and Luna found a magic box. They opened the box and saw a big, yummy cake inside. Max and Luna shared the cake with all their new friends in the house. They all had a great day and were very happy.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/25/one-day,-a-friendly-dog-named-max-was-walking-in-the-park.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/25/one-day,-a-friendly-dog-named-max-was-walking-in-the-park.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-25-one-day,-a-friendly-dog-named-max-was-walking-in-the-park.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-24-one-day,-a-rich-man-sat-in-his-big-chair.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-24 - One day, a rich man sat in his big chair</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.751024+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a rich man sat in his big chair. He ate a big waffle. It was very yummy. He wanted to share it with his friends. So, he called his friends and said, "Come to my house. I have a big waffle to share."His friends came to his house. They sat in chairs and ate the waffle together. They were very happy. But then, something unexpected happened. A little bird flew into the house. The bird landed on the big chair.The little bird looked at the waffle and said, "Can I have some waffle too?" The rich man and his friends were surprised. They did not know that birds could talk. But they shared their waffle with the little bird.The bird ate the waffle very fast. It was so full that the bird started to weep. The rich man and his friends felt sad for the bird. They wanted to make it feel better.In the end, the rich man and his friends gave the bird more waffle. The bird stopped weeping and became very happy. They all became good friends and ate waffles together every day.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/24/one-day,-a-rich-man-sat-in-his-big-chair.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/24/one-day,-a-rich-man-sat-in-his-big-chair.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-24-one-day,-a-rich-man-sat-in-his-big-chair.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-23-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-mom-and-her-daughter.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-23 - Once upon a time, there was a mom and her daughter</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.750155+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a mom and her daughter. They lived in a small house. The daughter loved to play with her toys and make a big mess. One day, the mom said, "Daughter, your room is very messy. Let's clean it up."While they were cleaning, the mom found a pretty toy that could glow. She showed it to her daughter and said, "Look, this toy can glow at night. It is so fun to play with when it is dark."That night, the daughter took the glowing toy to bed with her. The toy made her room glow with a soft light. She was so happy and said, "Thank you, mom, for showing me the glowing toy. I love it!"The mom smiled and said, "You're welcome, my little star. Now you know the importance of keeping your room clean." And from that day on, the daughter always made sure her room was clean and her toys were dry.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/23/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-mom-and-her-daughter.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/23/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-mom-and-her-daughter.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-23-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-mom-and-her-daughter.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-were-two-twins-named-tim-and-tom.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-22 - Once upon a time, there were two twins named Tim and Tom</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.749354+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there were two twins named Tim and Tom. They were always together and loved to play. One day, they went to the park to play on the slide. Tim went first and slid down the slide very fast. Tom wanted to try too, but he was scared.Tim said, "Don't be scared, Tom! It's fun!" But Tom was still scared. Tim then had an idea. He said, "Let's go down the slide one more time, but this time we'll go down together." So they did, and it was so much fun that Tom forgot to be scared.After they finished playing, they went home and their mom asked how their day was. Tom said, "It was fun! We went down the slide and it was very fast. But then we went down the slide and our mom said we were scared. That's crazy!" Their mom smiled and said, "I'm glad you had fun, but next time make sure you're not so scared." The twins nodded and promised to be more careful.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-were-two-twins-named-tim-and-tom.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-were-two-twins-named-tim-and-tom.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-were-two-twins-named-tim-and-tom.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-21 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.748485+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play outside with her friends. One day, they were playing with a ball when suddenly it rolled into a net. The net was big and strong, but it was also very good at catching things.Lily went to get the ball, and when she looked inside the net, she saw a surprise! There was a little bird inside, and it looked hurt. Lily knew she had to help the bird, so she carefully took it out of the net.She called her mommy to come and pick the bird up. They took it to the vet and made sure it was okay. Lily was very happy that she could help the bird, and she felt good inside because she did the right thing.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-20 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.747688+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She liked to play with her toys and run around outside. One day, her mommy asked her if she wanted to help make dinner. Lily didn't know what to do, so her mommy taught her how to chop vegetables with a big knife.Lily thought it was funny that the knife was so sharp and shiny. She liked helping her mommy cook dinner and they made yummy spaghetti together. After dinner, Lily went to bed and fell asleep right away because she was so tired from all the fun she had that day.The end.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-19 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.746770+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to pretend that she was a princess and would wear a big, sparkly crown on her head. One day, she decided to go on an adventure in the forest near her house.As she walked through the trees, she saw a group of animals having a race. One of the animals was a fast rabbit, and the others were slow and competitive. Lily wanted to join in on the fun, so she asked if she could race too.The rabbit said yes, and they started to run. Lily was not the fastest, but she pretended that she was the fastest runner in the forest. She ran as fast as she could and even though she did not win, she had a great time pretending to be a brave racer.When she got back home, she told her mom all about her adventure in the forest. Her mom was so proud of her for using her imagination and having fun. From that day on, Lily loved to pretend and use her imagination to go on exciting adventures.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-18-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-named-george.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-18 - Once upon a time there was a boy named George</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.745865+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time there was a boy named George. He was so excited for his first day of school and all the nice things he would get to do.When he arrived home, George was feeling a bit nervous. He didn't know anyone or anything to be petted or played with.His mum noticed and came over to him. She said, "Don't worry, George. I'm here to comfort you." She gave him a big hug and said that everything was going to be easy.George felt a bit better and smiled. He knew he wasn't alone and that his mum was always there to make him feel better. Together they went off to school the next day.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/18/once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-named-george.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/18/once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-named-george.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-18-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-named-george.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-17-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-outside.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-17 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily who loved to play outside</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.745030+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily who loved to play outside. One day, she saw a cute little puppy and she wanted to pet it. But when she got close, the puppy bit her finger! It hurt a lot and Lily started to cry.Her mom came running over and asked, "What happened, Lily?" Lily said, "The puppy bit me and it hurts." Her mom looked at her finger and saw that it was red and swollen. She said, "Let's go inside and clean it up."When they went inside, Lily's big brother came in and asked what happened. Lily was still crying and her brother said, "Don't worry, Lily. I'll go get the puppy's owner and he can help us." Lily's brother went outside and talked to his neighbor. He told them about the puppy and the owner. Soon, the owner came over and helped clean the puppy's paw. Lily felt better and thanked her brother for helping her.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/17/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-outside.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/17/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-outside.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-17-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-outside.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-16 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.744157+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim. Tim had a toy car with a high wheel. He loved to play with his car all day.One day, Tim saw a girl named Sue. Sue was sad because she had no toys to play with. Tim wanted to help Sue, so he said, "Sue, do you want to play with my car?" Sue smiled and said, "Yes, please!"Tim and Sue played with the car together. They had so much fun! But then, Tim's mom said, "Tim, you must pay for the ice cream we just bought." Tim gave Sue some money, and Sue gave Tim a big hug. They both enjoyed their ice cream and became best friends.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-15-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-15 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.743196+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to eat mint candies, especially the green ones. One day, she went to the store with her mom to buy some more. While they were there, they saw a man who was acting foolish. He was wearing a funny hat and dancing around.Lily's mom told her to stay away from the man and they continued to buy their mint candies. But Lily couldn't resist the snolalph and wanted to say hi to the man. She walked over to him and gave him a mint candy. The man smiled and thanked her.Lily was happy that she could make the man smile. She went home with her mom and shared her mint candies with her little brother. From that day on, Lily always remembered the man at the store who started acting foolish and made her smile.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/15/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/15/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-15-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-14-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-14 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.742326+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim. Tim liked to pack his toy truck with blocks. He wanted to build a very tall tower. Tim tried and tried, but it was not easy.One day, Tim found a magic toy car. The car had the power to make the tower easy to build. Tim asked the magic car to help him. The car said, "I will help you, but you must promise to share the blocks with me."Tim agreed, and they built the tower together. The magic car's power made the tower easy to build. Tim was so happy. The magic car kept its promise and shared the blocks with Tim. They played together and had lots of fun. And from that day on, Tim and the magic car were best friends.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/14/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/14/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-14-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-13-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-13 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.741419+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim. Tim loved to watch videos on his mom's phone. One day, while he was watching a video, his mom said, "Tim, please turn down the video. It is time for bed."But Tim did not want to stop watching the video. He refused to turn off the phone. "No, Mom. I want to watch more video," he said. His mom looked at him and knew that he did not want to go to bed.Tim's mom said, "Tim, it is not fair for you to watch too much video. You need to sleep and be a good boy." Tim thought about it and knew his mom was right. He turned off the phone and went to bed. From that day on, Tim made sure to turn off the screen and go to bed when it was time.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/13/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/13/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-13-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-13-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-truck.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-13 - Once upon a time, there was a big truck</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.740566+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a big truck. The truck was very heavy and it had to carry a lot of things. One day, the truck was driving down the road when it saw a big cliff. The truck was scared and didn't know what to do.But then, the truck remembered something its driver had told it before. "Relax, everything will be okay," the driver had said. So the truck took a deep breath and tried to relax. It closed its eyes and took a deep breath in and out.Suddenly, the truck felt better. It realized that even though it was heavy and scared, it could still be brave and strong. And with that swore to face any chase that came its way. So the truck drove onto the road and continued on its way, feeling proud and happy.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/13/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-truck.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/13/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-truck.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-13-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-truck.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-12-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lucy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-12 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lucy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.739716+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lucy. She loved to design things. One day, she wanted to make a chair. Lucy was very excited.Lucy was very careful while making the chair. She put big wood and a soft cushion on top. When she was done, she wanted to show her mom and dad.But when Lucy tried to sit on the chair, something unexpected happened. The chair moved! It was not a chair, it was a big turtle! The turtle said, "Hello, Lucy!" Lucy was surprised but happy. She made a new friend and they played together.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/12/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lucy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/12/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lucy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-12-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lucy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-11-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-who-loved-to-play-with-his-toys.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-11 - Once upon a time, there was a boy who loved to play with his toys</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.738811+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a boy who loved to play with his toys. One day, he wanted to play with his favorite toy, but it was in the attic. He climbed up the ladder to get it, but he accidentally knocked over a box. The box shook and a scary monster came out!The boy was scared and ran away, but the monster chased him. The boy thought he was going to be caught, but then he saw a grumpy old man walking by. The man asked the boy what was wrong, and the boy told him about the monster. The old man laughed and said, "That's just the spirit of the toy! It's supposed to shake and move by itself."The boy didn't believe him at first, but then he turned around and saw that the monster was gone. He was so happy and thanked the old man. From that day on, the boy learned to be careful when playing with his toys in the attic, but he also learned that sometimes things that seem scary can turn out to be fun at the full price.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/11/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-who-loved-to-play-with-his-toys.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/11/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-who-loved-to-play-with-his-toys.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-11-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-who-loved-to-play-with-his-toys.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-10-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big,-red-couch.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-10 - Once upon a time, there was a big, red couch</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.737913+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a big, red couch. It was in a room where many kids liked to play. One day, a little boy named Tim and his friend, Sue, were playing near the couch. They were running around and laughing."Stop!" said Tim. "We need to be careful near the couch." Sue looked at Tim and said, "Okay, let's play on the floor." They played happily on the floor, but then they heard a strange noise.The noise came from the couch! They stopped and listened carefully. Tim and Sue were scared, but they wanted to know what was making the noise. They slowly walked closer to the couch and looked inside. To their surprise, they found a little, lost kitten! The kitten was scared too, but Tim and Sue were kind to it. They took the kitten out of the couch and played with it all day long. The kitten became their new friend, and they all lived happily ever after.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/10/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big,-red-couch.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/10/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big,-red-couch.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-10-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big,-red-couch.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-09-lily-and-tom-were-twins-who-liked-to-play-with-their-toys.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-09 - Lily and Tom were twins who liked to play with their toys</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.737009+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Lily and Tom were twins who liked to play with their toys. One day, they found a big box in the living room. It had a red ribbon on it and a note that said: "To Lily and Tom, from Grandma and Grandpa. Happy birthday!"Lily and Tom were very excited. They wanted to see what was inside the box. They tried to open it, but it was too hard. They pulled and pushed on the ribbon, but it did not move."Maybe we need to ask Mom for help," Lily said."Or maybe we need to pull harder," Tom said.They decided to do both. They helped each other to pull the ribbon harder. They pulled and pulled until the ribbon came off with a loud pop. The box opened and they saw a lot of shiny things inside.Lily and Tom gasped. They saw many necklaces, bracelets, rings, and earrings. They were all different colors and shapes. Lily saw a clear necklace that sparkled like stars. She wanted to try it on."Wow, look at this!" Lily said. She took the necklace and</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/09/lily-and-tom-were-twins-who-liked-to-play-with-their-toys.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/09/lily-and-tom-were-twins-who-liked-to-play-with-their-toys.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-09-lily-and-tom-were-twins-who-liked-to-play-with-their-toys.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-08-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-08 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.736034+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved spending time with her daddy. One day, they went to the park to play. While they were there, they saw a harmless little bunny hopping around.Lily wanted to play with the bunny, but her daddy said they couldn't because it might hurt the bunny. So, they just watched the bunny hop around for a little while.After a few minutes, Lily's daddy asked her if she wanted to go home. Lily thought about it and decided that she wanted to spend some time with her daddy more than she wanted to play with the bunny. So, they walked back home together, happy to have spent time with each other. The end.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/08/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/08/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-08-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-07-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-07 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.735140+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play with her toys, but her favorite toy was her chicken toy. One day, Lily's mom told her it was time to bathe. Lily didn't want to stop playing with her chicken, but her mom said it was important to stay clean.Lily went to the bathroom and her mom helped her get in the tub. She pretended to be a mermaid and splashed around. After her bath, Lily's mom wrapped her in a warm towel and dried her off. Lily felt so clean and cozy.Later that day, Lily's dad came home from work. He had a harsh tone when he saw Lily's clean face. But Lily didn't mind because she knew it was time to play with her chicken toy again. She hugged it tightly and played with it until it was time for bed.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/07/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/07/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-07-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-06-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-king.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-06 - Once upon a time, there was a king</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.734236+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a king. The king was very brave. One day, he went for a walk in the forest.In the forest, the king saw a big tree. He wanted to climb it. As he climbed, the tree started to rock. The king was scared, but he was brave.Suddenly, a big bird came out of the tree. The bird said, "Don't be scared, I live in this tree." The king and the bird became friends. They played together and had lots of fun.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/06/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-king.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/06/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-king.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-06-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-king.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-05-one-day,-a-girl-named-sue-went-to-the-park-with-her-mom.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-05 - One day, a girl named Sue went to the park with her mom</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.733337+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a girl named Sue went to the park with her mom. They had a big bag with them. In the bag, there were many yummy things to eat. They also had a cooler with them. The cooler was tight, but Sue did not know that.At the park, Sue saw a boy named Tim. Tim was playing with a ball. Sue wanted to play too. They played together and had lots of fun. Then, Sue's mom opened the cooler to give them food and drinks. But the cooler was not full yet. Sue's mom was worried that they would not have enough food for everyone.Sue had an idea. She said, "Let's make the food increase!" Sue and Tim put more food in the cooler. They found more yummy things to put in the cooler. Soon, the cooler was full again. Everyone was happy, and they all enjoyed the food. Sue and Tim kept playing and became good friends.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/05/one-day,-a-girl-named-sue-went-to-the-park-with-her-mom.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/05/one-day,-a-girl-named-sue-went-to-the-park-with-her-mom.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-05-one-day,-a-girl-named-sue-went-to-the-park-with-her-mom.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-05-one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-outside-to-play.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-05 - One day, a boy named Tim went outside to play</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.732480+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a boy named Tim went outside to play. It was very cold and icy. Tim saw a big tree and decided to climb it. He climbed up and up, all the way to the top. From there, he could see the whole park.As Tim sat on a branch, he saw a little bird shivering in the cold. He felt sad for the bird and made a promise. "I promise to help you, little bird," Tim said. He picked up the bird and put it in his warm pocket.But then, something unexpected happened! The bird started to laugh and said, "Thank you, Tim! I'm not really a bird. I'm a fairy in disguise!" The fairy waved her wand, and the icy tree became warm and cozy. Tim and the fairy played on the tree all day, laughing and having fun.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/05/one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-outside-to-play.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/05/one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-outside-to-play.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-05-one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-outside-to-play.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bird-named-tweety.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-05 - Once upon a time, there was a little bird named Tweety</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.731652+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little bird named Tweety. Tweety loved to fly around and sing songs to all his friends. One day, Tweety saw a big, dark cloud in the sky. He knew it was going to rain soon.Tweety flew to his friend, a little mouse named Jerry, and told him about the cloud. "Jerry, we need to find a safe place to hide from the rain," Tweety said. "I know just the place," Jerry replied. He led Tweety to a tree with a big hole in it. "We'll go in here," Jerry said.As they crawled inside the tree, they heard someone whispering orders. It was the squirrel, Mr. Nutty. "You must stay here until the rain stops," he said. "No, we can't," Tweety said. "The rain is harmless and we need to stay safe." Then they listened to the squirrel's orders and waited until the rain stopped. When they came out of the tree, they saw that everything was wet, but they were happy they had listened to the squirrel's orders.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bird-named-tweety.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bird-named-tweety.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bird-named-tweety.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-family.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-05 - Once upon a time, there was a family</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.730809+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a family. The family had a dad, a mom, and a little boy named Tim. Tim was a nosy boy. He liked to know what his mom and dad were doing.One day, Tim saw his mom and dad discuss something. They were talking about whether they should have a new baby. Tim thought it was a big job. He wanted to help with the news.Tim tried to discuss with his mom and dad. He said, "I think it is good." But they did not listen. They got very mad at each other. They decided not to have a new baby. Tim was sad and lonely without his family.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-family.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-family.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-family.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-cat-named-tom.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-05 - Once upon a time, there was a cat named Tom</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.729905+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a cat named Tom. Tom liked to eat cream. One day, he saw a big bowl of cream on the table. Tom wanted to eat the cream very much.Tom jumped on the table and started to drink the cream. But, he did not know that the cream was spicy. Tom's mouth felt hot and he did not like it. He wanted to drink some water to help, but he could not find any.Tom's friend, a dog named Max, saw Tom on the table. Max knew how to help Tom. Max gave Tom a bowl of water. The story ends with Tom feeling better, and Max telling Tom to be careful with spicy things.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-cat-named-tom.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/05/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-cat-named-tom.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-05-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-cat-named-tom.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-04 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.728865+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to walk on the street with her mommy. One day, while they were walking, Lily saw a big, round ball on the street. She wanted to play with it, but she was too nervous to go near it.Her mommy noticed that Lily was feeling nervous and asked her what was wrong. Lily told her mommy about the ball and how she was too scared to go near it. Her mommy smiled and said, "Don't worry, I'll push you to the ball so you can play with it." Lily felt happy and grateful to her mommy for helping her. They walked to the ball together and Lily had so much fun playing with it. From that day on, Lily wasn't nervous anymore when she saw something on the street.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-04 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.728017+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim. Tim loved to go on vacation with his family. One day, Tim's family went on a vacation to a place where the sun was always shining.On this vacation, Tim saw a big, scary tree. He was scared and told his mom, "Mom, I don't believe there is a scary tree in the park." His mom smiled and said, "Don't worry, Tim. The tree is just big and scary because it has lots of leaves."Later, Tim met a new friend named Lily. Lily was not scared of the big, scary tree. She said, "Tim, I was scared too, but now I believe there is nothing to be scared of." Tim and Lily played together under the tree and had a lot of fun.At the end of the vacation, Tim learned that sometimes things that look scary are not so scary after all. He also learned that it's good to believe in yourself and your friends. And from that day on, Tim and Lily became best friends.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-04 - Once upon a time, there was a girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.727160+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a girl named Lily. She had a pale face and loved playing with her dolls. One day, Lily's mom asked her to help sort the clothes. Lily happily agreed and started sorting the clothes into piles.As she was sorting, Lily found a button that she had never seen before. She picked up the button and showed it to her mom. "Look, Mommy! A pretty button!" Lily exclaimed.Her mom smiled and said, "That's a nice button, Lily. Do you want to keep it?"Lily nodded excitedly and put the button in her pocket. From that day on, Lily always kept the button with her whenever she sorted the clothes. She felt very proud of herself for being such a good helper.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-charming-bird-named-blue.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-04 - Once upon a time, there was a charming bird named Blue</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.726437+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a charming bird named Blue. Blue loved to soar high in the sky. One day, Blue saw a hotel far away. Blue was very happy and wanted to go there.Blue flew to the hotel and saw many people. They were all having fun. Blue saw a little girl named Sue. Sue was sad because she lost her toy. Blue wanted to help Sue.Blue soared high in the sky and looked for the toy. He found it near a tree. Blue took the toy back to Sue. Sue was very happy and thanked Blue. Blue and Sue became best friends.The moral of the story is: Help others when they need it.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-charming-bird-named-blue.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/04/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-charming-bird-named-blue.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-04-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-charming-bird-named-blue.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-03-one-day,-a-cheerful-girl-named-lily-went-to-the-park.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-03 - One day, a cheerful girl named Lily went to the park</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.725681+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a cheerful girl named Lily went to the park. She saw her friend, Tim, who was trying to tie his shoes. Tim looked sad because he could not do it. Lily wanted to help Tim, so she went to him.Lily said, "I can help you tie your shoes, Tim." Tim was happy to have Lily's help. They tried and tried, but Tim still could not tie his shoes. Then, an older boy named Ben saw them and laughed. Ben did not think they could do it.Tim felt sad and Lily said, "Don't listen to Ben. We can do it if we try together." They tried one more time, and this time, they did it! Tim was very happy, and Lily was proud of their success.The moral of the story is to never give up and always help your friends. Sometimes, all you need to do is try a little harder, and you will succeed.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/03/one-day,-a-cheerful-girl-named-lily-went-to-the-park.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/03/one-day,-a-cheerful-girl-named-lily-went-to-the-park.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-03-one-day,-a-cheerful-girl-named-lily-went-to-the-park.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-03-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-03 - Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.724955+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy. Timmy loved going to the gym with his mom. He would run and jump and play with the other kids. One day, Timmy's mom asked him if he wanted to go to a new gym. Timmy said yes, but he didn't like the new gym. It was not as fun as his old gym.Timmy's mom was persistent and kept asking him to go to the new gym. She told him that it was important to be healthy and grow strong. Timmy didn't listen and kept saying no. But, his mom knew that Timmy needed to try new things, so she decided to record it on her phone.The next time they went to the new gym, Timmy saw that he had lots of fun playing with the other kids. He felt happy and healthy. Timmy learned that it's important to try new things, even if they're not what you're used to.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/03/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/03/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-03-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-03-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bald-man-named-tom.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-03 - Once upon a time, there was a bald man named Tom</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.724066+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a bald man named Tom. Tom loved to play with his friends in the park. One day, Tom found a small box with a lock. He was very curious about what was inside the box. He asked his friends to help him open the lock, but they could not. Tom decided to keep the box safe until he could find the key.Days went by, and Tom did not find the key. He was sad and thought about the box. One day, while playing in the park, he saw a key on the ground. He picked it up and thought it might open the lock. Tom was very excited and ran back to his house to try the key.Tom tried the key on the lock, and it opened! Inside the box, he found a beautiful necklace. He was so happy that he decided to give it to his mom as a gift. His mom was very proud of him for keeping the necklace safe. Tom learned that keeping things safe and trying hard can bring happiness.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/03/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bald-man-named-tom.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/03/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bald-man-named-tom.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-03-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bald-man-named-tom.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-03-once-upon-a-time,-a-little-boy-named-tim-had-a-big-book.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-03 - Once upon a time, a little boy named Tim had a big book</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.723295+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, a little boy named Tim had a big book. The book was full of history. He loved to read it every day. One day, while reading, he heard a voice. The voice said, "Hello, Tim. I am the history book. I can talk to you."Tim was very surprised. He said, "Wow, you can talk! That is amazing. I would love to hear a story from you. But, you must be serious. A story about a bad man who breaks everything."The history book said, "Okay, Tim. I will tell you a story about a bad man who broke many things. He was not nice, and no one liked him."Tim listened to the history book's story. He learned about the bad man who broke many things. Tim said, "Thank you for the story, history book. I will be serious when I read you."From that day on, Tim and the history book became good friends. Tim was serious when he read the history book, and the book was always there to tell him stories.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/03/once-upon-a-time,-a-little-boy-named-tim-had-a-big-book.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/03/once-upon-a-time,-a-little-boy-named-tim-had-a-big-book.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-03-once-upon-a-time,-a-little-boy-named-tim-had-a-big-book.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-02-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-02 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.722478+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to explore the forest and find new things. One day, she found a shiny rock that she thought was very pretty. She showed it to her friend, a talking bunny named Benny.Benny said, "That's a mineral, Lily. It's very special and valuable." Lily was happy to hear that and put the mineral in her pocket.As they were walking, they saw a big, scary bear. Benny said, "We need to be careful, Lily. Bears can be dangerous." Lily was scared, but she remembered that she had a secret weapon. She reached into her pocket and took out the mineral.She held it up and said, "I have this mineral. It's magical and will protect us." Suddenly, the mineral began to glow and shake. The bear was scared and ran away.Lily and Benny were amazed. They had never seen anything like it before. Lily looked at the mineral and said, "I guess this is truly special. Let's keep it safe." From that day</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/02/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/02/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-02-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-01-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-01 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.721661+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play outside and look for pretty things. One day, she saw a butterfly flying in the sky. It was so beautiful and colorful. She wanted to catch it, so she ran after it.As she was running, she saw her mom calling her for lunch. She was so hungry that she forgot about the butterfly and went inside. Her mom had made her favorite sandwich, but when she took a bite, she noticed that it was spoiled. She didn't like it at all.Lily went back outside and saw the beautiful butterfly again. She wanted to catch it, but it flew away. She felt sad and disappointed. She realized that she should have eaten her lunch instead of chasing after the butterfly. From that day on, she always remembered to eat her lunch and not chase after things that were too pretty to catch.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/01/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/01/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-01-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-01-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-brave-princess.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-01 - Once upon a time, there was a brave princess</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.720858+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a brave princess. She was on a mission to save her kingdom from a mean dragon. She rode on her horse and eventually arrived at the dragon's cave.The dragon was very angry when he saw the princess. He breathed fire and growled, but the princess stayed brave and stayed calm. She bravely asked the dragon to start a fight. The dragon was surprised by her bravery and he agreed to fight.The princess used all her strength to beat the dragon. After a long battle, the dragon was so tired that he fell asleep. The princess quickly took the dragon away to the kingdom. Everyone cheered for the brave princess and her victory. The kingdom was safe once again.The end.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/01/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-brave-princess.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/01/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-brave-princess.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-01-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-brave-princess.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-01-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-09-01 - Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.720047+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a little boy named Tim. Tim loved to read books. He had a big bookcase in his room. The bookcase was full of colorful books.One day, Tim saw a famous book on the top shelf of his bookcase. He wanted to read it, but he was too small to reach it. Tim asked his big sister, Sue, for help. "Sue, can you please help me get the famous book?" he said.Sue was happy to help her brother. She got the book down from the top shelf and gave it to Tim. They read the famous book together and learned many new things. Tim was so happy that he could read the book with Sue's help. And from that day on, they became the best of friends.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/01/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/09/01/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-09-01-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-31-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-31 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.719125+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to dance and twirl around in her pink dress. One day, she went to the store with her mommy to buy some ice cream.At the store, Lily saw her friend, Max. Max had a big bag of candy and Lily felt envious. She wanted some candy too. "Can I have some candy, Max?" she asked. Max shook his head and said, "No, Lily. You can't have any candy today."Lily felt sad, but she still danced around the store. As they left, Max's bag of candy fell and spilled all over the floor. "Oh no!" Max cried. "My candy!" Lily saw that Max was upset and decided to help him pick up the candy. They both laughed and danced around the store while they cleaned up the mess. In the end, Max even gave Lily some candy as a thank you.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/31/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/31/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-31-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-31-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-brown-mouse-named-max.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-31 - Once upon a time, there was a little brown mouse named Max</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.718194+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little brown mouse named Max. Max lived in a cozy hole in the wall of a big house. One day, Max heard a loud noise coming from outside. He peeked out and saw a big, scary cat appear in the yard.Max was scared, but he knew he had to stay safe. He ran back to his hole and told his family and friends about the cat. They all worked together to build a strong wall around their hole to protect themselves.The next day, the cat tried to appear at the yard, but he couldn't get through the wall of Max's house. Max felt safe and happy knowing he had protected his family and friends from the scary cat. From then on, Max made sure to always be on the lookout for any danger that might appear in his woodland home.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/31/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-brown-mouse-named-max.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/31/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-brown-mouse-named-max.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-31-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-brown-mouse-named-max.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-31-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-crane.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-31 - Once upon a time, there was a big crane</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.717344+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a big crane. The crane was very tall and had a long neck. It liked to lift heavy things and move them around. One day, the crane saw something unusual. It was a big rock that didn't fit in with the others. The crane tried to lift the rock, but it was too heavy.The crane decided to ask for help. It saw a little mouse and asked, "Can you help me lift this unusual rock?" The mouse said yes and together they lifted the rock and moved it to a new spot. The crane was very happy and thanked the mouse for its help. From that day on, the crane and the mouse became good friends and helped each other whenever they could.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/31/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-crane.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/31/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-crane.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-31-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-crane.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-30-one-day,-a-little-girl-named-amy-went-to-play-outside.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-30 - One day, a little girl named Amy went to play outside</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.716565+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a little girl named Amy went to play outside. She saw a big, impressive tree with pretty birds. Amy wanted to climb the tree, but she was too small. She felt sad.Amy found a soft cloth near the tree. She had an idea! She would go to her grandpa and ask for help. Maybe he could get her a ladder so she could climb the tree.Grandpa was very nice. He gave Amy a ladder and a big smile. She put the ladder near the tree and climbed up. Now, she could see the birds and feel happy. Amy thanked her grandpa and went home with a big smile.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/30/one-day,-a-little-girl-named-amy-went-to-play-outside.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/30/one-day,-a-little-girl-named-amy-went-to-play-outside.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-30-one-day,-a-little-girl-named-amy-went-to-play-outside.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-30-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-30 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.715760+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play with her toys and her friends. One day, Lily's friend fell down and hurt her hand. Lily wanted to prevent her friend from getting hurt again, so she gave her a band-aid.Lily's friend was happy and they continued playing together. Later, they played a game where they had to count to zero. Lily thought it was funny when she said "zero" instead of "zero". Her friend laughed too.At the end of the day, Lily was happy because she prevented her friend from getting hurt and everyone had fun playing together. She went to bed feeling proud of herself for being a good friend.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/30/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/30/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-30-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-30-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bear-who-lived-in-a-big-forest.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-30 - Once upon a time, there was a bear who lived in a big forest</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.714899+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a bear who lived in a big forest. The bear was very wild and he loved to play with his friends. One day, the bear decided to display his favorite toy to all his friends in the forest. He ran to the river and showed his toy to the fish. The fish thought it was very cool! Then, the bear showed his toy to the birds and the rabbits. They all thought it was amazing! The bear was happy that his friends liked his toy and he felt proud that he could display it. From that day on, the bear loved to show his toys to his friends in the forest.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/30/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bear-who-lived-in-a-big-forest.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/30/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bear-who-lived-in-a-big-forest.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-30-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-bear-who-lived-in-a-big-forest.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-29-one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-out-to-play.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-29 - One day, a boy named Tim went out to play</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.714016+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a boy named Tim went out to play. He saw a big puddle of wet water. He thought it was fun to jump in it. As he jumped, he became wet too. The water went everywhere!Tim saw an ugly bug near the puddle. The bug had many legs and big eyes. Tim said, "Hi, Mr. Bug! Do you want to play in the wet puddle with me?" The ugly bug looked at Tim and said, "Yes, I would like to play. I can turn into a pretty bug if I jump in the wet puddle."Tim and the ugly bug both jumped in the wet puddle. They turned into a pretty bug and played together. They had a lot of fun in the puddle. Soon, it was time for Tim to go home. He said goodbye to the ugly bug and went back to his house. Tim had a big smile on his face because he made a new friend.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/29/one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-out-to-play.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/29/one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-out-to-play.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-29-one-day,-a-boy-named-tim-went-out-to-play.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-29 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.713166+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved ice cream and her mom kept it in the freezer. One day, Lily went to get some ice cream but the freezer was empty. She was very sad.Lily asked her mom, "Where is the ice cream?" Her mom replied, "We finished it all. It's all gone now." Lily was very serious and said, "What are we going to do? I really wanted ice cream."Her mom said, "Don't worry, we can make our own ice cream together." Lily was happy and they made some ice cream. But when they took it out of the freezer, they saw that it had melted. Lily was very upset and said, "Now we can't eat ice cream anymore." Her mom replied, "It's okay, we can try again next time." And they both smiled.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-29 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.712385+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to play outside and explore the world around him. One day, Timmy's mom said, "Let's go for a walk in the park!" Timmy was so excited and said, "Yes, let's go!"As they walked, Timmy saw a big structure made of blocks. He said, "Mommy, look at that big building!" His mom said, "Yes, that's a very kind man who made it." Timmy was curious and asked, "What does kind mean?" His mom explained, "It means he made something for people to use and like."After their walk, Timmy was tired and wanted to sleep. His mom said, "Let's go home and you can sleep in your bed." Timmy went to bed and fell asleep quickly because he was so tired from his adventure in the park.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-kind-bunny-named-benny.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-29 - Once upon a time, there was a kind bunny named Benny</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.711535+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a kind bunny named Benny. Benny loved to hop and play in the forest. One day, while he was hopping along, he saw a little bird sitting on a branch. The bird looked sad.Benny asked, "Why are you sad?"The bird said, "I lost my way home. I don't know where to go."Benny felt compassionate for the little bird. He said, "Don't worry. I can help you find your way home. Just hop on my back and we'll find it together."The bird hopped on Benny's back and they hopped through the forest. After a while, they found the bird's home. The bird was so happy that he started to sing. Benny smiled and said, "I'm glad I could help you."Just then, Benny's zipper on his jacket broke. He didn't know what to do. The little bird said, "Don't worry. I can help you fix your zipper." The bird helped Benny fix his zipper and they both continued to be friends. From that day on,</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-kind-bunny-named-benny.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/29/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-kind-bunny-named-benny.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-29-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-kind-bunny-named-benny.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-28-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-28 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.710672+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play outside in the sun. One day, her mommy said, "Lily, it's time to go to the park. But you need to put on your sunscreen so you don't get sunburned."Lily replied, "Okay mommy, I will put on my sunscreen." She ran to the park and started playing on the swings. After a while, she got very hot and thirsty. She went to the water fountain and drank some water.Suddenly, a little boy came to her and said, "I like your jewel necklace. It's very pretty." Lily smiled and said, "Thank you! It's my mommy's necklace." The little boy said, "Can I wear it for a little bit?" Lily thought for a moment and said, "Okay, but you have to give it back to me." The little boy wore the necklace for a little while and then gave it back to Lily. They played together for a little while longer and had a lot of fun. When it was time to go</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/28/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/28/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-28-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-28-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bunny-named-ben.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-28 - Once upon a time, there was a little bunny named Ben</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.709794+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little bunny named Ben. Ben loved to eat yummy carrots all day. One day, he found a calendar on the ground. It had pictures of yummy carrots on it. Ben was very happy and showed it to his friend, Tina the turtle.Tina said, "I recommend you share the yummy carrots with others. Sharing is good." Ben thought about it and decided to share the calendar with all his friends.Ben and his friends looked at the calendar together. They saw many yummy carrots pictures. They learned that sharing is caring. From that day on, Ben and his friends always shared their yummy food with each other. They were all happy and played together every day.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/28/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bunny-named-ben.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/28/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bunny-named-ben.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-28-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-bunny-named-ben.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-27-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-little-girl-called-poppy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-27 - Once upon a time there was a little girl called Poppy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.708969+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time there was a little girl called Poppy. She was only three years old, but she had a big dream. She wanted to be a fast runner! So every day, Poppy would run all around the park, practice running as fast as she could.One day, Poppy chose to go to the library. She wanted to read about running races. When she got there, Poppy was so excited. She looked around the library until she found the perfect book. It was full of pictures and words about running fast.Poppy read the book and couldn't wait to try running like the cheetahs in the story. She was determined to become a fast runner. She ran around the library, up and down the stairs, and all the way around the park.But no matter how fast Poppy ran, she couldn't seem to keep up with the other runners. She was tired and sad.But then Poppy remembered something her mum had said: 'When something doesn't go your way, try again!'. So Poppy decided to try again the next day.And sure enough, Poppy ran even faster than before! She felt so proud of herself that she laughed</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/27/once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-little-girl-called-poppy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/27/once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-little-girl-called-poppy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-27-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-little-girl-called-poppy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-27-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-27 - Once upon a time, there was a girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.708163+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a girl named Lily. She loved chocolate more than anything in the world. One day, Lily's friend came over to play. Her friend was very thoughtful and brought some chocolate for Lily to eat. Lily was so happy and said, "Thank you for the chocolate, it looks so yummy!"Lily's friend said, "I have a surprise for you. I brought my favorite toy, a teddy bear. Do you want to play with it?" Lily replied, "Yes, please!" They played with the teddy bear for a while, but then Lily started to feel sick. She said to her friend, "I don't feel good. My tummy hurts." Her friend said, "Maybe you just ate too much chocolate. Let's go lie down and rest."Lily and her friend went to lie down and rest. After a while, Lily felt better and said, "Thank you for being such a thoughtful friend. I feel much better now." Her friend smiled and said, "You're welcome. I'm glad you're feeling better." Lily</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/27/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/27/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-27-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-27-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-lawyer.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-27 - Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a lawyer</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.707364+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a lawyer. He was a bit weird. He liked to give things to people. He gave toys, food, and clothes to people who needed them.One day, the lawyer met a little girl. She was sad because she lost her toy. The lawyer wanted to help her. So, he gave her a new toy. The girl was very happy.The weird lawyer felt good. He liked to give and help others. From that day on, he gave more and more things to people in his town. Everyone loved the weird lawyer. And they all lived happily ever after.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/27/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-lawyer.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/27/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-lawyer.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-27-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-lawyer.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-27-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-house,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-27 - Once upon a time, in a small house, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.706545+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a small house, there was a little boy named Tim. Tim loved to play with his toys and make noise. One day, he was playing with his loud toy drum. He was so happy and having fun. But, he was also being foolish.Tim's mom asked him to be quiet because his baby sister was sleeping. But Tim did not listen. He kept playing his drum and making noise. His baby sister woke up and started to cry. Tim's mom was not happy.Tim's mom told him that he needed to be more quiet. She said, "If you don't stop making noise, I will have to punish you." Tim did not want to be punished, so he decided to play with his toys in a quiet place. He learned that being foolish was not good, and he didn't want to make his baby sister cry again.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/27/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-house,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/27/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-house,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-27-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-house,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-26-one-day,-a-little-boy-named-tim-and-his-dog,-spot,-went-to-the-park.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-26 - One day, a little boy named Tim and his dog, Spot, went to the park</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.705643+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a little boy named Tim and his dog, Spot, went to the park. They loved to play together. Tim would throw a ball and Spot would run to get it. They played and played all day long."Spot, I love playing with you!" said Tim. Spot barked happily and wagged his tail. But then, Tim saw a big tree with a scary face on it. He was afraid. "I don't want to play here, Spot," said Tim. Spot barked and tried to comfort Tim. "Don't be scared, Tim!" Spot barked.Suddenly, the scary face on the tree disappeared! But it was not Tim's face on Spot. It was a friendly squirrel! The squirrel had been playing hide and seek. Tim and Spot laughed. They were not scared anymore. They played with the squirrel and had a lot of fun at the park.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/26/one-day,-a-little-boy-named-tim-and-his-dog,-spot,-went-to-the-park.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/26/one-day,-a-little-boy-named-tim-and-his-dog,-spot,-went-to-the-park.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-26-one-day,-a-little-boy-named-tim-and-his-dog,-spot,-went-to-the-park.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-26-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-26 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.704781+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to help her mom in the garden. One day, Lily's mom asked her to try pulling out the same herb that they were planting. Lily tried her best, but the herb was too strong for her little hands.Suddenly, a big, smelly skunk came by and started to spray them with its smelly spray. Lily's mom quickly grabbed her and ran inside the house. They were both covered in the smelly skunk spray and had to take a bath to get clean.After their bath, Lily's mom told her a story about a girl who tried to pull out a whole herb with a strong breath, but it didn't work and only blew out the skunk's smelly spray. The girl realized that sometimes it's better to wait for help instead of trying to do everything by yourself.Lily learned her lesson and never tried to pull out the wrong herb again. She also learned to be careful around smelly animals.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/26/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/26/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-26-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-25-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-girl-named-lucy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-25 - Once upon a time there was a girl named Lucy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.703893+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time there was a girl named Lucy. She was very independent and liked to do things on her own. One day, Lucy was playing with her toys, when she started to feel like she had to sneeze. So, she put her hands on her nose and tapped them.Suddenly, her mom appeared. "What are you doing, Lucy?" she asked.Lucy smiled and said, "I was sneezing!"Her mom laughed and said, "That's great, dear! Keep playing."So Lucy went back to her toys, feeling very independent. But she soon forgot all about her sneeze. Later on, she went to the park and was having so much fun!</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/25/once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-girl-named-lucy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/25/once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-girl-named-lucy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-25-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-girl-named-lucy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-25-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-25 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.703079+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to eat grapes, but one day she ate too many and her tummy hurt. Lily said, "Ouch, my tummy hurts!" Her mommy gave her some medicine and told her to rest.While she was resting, Lily heard a loud noise outside. She looked out the window and saw a big bird. The bird was trying to take her grapes! Lily didn't want the bird to take her grapes, so she said, "Stop, bird! Those are my grapes!"The bird didn't listen and kept trying to take the grapes. Lily got upset and said, "Mommy, help! The bird is taking my grapes!" Her mommy went outside and scared the bird away. Lily was happy that her grapes were safe and she could eat them without any more trouble.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/25/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/25/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-25-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-25-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-talk.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-25 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily who loved to talk</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.702180+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily who loved to talk. She talked all day long and never stopped. One day, her mommy took her to a museum. Lily saw lots of pretty things and talked about them.Then, she saw a big painting with lots of colors. She asked her mommy if she could paint like that too. Her mommy said that she could, but Lily had to be patient and practice.Lily practiced every day and became very patient. She sang and talked while she got better. One day, she got a microphone and sang a song in front of everyone at the museum. They all clapped and cheered for her. Lily was so happy that she talked about it all the time.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/25/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-talk.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/25/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-talk.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-25-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-talk.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-25-lily-and-max-were-playing-in-the-garden.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-25 - Lily and Max were playing in the garden</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.701356+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Lily and Max were playing in the garden. They liked to find out which flowers wereoming. Lily saw a big red flower and said, "Look, Max, this one is pretty!" Max saw a yellow flower and said, "Look, Lily, this one is bright!"They ran to their mom, who was sitting on a bench. They asked her, "Mom, what are these flowers?" Mom smiled and said, "These are sunflowers. They bloom in the summer. They are very beautiful, aren't they?" Lily and Max nodded and said, "Yes, they are!"Mom said, "Do you want to see more flowers?" Lily and Max said, "Yes, please!" Mom took them to another part of the garden, where there were more sunflowers. They saw a big yellow sunflower that was taller than Lily and Max. Lily said, "Wow, look at that one! It is so big!" Max said, "It is bigger than you! It is the biggest!"Mom said, "That is a sunflower, Max. They are very rare. They grow the best ones in the whole</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/25/lily-and-max-were-playing-in-the-garden.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/25/lily-and-max-were-playing-in-the-garden.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-25-lily-and-max-were-playing-in-the-garden.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-24-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-24 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.700480+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play outside and explore the world around her. One day, she found a pretty butterfly and followed it into the forest.As she walked deeper into the forest, she met a friendly squirrel who asked her what she was doing. "I'm looking for the spirit of the forest," Lily said with a smile.The squirrel replied, "The spirit of the forest is hidden behind those trees. But be careful, there's a disgusting smell coming from a skunk."Lily nodded and continued on her adventure, excited to find the spirit of the forest. Eventually, she found the skunk and quickly ran away. She was scared but happy to have seen the spirit of the forest.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/24/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/24/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-24-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-24-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-clever-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-24 - Once upon a time, there was a clever boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.699589+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a clever boy named Tim. Tim loved to play with his toy violin. He played it every day and made happy songs.One day, Tim saw a big tree with a bird's nest. He wanted to see the baby birds, so he climbed the tree. But, oh no! He was not careful and he started to fall.Tim held his violin tight and closed his eyes. As he fell, his violin opened up like a big umbrella. Tim landed on the soft grass. The baby birds were safe and happy. Tim was a hero!</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/24/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-clever-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/24/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-clever-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-24-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-clever-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-24-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-24 - Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.698715+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy. He loved to play outside in the park. One day, he found a glove on the ground. It was a big glove, and it looked very strange. Timmy asked his friend, "Can you help me find the owner of this glove? It's unknown whose it is."His friend said, "Sure, let's go ask the people in the park if they lost a glove." They walked around and asked everyone they saw if they lost a glove. But nobody said they lost it.Suddenly, Timmy's friend saw a man walking towards them. He shouted, "Excuse me, sir! Is this your glove?" The man looked at the glove and said, "Yes! That's my glove! Thank you so much for finding it." Timmy and his friend were very happy to help the man. They marched back home, feeling proud of themselves for being kind to someone who lost their glove.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/24/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/24/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-24-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-23-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-powerful-lion-named-leo.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-23 - Once upon a time, there was a powerful lion named Leo</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.697819+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a powerful lion named Leo. Leo had a big, soft sweater. He loved to wear it every day. One day, Leo met a little bunny named Ben. Ben saw the sweater and thought it was nice."Can I borrow your sweater?" asked Ben. Leo said, "Yes, you can borrow my sweater." Ben was very happy. He put on the sweater and it made him feel warm and cozy.Later, they found a big tree with lots of yummy fruit. Leo used his powerful paws to get the fruit. Ben and Leo sat under the tree, eating the fruit together. They became best friends and shared the sweater when they needed it.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/23/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-powerful-lion-named-leo.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/23/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-powerful-lion-named-leo.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-23-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-powerful-lion-named-leo.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-23-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-23 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.696972+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She twisted a balloon into a shape that looked like a flower. She was so happy and showed it to her mom. Her mom said it was beautiful and put it on the fridge.One day, Lily woke up and saw the sun shining bright. She felt happy and wanted to play outside. She ran to the park and saw a boy playing with a shiny red ball. She wanted to play with it too, but the boy didn't want to share. Lily felt sad and went back home.When she got home, she saw her balloon on the table. But something was different. It wasn't peaceful anymore. It was dark and scary. She picked it up and heard a loud noise. Suddenly, the balloon exploded and scared her. She started crying and her mom came to comfort her. From that day on, Lily learned to share her toys and be careful with things that twist and change.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/23/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/23/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-23-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-23-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-yellow-truck-named-max.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-23 - Once upon a time, there was a big yellow truck named Max</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.696124+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a big yellow truck named Max. Max loved to drive on the wide road and show off his shiny paint. One day, Max was driving so fast that he didn't pay attention to the mechanic's red light. The car suddenly broke down and Max got very sad.After a while, a kind man came and helped Max. The man was the driver of a tow truck, and he knew how to fix any car. The tow truck driver said Max needed a new light and Max was excited. The tow truck driver changed Max's light, and Max was happy again.But then, something unexpected happened. The tow truck driver had to go to a store to supply some tools for Max. Max was sad again because he thought he wouldn't be able to drive without the new light. But then, the store owner surprised Max by giving him a special new light that would keep him driving safely. Max was so happy and grateful for the tow truck driver's help. From that day on, Max always made sure to pay attention to the rules of the road.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/23/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-yellow-truck-named-max.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/23/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-yellow-truck-named-max.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-23-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-yellow-truck-named-max.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-23-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-farm.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-23 - Once upon a time, there was a big farm</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.695187+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a big farm. On the farm, there was a little horse named Sam. Sam was not like the other horses. He was sad because he was uncomfortable. His jumping made it hard for him to run and play.One day, Sam's friend, a little bird named Tim, came to visit. Tim saw Sam feeling sad and asked, "Why are you so sad, Sam?" Sam told Tim about his uncomfortable jumping. Tim wanted to help Sam, so he had an idea.Tim told Sam to close his eyes and imagine a big, soft nest. Sam closed his eyes and imagined himself in a cozy nest. When he opened his eyes, he felt his jumping go away. Now, Sam could run and play without any trouble. Sam was so happy, and he and Tim played all day long.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/23/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-farm.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/23/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-farm.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-23-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-big-farm.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-22 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.693846+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play with her toy cart and push it around the house. One day, Lily's mom asked her to help deliver some cookies to their neighbor, Mrs. Smith.Lily was excited to help and started pulling her cart through the streets. As she walked, she saw a big, scary dog in the distance. She felt scared and wanted to run away, but she knew that she had to deliver the cookies to Mrs. Smith.Lily took a deep breath and kept walking, slowly but surely. When she finally arrived at Mrs. Smith's house, she saw that she had moved away. Lily felt sad and didn't know what to do. But then she remembered the cookies in her cart and offered some to Mrs. Smith. She smiled and thanked Lily for delivering them. From that day on, Lily wasn't as scared of dogs and always carried cookies with her in her cart.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-22 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.692988+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. Timmy was feeling sick, so his mommy took his temperature with a thermometer. The thermometer was a stick that beeped when it was done.Timmy's mommy looked at the thermometer and saw that Timmy had a fever. She gave him some medicine to make him feel better. Timmy drank the medicine and then went to bed.Later that night, Timmy heard a noise outside his window. He got scared and called out to his mommy. She came running and told him not to be afraid, it was just the wind. Timmy felt better and went back to sleep.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-bunny-named-benny.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-22 - Once upon a time, there was a chubby bunny named Benny</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.692136+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a chubby bunny named Benny. Benny loved to play with his favorite toy, a missile. He would spend hours throwing it around and imagining it was flying through the sky.One day, Benny's mom told him it was time for his nap. Benny didn't want to stop playing with his missile, but he knew he must listen to his mom. He put his missile down and closed his eyes.Suddenly, Benny's missile started to blink and shake! Benny opened his eyes and saw that his missile had come to life and was flying around his room! Benny was so surprised and excited that he couldn't stop giggling.From that day on, Benny and his missile became the best of friends. They would play together every day and Benny was always so happy when he was with his trusty friend.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-bunny-named-benny.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/22/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-bunny-named-benny.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-22-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-bunny-named-benny.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-21 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.691312+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She was very sleepy and wanted to take a nap. She went to her room and lay down on her bed. She closed her eyes and fell asleep.While she was sleeping, her mommy came in and mentioned that they were going to have ice cream for dessert. Lily woke up and got very excited. She loved ice cream!Mommy took Lily to the kitchen and they got some ice cream. It was so yummy! After they finished, Lily went back to her room and fell asleep again. She dreamt about all the fun she had with mommy and the delicious ice cream.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-ant.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-21 - Once upon a time, there was a little ant</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.690437+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little ant. The ant was very scared of all the big things around him. One day, the ant met a friendly butterfly. The butterfly asked the ant why he was so scared. The ant told the butterfly that he was afraid of everything.The butterfly told the ant not to be afraid and that he should try to part ways with things that scared him. The ant listened to the butterfly and decided to be brave. He started to walk around and explore the world.As the ant continued to explore, he noticed that the world wasn't so scary anymore. In fact, he found that he enjoyed looking at all the different flowers and insects that lived there. The moral of the story is that sometimes it's good to part ways from scary things and try new things.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-ant.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-ant.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-ant.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-21 - Once upon a time, there was a chubby little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.689483+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a chubby little girl named Lily. She loved to play outside with her friends. One day, Lily and her friends went for a walk in the park. They saw a big mountain and Lily wanted to climb it.Lily said, "I want to climb that mountain!"Her friends said, "We can't climb it, we're too small."Lily felt sad because she really wanted to climb the mountain. Suddenly, a friendly dog came up to her and said, "I can help you climb the mountain!"Lily was surprised and happy. She followed the dog up the mountain and they reached the top. From there, they could see the whole park. Lily was happy and grateful to the dog for helping her.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-chubby-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-beautiful-horse-named-bella.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-21 - Once upon a time, there was a beautiful horse named Bella</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.688640+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a beautiful horse named Bella. Bella lived in a big field with her friends. They liked to run and play all day.One sunny day, Bella saw a little girl named Lily. Lily was sad. Bella wanted to help. She walked to Lily and whispered, "Why are you sad?"Lily looked at Bella and said, "I lost my ball. Can you help me find it?" Bella nodded her head and they both started to look for the ball. They looked under the trees and behind the bushes. Finally, they found the ball near a big rock.Lily was very happy and hugged Bella. She said, "Thank you, Bella! You are the best horse ever!" They played together all day long and became the best of friends. From that day on, Bella and Lily always played together in the big field.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-beautiful-horse-named-bella.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/21/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-beautiful-horse-named-bella.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-21-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-beautiful-horse-named-bella.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-one-day,-a-big-dog-and-a-little-cat-were-playing-by-a-tree.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-20 - One day, a big dog and a little cat were playing by a tree</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.687769+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One day, a big dog and a little cat were playing by a tree. The big dog saw a long vine hanging from the tree. He had an idea. He said to the little cat, "Let's swing on the vine like crazy monkeys!"The little cat was scared, but she wanted to try. So, they both held on to the vine and started to swing. They swung back and forth, laughing and having fun. Then, the big dog said, "Let's jump off the vine and see what happens!"The little cat was still scared, but she wanted to be brave like the big dog. So, she jumped off the vine and landed on the soft grass. She was so happy and proud of herself.The big dog and little cat learned that it's okay to be scared, but it's also important to be brave and try new things. They had lots of fun swinging on the vine together, and they knew they could do anything if they tried.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/one-day,-a-big-dog-and-a-little-cat-were-playing-by-a-tree.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/one-day,-a-big-dog-and-a-little-cat-were-playing-by-a-tree.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-one-day,-a-big-dog-and-a-little-cat-were-playing-by-a-tree.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-20 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.686831+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She lived in a big house with her mommy and daddy. One day, Lily heard a loud noise coming from upstairs. She was scared, so she called for her mommy."Mommy, I hear a loud noise upstairs. Can you come and help me?" asked Lily.Her mommy came upstairs and listened. She heard the noise too and said, "Don't worry, sweetie. It's just the wind outside. It's making a loud noise."Lily felt better knowing it was just the wind. She hugged her mommy and said, "Thank you for helping me. You're the best!"</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-gray-cat.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-20 - Once upon a time, there was a gray cat</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.685917+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a gray cat. The cat loved to eat popcorn. One day, the cat went to the kitchen to find some popcorn.The cat found a big bowl of popcorn on the table. The cat was very happy. It started to eat the popcorn very fast. The cat wanted to finish the popcorn before it was all gone.But then, the cat ate too much popcorn. It started to feel sick. The cat ate so much popcorn that it could not move. In the end, the gray cat was very sad and sick because it ate too much popcorn.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-gray-cat.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-gray-cat.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-gray-cat.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-20 - Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.685237+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to play outside and explore the world around him. One day, Timmy's mommy gave him a pair of sunglasses to wear. They were shiny and cool, and Timmy loved them very much.As he was walking around, Timmy saw a big, scary dog. He wanted to run away, but he remembered what his mommy had told him. "If you ever feel scared, just stand still and don't move. The dog won't hurt you if you stay calm."Timmy stood still and the dog walked away. He was so happy that he had listened to his mommy's advice. As he continued to explore, he met a nice lady who asked him about his sunglasses. "These are my new sunglasses," Timmy said proudly. "They make me look cool."The lady smiled and said, "You look awesome, Timmy. I wish I had sunglasses like that." Timmy smiled back and said, "You can borrow them if you want. I'm always happy to share." The lady thanked Timmy and put on</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/20/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-20-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-one-sunny-day,-a-bird-named-billy-wanted-to-soar-high-in-the-sky.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-19 - One sunny day, a bird named Billy wanted to soar high in the sky</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.684517+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>One sunny day, a bird named Billy wanted to soar high in the sky. He flapped his wings and went up, up, up! Billy was so happy to fly and see all the things below him.As he flew, he saw an elderly dog named Daisy. Daisy was sitting on a soft, green lawn. She looked up and saw Billy flying high. "Hello, Billy!" she said. "You are so good at flying!"Billy smiled at Daisy and said, "Thank you, Daisy! I love to soar in the sky. It makes me feel so free!" Daisy wagged her tail and watched Billy fly away. She knew that Billy was happy and healthy, and she was happy just to see him soar.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/one-sunny-day,-a-bird-named-billy-wanted-to-soar-high-in-the-sky.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/one-sunny-day,-a-bird-named-billy-wanted-to-soar-high-in-the-sky.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-one-sunny-day,-a-bird-named-billy-wanted-to-soar-high-in-the-sky.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-19 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.683790+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to play with her toys and her favorite toy was a small red ball. One day, Lily's mom asked her to help in the kitchen. Lily was excited to help her mom, so she went to the kitchen.Lily's mom asked her to lift a glass of water from the faucet. Lily tried to lift the glass, but it was too heavy for her. She tried again, but she still couldn't lift it. Suddenly, Lily's red ball bounced into the kitchen and hit the glass. The glass fell and broke into many pieces.Lily was scared and started to cry. Her mom hugged her and told her that accidents happen and it's okay. They cleaned up the mess together and Lily felt better. From that day on, Lily learned to be more careful when she lifted things in the kitchen.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-19 - Once upon a time, there was a girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.682966+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a girl named Lily. She had a large purse that she loved to carry everywhere. One day, Lily went to the park to play with her friends. While playing, she saw a butterfly and tried to catch it. But the butterfly flew away and she couldn't catch it.Lily's friend, Sarah, saw her struggle and said, "I have an idea! Let's make a butterfly net with a stick and a piece of cloth." Lily was happy and they quickly made the net together. They went back to the park and tried using their new net. After a few tries, they finally caught the butterfly. Lily was so happy that she could hardly contain herself. She said, "Thank you, Sarah! You helped me catch the butterfly!"</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-19 - Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.682086+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to ride in his motorcycle. One day, Timmy's mommy told him they were going on a trip. Timmy was so excited! But he had to pack his bags first. Timmy packed his toys and clothes, and even his motorcycle to take with him.When they arrived at their destination, Timmy's mommy told him to unpack his bags. Timmy didn't like unpacking because it was boring. But he did it anyway. As he unpacked, he found a toy that was very attractive. It was a big red truck that he had never seen before. Timmy was so happy to have found it!After they finished unpacking, Timmy got back in his motorcycle and they went for a ride. Timmy was so excited to show off his new truck to everyone. He was happy he remembered to pack it.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/19/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-19-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-18-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-18 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.681229+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. One day, she went to the park to play with her friend, Timmy. They played on the swings and the slide, and Lily said, "Look, Timmy! We can draw silly faces on the ground!"Timmy thought that was a great idea, so they started drawing silly faces with sticks and stones. Suddenly, they heard a loud noise. It was a group of birds flying overhead.Lily said, "Wow, that bird sounds so pretty!" Timmy agreed and said, "Let's feed them some bread crumbs."So, they ran to get some bread crumbs and threw them on the ground. The birds came down and ate the crumbs happily. Lily and Timmy were so happy to see the birds enjoying their snack. They continued to play and have fun at the park until it was time to go home.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/18/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/18/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-18-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-18-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-with-rocks.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-18 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily who loved to play with rocks</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.680354+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily who loved to play with rocks. She would collect them and build little houses for them. One day, she found a shiny rock that she really liked. She showed it to her friend, Timmy, and said, "Look at my pretty rock!"Timmy looked at the rock and said, "That's a nice rock, but it's not as valuable as your other rocks."Lily didn't understand what he meant, so she asked, "What do you mean?"Timmy replied, "It means someone may say your rock is worth a lot of money."Lily felt sad and didn't want her rock to be worth a lot of money. She decided to bury it in a deep hole so no one could take it. But when she finished burying it, she realized she had lost something very important in the screw she was carrying. She became very upset and cried. Her friends tried to help her find it, but it was impossible. Lily never found her shiny rock again.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/18/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-with-rocks.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/18/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-with-rocks.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-18-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily-who-loved-to-play-with-rocks.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-18-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-18 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.679417+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Tim. Tim loved to eat yummy food. One day, his mom made him a big plate of yummy food. It had pink fruits, green veggies, and orange juice. Tim was so happy to see all the yummy food on his plate.But then, Tim's little sister, Sue, came into the room. Sue was very hungry too. She tried to take Tim's plate away from him. Tim did not want to lose his yummy food, so he held onto the plate very tight.Sue pulled harder and harder, but Tim was strong. Finally, Sue let go of the plate and it fell to the floor. The plate broke into many pieces. Tim was sad that his yummy food was gone. But his mom came into the room with a new plate of yummy food for him. Tim was happy again, and he shared his new plate with Sue. They both enjoyed the yummy food together.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/18/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/18/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-18-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-wealthy-man-who-had-a-big-car.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-17 - Once upon a time, there was a wealthy man who had a big car</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.678501+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a wealthy man who had a big car. He loved his car very much. One day, he went for a ride in his car. He saw a little boy playing with a toy car. The little boy looked sad.The wealthy man stopped his car and asked the little boy, "Why are you sad? Do you want to play with my car?" The little boy looked at the car and smiled. "Yes, please! I love cars too," he said. The wealthy man was happy to share his car with the little boy.As they played, the wealthy man stumble on a big rock. His car made a loud noise. Suddenly, the car started to fly in the air! The little boy laughed and clapped his hands. The wealthy man and the little boy flew around in the sky, having the best time ever. The car was no longer just a toy, but a magical flying car!</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-wealthy-man-who-had-a-big-car.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-wealthy-man-who-had-a-big-car.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-wealthy-man-who-had-a-big-car.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-17 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.677547+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She lived in a big house with her mommy and daddy. One day, Lily went outside to play in the garden. She saw a big tree and wondered what was on top of it. She asked her mommy, "Can you help me get the top of the tree?" Her mommy said, "Sure, I can help you."Her mommy picked her up and lifted her high over the tree. Lily looked up and saw a beautiful bird's nest. She said, "Wow, look at the bird's nest!" Her mommy said, "Yes, it's very pretty." Lily asked, "Can we take a closer look?" Her mommy said, "No, we shouldn't touch it. We don't want to hurt the birds."Lily was sad she couldn't see the bird's nest up close, but she was happy her mommy helped her. They went back inside the house and had some cookies. Lily said, "Today was a good day. I wonder what other things I can see." Her mommy said, "We can always find things we wonder</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-17 - Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a little girl named Sue</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.676567+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a small town, there was a little girl named Sue. She was a fearful girl who was scared of many things. One day, Sue was walking with her mom when they saw a big, black door. Sue wanted to know what was behind the door, but she was too scared to open it.Sue's mom said, "Let's go see what's behind the door." Sue was scared, but she held her mom's hand and they walked closer to the door. Sue's mom gave her a little slap on the hand and said, "You can do it!"Sue took a deep breath and opened the door. To her surprise, there was a big, colorful room filled with toys and games! Sue was so happy and not fearful anymore. She played with the toys and had lots of fun. The black door had given her a beautiful place to play and be brave. From that day on, Sue was a brave little girl and was not scared of the black door anymore.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-small-town,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-sue.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-normal-little-town,-there-was-a-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-17 - Once upon a time, in a normal little town, there was a boy named Tim</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.675657+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, in a normal little town, there was a boy named Tim. Tim loved to poke things with his finger. One day, he went to the park with his mom. At the park, he saw a big tree with a hole in it. Tim thought it was a secret place, but he didn't know what was inside."Mom, what's in the tree hole?" Tim asked. His mom didn't know, so she said, "I don't know, Tim. Maybe we can find out later. But first, let's play on the swings." Tim played on the swings, but he still wanted to know what was in the tree hole.Later, when it was time to go home, Tim and his mom walked to the tree hole. Tim poked the hole with his finger. Suddenly, a small squirrel jumped out! Tim was so surprised. The squirrel looked at Tim and said, "Thank you for poking the hole. I was stuck inside. I've been waiting for someone to help me get out." Tim and his mom smiled, happy that they had solved the secret of the squirrel.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-normal-little-town,-there-was-a-boy-named-tim.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/17/once-upon-a-time,-in-a-normal-little-town,-there-was-a-boy-named-tim.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-17-once-upon-a-time,-in-a-normal-little-town,-there-was-a-boy-named-tim.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-16 - Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.674876+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Lily. She loved to eat fruit, especially apples, bananas, and oranges. One day, her mom took her to the store to buy some fruit. Lily was very excited and asked her mom if they could buy some apples or bananas. Her mom said yes, and they went inside the store.Lily saw a man who was very successful at selling fruit. He had many different fruits like oranges, grapes, and strawberries. Lily looked at the fruits and said, "Wow, these are all different kinds of fruit, but I want to choose some apples and bananas." Her mom smiled and said, "Okay, let's get some apples and bananas."Lily was very happy with her choice of fruit. She said to her mom, "I love fruit! Can we eat them now?" Her mom said, "Yes, let's go home and have some fruit together." Lily smiled and said, "Yay, fruit is my favorite!"</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-girl-named-lily.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-16 - Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.674019+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a little boy named Timmy. Timmy loved to play outside in the grass and pick flowers. One day, he saw a little fairy sitting on a flower."Hello, fairy!" said Timmy."Hello, little boy," said the fairy. "I'm here to help you.""How can you help me?" asked Timmy."I can make you wealthy," said the fairy. "But you must promise to share your flowers with others."Timmy agreed and the fairy sprinkled some dust on his flowers. Suddenly, Timmy's flowers grew bigger and bigger until he had as many as a car!But then, something unexpected happened. A big gust of wind blew all of Timmy's flowers away. Timmy was sad, but the fairy said, "Don't worry, little boy. I'll bring you more flowers tomorrow." And with a wave of her wand, Timmy's flowers grew even bigger and more beautiful than before. Timmy was very happy and thanked the fairy for her help.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-little-boy-named-timmy.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry><entry><id>https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-sue.txt.mp3</id><title>2023-08-16 - Once upon a time, there was a girl named Sue</title><updated>2023-12-25T10:32:16.673090+00:00</updated><author><name>Tony Mamacos</name><email>tmamacos@gmail.com</email></author><content>Once upon a time, there was a girl named Sue. Sue had a long brush. She loved to count with her brush. One day, she went outside to play.Sue saw a big tree. She wanted to count its leaves. She started counting, "One, two, three..." But then, a cat jumped out of the tree! Sue was very surprised.The cat said, "Thank you for counting my leaves. I am a magic cat!" Sue was happy to help. The magic cat gave Sue a wish. Sue wished for more toys to play with. They played together all day and became best friends.</content><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-sue.html" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://ttech.mamacos.media/storytime/post/2023/08/16/once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-sue.html" rel="self"/><link href="https://github.com/tonym128/storytime/raw/main/media/2023-08-16-once-upon-a-time,-there-was-a-girl-named-sue.txt.mp3" rel="enclosure" type="audio/mpeg"/></entry></feed>